1	Throughout	throughout	IN	O	5	case
2	Robert	Robert	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
4	's	's	POS	O	3	case
5	article	article	NN	O	13	nmod
6	`	`	``	O	7	punct
7	Attention	attention	NN	O	5	dep
8	Wholefood	wholefood	NN	O	9	compound
9	Shoppers	shopper	NNS	O	7	nmod:poss
10	'	'	POS	O	9	case
11	,	,	,	O	13	punct
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	implores	implore	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	need	need	NN	O	24	nsubj
16	for	for	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	elite	elite	NN	O	19	compound
19	fixation	fixation	NN	O	15	nmod
20	over	over	IN	O	22	case
21	organic	organic	JJ	O	22	amod
22	food	food	NN	O	19	nmod
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	change	change	VB	O	13	ccomp
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
27	recentralize	recentralize	VB	O	24	conj
28	their	they	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	focus	focus	NN	O	27	dobj
30	on	on	IN	O	31	mark
31	supporting	support	VBG	O	27	advcl
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	developing	develop	VBG	O	34	amod
34	countries	country	NNS	O	31	dobj
35	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	idea	idea	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	7	case
4	local	local	JJ	O	7	amod
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	organic	organic	JJ	O	4	conj
7	foods	food	NNS	O	2	nmod
8	has	have	VBZ	O	10	aux
9	rapidly	rapidly	RB	O	10	advmod
10	overtaken	overtake	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	mindset	mindset	NN	O	10	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	many	many	JJ	O	15	amod
15	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	12	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
17	there	there	EX	O	18	expl
18	is	be	VBZ	O	10	conj
19	no	no	DT	O	20	neg
20	longer	longer	JJR	O	18	advmod
21	a	a	DT	O	22	det
22	sense	sense	NN	O	18	nsubj
23	of	of	IN	O	24	case
24	urgency	urgency	NN	O	22	nmod
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	deliver	deliver	VB	O	18	advcl
27	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	28	amod
28	aid	aid	NN	O	26	dobj
29	to	to	TO	O	30	case
30	those	those	DT	O	26	nmod
31	who	who	WP	O	32	nsubj
32	need	need	VBP	O	30	acl:relcl
33	it	it	PRP	O	32	dobj
34	most	most	RBS	O	32	advmod
35	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	4	mark
2	many	many	JJ	O	3	amod
3	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	4	nsubj
4	have	have	VBP	O	17	advcl
5	good	good	JJ	O	6	amod
6	intentions	intention	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	on	on	IN	O	8	case
8	eating	eating	NN	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
10	living	live	VBG	O	4	conj
11	healthier	healthier	JJR	O	10	dobj
12	,	,	,	O	17	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	16	det
14	real	real	JJ	O	16	amod
15	food	food	NN	O	16	compound
16	crisis	crisis	NN	O	17	nsubj
17	surrounds	surround	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	those	those	DT	O	17	dobj
19	living	live	VBG	O	18	acl
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	19	nmod
22	who	who	WP	O	24	nsubj
23	are	be	VBP	O	24	aux
24	struggling	struggle	VBG	O	21	acl:relcl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	make	make	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	their	they	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
28	own	own	JJ	O	29	amod
29	food	food	NN	O	26	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Through	through	IN	O	9	case
2	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
3	logical	logical	JJ	O	9	amod
4	,	,	,	O	9	punct
5	ethical	ethical	JJ	O	9	amod
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
8	pathetic	pathetic	JJ	O	5	conj
9	appeals	appeal	NNS	O	12	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	12	punct
11	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
12	delivers	deliver	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
13	a	a	DT	O	17	det
14	compelling	compelling	JJ	O	17	amod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	successful	successful	JJ	O	14	conj
17	argument	argument	NN	O	12	dobj
18	in	in	IN	O	32	mark
19	that	that	IN	O	32	mark
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	elitist	elitist	JJ	O	22	amod
22	attitude	attitude	NN	O	32	nsubj
23	on	on	IN	O	28	case
24	organic	organic	JJ	O	28	amod
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	local	local	JJ	O	24	conj
27	grown	grown	JJ	O	28	amod
28	foods	food	NNS	O	22	nmod
29	is	be	VBZ	O	32	cop
30	not	not	RB	O	32	neg
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	answer	answer	NN	O	17	acl
33	when	when	WRB	O	35	advmod
34	there	there	EX	O	35	expl
35	are	be	VBP	O	32	advcl
36	millions	million	NNS	O	35	nsubj
37	of	of	IN	O	39	case
38	malnourished	malnourished	JJ	O	39	amod
39	people	people	NNS	O	36	nmod
40	throughout	throughout	IN	O	42	case
41	the	the	DT	O	42	det
42	world	world	NN	O	39	nmod
43	who	who	WP	O	44	nsubj
44	need	need	VBP	O	42	acl:relcl
45	support	support	NN	O	44	dobj
46	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	prior	prior	JJ	O	3	amod
3	years	year	NNS	DURATION	12	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	12	punct
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	7	compound
7	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	12	nsubj
8	had	have	VBD	O	12	aux
9	been	be	VBN	O	12	cop
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	full	full	JJ	O	12	amod
12	support	support	NN	O	0	ROOT
13	of	of	IN	O	14	mark
14	sending	send	VBG	O	12	acl
15	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	16	amod
16	aid	aid	NN	O	14	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
19	;	;	:	O	12	punct
20	but	but	CC	O	25	cc
21	recently	recently	RB	DATE	25	advmod
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	focus	focus	NN	O	25	nsubj
24	has	have	VBZ	O	25	aux
25	turned	turn	VBN	O	12	parataxis
26	to	to	TO	O	32	case
27	growing	grow	VBG	O	32	amod
28	healthier	healthier	RBR	O	32	amod
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	more	more	RBR	O	31	advmod
31	organic	organic	JJ	O	28	conj
32	foods	food	NNS	O	25	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	argues	argue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	through	through	IN	O	5	case
4	deductive	deductive	JJ	O	5	amod
5	reasoning	reasoning	NN	O	2	nmod
6	by	by	IN	O	7	mark
7	explaining	explain	VBG	O	2	advcl
8	the	the	DT	O	11	det
9	current	current	JJ	DATE	11	amod
10	food	food	NN	O	11	compound
11	crisis	crisis	NN	O	7	dobj
12	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
13	then	then	RB	O	14	advmod
14	hones	hone	VBZ	O	2	conj
15	in	in	IN	O	19	case
16	on	on	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	specific	specific	JJ	O	19	amod
19	struggles	struggle	NNS	O	14	nmod
20	developing	develop	VBG	O	21	amod
21	nations	nation	NNS	O	23	nsubj
22	are	be	VBP	O	23	aux
23	facing	face	VBG	O	19	acl:relcl
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	demonstrates	demonstrate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
4	there	there	EX	O	7	expl
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	little	little	JJ	O	7	amod
7	margin	margin	NN	O	2	ccomp
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	survival	survival	NN	O	7	nmod
10	for	for	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	people	people	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
16	demands	demand	VBZ	O	7	conj
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	19	compound
19	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	16	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	take	take	VB	O	16	xcomp
22	action	action	NN	O	21	dobj
23	considering	consider	VBG	O	22	acl
24	its	its	PRP$	O	23	dobj
25	been	be	VBN	O	26	auxpass
26	done	do	VBN	O	24	acl
27	before	before	IN	O	26	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	explains	explain	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	`	`	``	O	2	punct
5	Foreign	foreign	JJ	O	6	amod
6	assistance	assistance	NN	O	13	nsubj
7	to	to	TO	O	8	case
8	farming	farming	NN	O	6	nmod
9	has	have	VBZ	O	13	aux
10	been	be	VBN	O	13	cop
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	high-payoff	high-payoff	JJ	O	13	amod
13	investment	investment	NN	O	2	ccomp
14	everywhere	everywhere	RB	O	13	advmod
15	,	,	,	O	13	punct
16	including	include	VBG	O	17	case
17	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	World	World	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	Bank	Bank	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
4	has	have	VBZ	O	5	aux
5	documented	document	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	average	average	JJ	O	7	amod
7	rates	rate	NNS	O	5	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	return	return	NN	O	7	nmod
10	on	on	IN	O	11	case
11	investments	investment	NNS	O	5	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	agricultural	agricultural	JJ	O	14	amod
14	research	research	NN	O	11	nmod
15	in	in	IN	O	16	case
16	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	19	case
18	35	35	CD	PERCENT	19	nummod
19	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	16	nmod
20	a	a	DT	DURATION	21	det
21	year	year	NN	DURATION	19	dep
22	,	,	,	O	19	punct
23	accompanied	accompany	VBN	O	19	acl
24	by	by	IN	O	26	case
25	significant	significant	JJ	O	26	amod
26	reductions	reduction	NNS	O	23	nmod
27	in	in	IN	O	28	case
28	poverty	poverty	NN	O	26	nmod
29	'	'	''	O	26	punct
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	26	appos
32	,	,	,	O	31	punct
33	152	152	CD	NUMBER	31	dep
34	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
35	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Parrlberg	Parrlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	pleads	plead	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	there	there	EX	O	4	expl
4	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	no	no	DT	O	7	neg
6	logical	logical	JJ	O	7	amod
7	reason	reason	NN	O	4	nsubj
8	why	why	WRB	O	14	advmod
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	14	nsubj
12	can	can	MD	O	14	aux
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	provide	provide	VB	O	7	acl:relcl
15	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	16	amod
16	aid	aid	NN	O	14	dobj
17	when	when	WRB	O	21	advmod
18	there	there	EX	O	21	expl
19	has	have	VBZ	O	21	aux
20	been	be	VBN	O	21	auxpass
21	proven	prove	VBN	O	14	advcl
22	success	success	NN	O	21	dobj
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	DATE	25	det
25	past	past	NN	DATE	22	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	help	help	NN	O	13	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	6	amod
6	aid	aid	NN	O	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	13	punct
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	poverty	poverty	NN	O	10	compound
10	line	line	NN	O	13	nsubjpass
11	has	have	VBZ	O	13	aux
12	been	be	VBN	O	13	auxpass
13	reduced	reduce	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	13	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
17	there	there	EX	O	21	expl
18	has	have	VBZ	O	21	aux
19	been	be	VBN	O	21	cop
20	an	a	DT	O	21	det
21	improvement	improvement	NN	O	13	conj
22	in	in	IN	O	26	case
23	their	they	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
24	insufficient	insufficient	JJ	O	26	amod
25	living	living	NN	O	26	compound
26	conditions	condition	NNS	O	21	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	people	people	NNS	O	10	nsubj
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	government	government	NN	O	2	conj
5	in	in	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
8	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	2	nmod
9	have	have	VBP	O	10	aux
10	developed	develop	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	an	a	DT	O	13	det
12	elitist	elitist	JJ	O	13	amod
13	attitude	attitude	NN	O	10	dobj
14	about	about	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	necessity	necessity	NN	O	10	nmod
17	for	for	IN	O	18	case
18	local	local	JJ	O	16	nmod
19	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
20	organically	organically	RB	O	21	advmod
21	grown	grow	VBN	O	10	conj
22	food	food	NN	O	21	dobj
23	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	As	as	IN	MISC	2	case
2	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	8	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	8	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	primary	primary	JJ	O	6	amod
6	focus	focus	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	has	have	VBZ	O	8	aux
8	been	be	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	how	how	WRB	O	11	advmod
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	specialize	specialize	VB	O	8	ccomp
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	enhance	enhance	VB	O	11	conj
14	our	we	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	food	food	NN	O	11	dobj
16	when	when	WRB	O	21	advmod
17	African	African	NNP	MISC	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	struggle	struggle	NN	O	21	nsubj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	produce	produce	VB	O	11	xcomp
22	barely	barely	RB	O	23	advmod
23	enough	enough	RB	O	21	xcomp
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	survive	survive	VB	O	23	xcomp
26	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	states	state	NNS	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	`	`	``	O	26	punct
5	The	the	DT	O	6	det
6	number	number	NN	O	26	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	12	case
8	`	`	``	O	12	punct
9	food	food	NN	O	12	compound
10	insecure	insecure	NN	O	12	compound
11	'	'	''	O	12	punct
12	people	people	NNS	O	6	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
15	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	17	punct
16	those	those	DT	O	17	nsubj
17	consuming	consume	VBG	O	26	parataxis
18	less	less	JJR	O	20	advmod
19	than	than	IN	O	18	mwe
20	2,100	2,100	CD	NUMBER	21	nummod
21	calories	calorie	NNS	O	17	dobj
22	a	a	DT	DURATION	23	det
23	day	day	NN	DURATION	21	dep
24	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	17	punct
25	will	will	MD	O	26	aux
26	increase	increase	VB	O	2	dep
27	30	30	CD	PERCENT	28	nummod
28	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	26	dobj
29	over	over	IN	O	32	case
30	the	the	DT	DATE	32	det
31	next	next	JJ	DATE	32	amod
32	decade	decade	NN	DATE	28	nmod
33	without	without	IN	O	35	case
34	significant	significant	JJ	O	35	amod
35	reforms	reform	NNS	O	32	nmod
36	'	'	POS	O	35	case
37	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	38	punct
38	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	32	appos
39	,	,	,	O	38	punct
40	1	1	CD	NUMBER	38	dep
41	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	38	punct
42	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	promise	promise	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	life	life	NN	O	2	nmod
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	dwindling	dwindle	VBG	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
11	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
12	argues	argue	VBZ	O	6	conj
13	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	time	time	NN	O	18	nsubj
16	for	for	IN	O	17	case
17	action	action	NN	O	15	nmod
18	is	be	VBZ	O	12	ccomp
19	now	now	RB	DATE	18	advmod
20	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	no	no	DT	O	5	neg
4	logical	logical	JJ	O	5	amod
5	reason	reason	NN	O	2	nsubj
6	why	why	WRB	O	24	advmod
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	people	people	NNS	O	24	nsubj
9	in	in	IN	O	10	case
10	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
11	must	must	MD	O	12	aux
12	remain	remain	VB	O	10	acl:relcl
13	so	so	RB	O	14	advmod
14	engrossed	engross	VBN	O	12	dep
15	on	on	IN	O	16	case
16	whether	whether	IN	O	14	nmod
17	or	or	CC	O	14	cc
18	not	not	RB	O	14	conj
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	food	food	NN	O	14	dep
21	their	they	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	eating	eating	NN	O	20	dep
23	is	be	VBZ	O	24	cop
24	organic	organic	JJ	O	5	acl:relcl
25	or	or	CC	O	24	cc
26	not	not	RB	O	24	conj
27	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	people	people	NNS	O	8	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	2	nmod
5	do	do	VBP	O	8	aux
6	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
7	even	even	RB	O	8	advmod
8	have	have	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	option	option	NN	O	8	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	decide	decide	VB	O	10	acl
13	if	if	IN	O	16	mark
14	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
16	organic	organic	JJ	O	12	advcl
17	enough	enough	RB	O	16	advmod
18	for	for	IN	O	21	mark
19	them	they	PRP	O	21	nsubj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	eat	eat	VB	O	16	ccomp
22	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Through	through	IN	O	5	case
2	Parrlberg	Parrlberg	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	logical	logical	JJ	O	5	amod
5	appeal	appeal	NN	O	9	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	9	punct
7	he	he	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	effectively	effectively	RB	O	9	advmod
9	implores	implore	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	need	need	NN	O	9	dobj
12	for	for	IN	O	13	case
13	Americans	american	NNS	MISC	11	nmod
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	switch	switch	VB	O	9	xcomp
16	focus	focus	NN	O	15	dobj
17	on	on	IN	O	20	case
18	their	they	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
19	prized	prize	VBN	O	20	amod
20	idea	idea	NN	O	15	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	food	food	NN	O	20	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
24	spend	spend	VB	O	15	conj
25	their	they	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
26	money	money	NN	O	24	dobj
27	on	on	IN	O	28	case
28	those	those	DT	O	24	nmod
29	who	who	WP	O	30	nsubj
30	have	have	VBP	O	28	acl:relcl
31	little	little	JJ	O	30	advmod
32	to	to	TO	O	33	mark
33	survive	survive	VB	O	30	xcomp
34	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	case
2	an	a	DT	O	3	det
3	associate	associate	NN	O	16	nmod
4	at	at	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Weatherhead	Weatherhead	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	Center	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nmod
8	for	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	10	case
9	International	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	Affairs	Affairs	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
11	at	at	IN	O	13	case
12	Harvard	Harvard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	University	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	16	punct
15	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	16	nsubj
16	devotes	devote	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	majority	majority	NN	O	16	dobj
19	of	of	IN	O	21	case
20	his	he	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	time	time	NN	O	18	nmod
22	in	in	IN	O	23	mark
23	researching	research	VBG	O	16	advcl
24	international	international	JJ	O	25	amod
25	agriculture	agriculture	NN	O	23	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	explains	explain	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	people	people	NNS	O	12	nsubj
5	in	in	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
8	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	4	nmod
9	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
10	under	under	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	belief	belief	NN	O	2	ccomp
13	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
14	their	they	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	health	health	NN	O	17	nsubj
16	will	will	MD	O	17	aux
17	improve	improve	VB	O	12	ccomp
18	if	if	IN	O	21	mark
19	their	they	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	food	food	NN	O	21	nsubj
21	has	have	VBZ	O	17	advcl
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	label	label	NN	O	21	dobj
24	`	`	``	O	23	punct
25	organic	organic	JJ	O	23	dep
26	'	'	''	O	23	punct
27	on	on	IN	O	28	case
28	it	it	PRP	O	21	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	understand	understand	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	why	why	WRB	O	9	advmod
6	organic	organic	JJ	O	7	amod
7	food	food	NN	O	9	nsubj
8	has	have	VBZ	O	9	aux
9	become	become	VBN	O	4	ccomp
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	greater	greater	JJR	O	12	amod
12	priority	priority	NN	O	9	xcomp
13	than	than	IN	O	14	mark
14	sending	send	VBG	O	9	advcl
15	international	international	JJ	O	16	amod
16	aid	aid	NN	O	14	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	countries	country	NNS	O	14	nmod
19	who	who	WP	O	23	nsubj
20	are	be	VBP	O	23	cop
21	not	not	RB	O	23	neg
22	even	even	RB	O	23	advmod
23	aware	aware	JJ	O	18	acl:relcl
24	of	of	IN	O	29	mark
25	what	what	WP	O	29	dobj
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	term	term	NN	O	29	nsubj
28	organic	organic	JJ	O	29	amod
29	means	means	NNS	O	23	advcl
30	when	when	WRB	O	32	advmod
31	it	it	PRP	O	32	nsubj
32	comes	come	VBZ	O	29	acl:relcl
33	too	too	RB	O	34	advmod
34	food	food	NN	O	32	dobj
35	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	explains	explain	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	`	`	``	ORGANIZATION	6	punct
6	Food	Food	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nsubj
7	and	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	6	cc
8	Drug	Drug	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
9	Administration	Administration	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	surveys	survey	NNS	O	6	conj
11	have	have	VBP	O	12	aux
12	revealed	reveal	VBN	O	2	ccomp
13	that	that	IN	O	29	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	17	det
15	highest	highest	JJS	O	17	amod
16	dietary	dietary	JJ	O	17	amod
17	exposures	exposure	NNS	O	29	nsubj
18	to	to	TO	O	20	case
19	pesticide	pesticide	NN	O	20	compound
20	residues	residue	NNS	O	17	nmod
21	on	on	IN	O	22	case
22	foods	food	NNS	O	20	nmod
23	in	in	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	26	compound
26	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	22	nmod
27	are	be	VBP	O	29	cop
28	so	so	RB	O	29	advmod
29	trivial	trivial	JJ	O	12	ccomp
30	'	'	''	O	29	punct
31	the	the	DT	O	33	det
32	safety	safety	NN	O	33	compound
33	gains	gain	NNS	O	38	nsubj
34	from	from	IN	O	35	mark
35	buying	buy	VBG	O	33	acl
36	organic	organic	JJ	O	35	dobj
37	are	be	VBP	O	38	cop
38	insignificant	insignificant	JJ	O	29	ccomp
39	.	.	.	O	2	punct
40	'	'	''	O	2	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Paarlberg	paarlberg	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	150	150	CD	NUMBER	2	nmod:tmod
5	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	aware	aware	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	safety	safety	NN	O	7	compound
7	concerns	concern	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
9	it	it	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	comes	come	VBZ	O	3	advcl
11	to	to	TO	O	12	case
12	food	food	NN	O	10	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
14	reassures	reassure	VBZ	O	10	conj
15	his	he	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	audience	audience	NN	O	14	dobj
17	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
18	in	in	IN	O	19	case
19	reality	reality	NN	O	23	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	23	punct
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	food	food	NN	O	23	nsubj
23	produced	produce	VBD	O	14	ccomp
24	today	today	NN	DATE	26	dep
25	is	be	VBZ	O	26	cop
26	safe	safe	JJ	O	23	ccomp
27	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
28	healthy	healthy	JJ	O	26	conj
29	to	to	TO	O	30	mark
30	eat	eat	VB	O	26	xcomp
31	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	argues	argue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	there	there	EX	O	5	expl
5	is	be	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
6	no	no	DT	O	8	neg
7	dire	dire	JJ	O	8	amod
8	need	need	NN	O	5	nsubj
9	for	for	IN	O	11	case
10	all	all	DT	O	11	det
11	food	food	NN	O	8	nmod
12	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
13	organic	organic	JJ	O	11	dep
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	crisis	crisis	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	real	real	JJ	O	3	amod
3	crisis	crisis	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	food	food	NN	O	3	nmod
6	comes	come	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	into	into	IN	O	8	case
8	play	play	NN	O	6	nmod
9	when	when	WRB	O	18	advmod
10	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	18	nsubj
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	many	many	JJ	O	15	amod
13	other	other	JJ	O	15	amod
14	developing	develop	VBG	O	15	amod
15	countries	country	NNS	O	10	conj
16	can	can	MD	O	18	aux
17	barely	barely	RB	O	18	advmod
18	survive	survive	VB	O	6	advcl
19	on	on	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	food	food	NN	O	18	nmod
22	that	that	WDT	O	25	nsubjpass
23	is	be	VBZ	O	25	aux
24	being	be	VBG	O	25	auxpass
25	produced	produce	VBN	O	21	acl:relcl
26	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	continues	continue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	by	by	IN	O	4	mark
4	explaining	explain	VBG	O	2	advcl
5	`	`	``	O	4	punct
6	surveys	survey	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	over	over	IN	O	11	case
8	the	the	DT	DATE	11	det
9	past	past	JJ	DATE	11	amod
10	several	several	JJ	DATE	11	amod
11	decades	decade	NNS	DATE	6	nmod
12	by	by	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	Centers	Centers	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	11	nmod
15	for	for	IN	ORGANIZATION	21	mark
16	Disease	Disease	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Control	Control	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	nsubj
18	and	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	17	cc
19	Prevention	Prevention	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	conj
20	have	have	VBP	O	21	aux
21	found	find	VBN	O	4	advcl
22	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
23	the	the	DT	O	26	det
24	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	26	compound
25	food	food	NN	O	26	compound
26	supply	supply	NN	O	27	nsubj
27	became	become	VBD	O	21	ccomp
28	steadily	steadily	RB	O	29	advmod
29	safer	safer	JJR	O	27	xcomp
30	over	over	IN	O	31	case
31	time	time	NN	O	27	nmod
32	'	'	''	O	27	punct
33	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
34	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	27	dep
35	,	,	,	O	34	punct
36	149	149	CD	NUMBER	34	dep
37	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
38	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	emphasizes	emphasize	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	9	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	7	det
5	industrial	industrial	JJ	O	7	amod
6	food	food	NN	O	7	compound
7	industry	industry	NN	O	9	nsubj
8	has	have	VBZ	O	9	aux
9	established	establish	VBN	O	2	ccomp
10	many	many	JJ	O	12	amod
11	safety	safety	NN	O	12	compound
12	measures	measure	NNS	O	9	dobj
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	idea	idea	NN	O	12	conj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	organic	organic	JJ	O	18	amod
18	food	food	NN	O	15	nmod
19	being	be	VBG	O	20	cop
20	safer	safer	JJR	O	9	xcomp
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	healthier	healthier	JJR	O	20	conj
23	is	be	VBZ	O	25	cop
24	so	so	RB	O	25	advmod
25	trivial	trivial	JJ	O	20	acl:relcl
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	countries	country	NNS	O	2	nsubj
4	that	that	WDT	O	8	nsubj
5	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	desperate	desperate	JJ	O	8	amod
8	need	need	NN	O	3	acl:relcl
9	of	of	IN	O	13	case
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
12	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	13	compound
13	help	help	NN	O	8	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	2	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	only	only	JJ	O	18	amod
18	way	way	NN	O	30	nsubj
19	for	for	IN	O	21	case
20	their	they	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	conditions	condition	NNS	O	18	nmod
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	food	food	NN	O	24	compound
24	supply	supply	NN	O	21	conj
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	improve	improve	VB	O	18	acl
27	is	be	VBZ	O	30	cop
28	through	through	IN	O	30	case
29	international	international	JJ	O	30	amod
30	aid	aid	NN	O	2	conj
31	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	4	case
2	an	a	DT	O	4	det
3	involved	involve	VBN	O	4	amod
4	researcher	researcher	NN	O	27	nmod
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	agriculture	agriculture	NN	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	27	punct
8	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	pleads	plead	NNS	O	27	nsubj
10	for	for	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	obsessive	obsessive	JJ	O	13	amod
13	focus	focus	NN	O	9	nmod
14	on	on	IN	O	16	case
15	organic	organic	JJ	O	16	amod
16	food	food	NN	O	13	nmod
17	in	in	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	20	compound
20	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	16	nmod
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	vanish	vanish	VB	O	13	acl
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	support	support	VB	O	22	conj
25	nations	nation	NNS	O	22	dobj
26	who	who	WP	O	25	acl:relcl
27	need	need	VBP	O	0	ROOT
28	it	it	PRP	O	27	dobj
29	most	most	RBS	O	27	advmod
30	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	Pararlberg	pararlberg	NN	O	2	nsubj
2	illustrates	illustrate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	selfish	selfish	JJ	O	5	amod
5	ways	way	NNS	O	2	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	American	american	JJ	MISC	8	amod
8	agriculture	agriculture	NN	O	5	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	need	need	NN	O	5	conj
12	for	for	IN	O	13	case
13	food	food	NN	O	11	nmod
14	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
15	be	be	VB	O	16	cop
16	organic	organic	JJ	O	2	advcl
17	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
18	locally	locally	RB	O	19	advmod
19	grown	grow	VBN	O	2	conj
20	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
21	be	be	VB	O	22	cop
22	unacceptable	unacceptable	JJ	O	19	xcomp
23	considering	consider	VBG	O	22	xcomp
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	developing	develop	VBG	O	26	amod
26	countries	country	NNS	O	29	nsubj
27	can	can	MD	O	29	aux
28	barely	barely	RB	O	29	advmod
29	produce	produce	VB	O	23	ccomp
30	food	food	NN	O	29	dobj
31	to	to	TO	O	32	mark
32	survive	survive	VB	O	29	advcl
33	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	evokes	evoke	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	sense	sense	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	sympathy	sympathy	NN	O	4	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	sadness	sadness	NN	O	6	conj
9	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
12	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	13	nsubj
13	has	have	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
14	akm	akm	NN	O	13	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	13	punct
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct
17	'	'	''	O	2	punct

1	bandoned	bandon	VBN	O	0	ROOT
2	sending	send	VBG	O	1	xcomp
3	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	4	amod
4	aid	aid	NN	O	2	dobj
5	,	,	,	O	2	punct
6	only	only	RB	O	8	advmod
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	focus	focus	VB	O	2	advcl
9	their	they	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	priorities	priority	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	on	on	IN	O	16	mark
12	if	if	IN	O	16	mark
13	their	they	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	food	food	NN	O	16	nsubjpass
15	was	be	VBD	O	16	auxpass
16	grown	grow	VBN	O	8	nmod
17	locally	locally	RB	O	16	advmod
18	or	or	CC	O	16	cc
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	a	a	DT	O	21	det
21	factory	factory	NN	O	16	conj
22	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	desire	desire	NN	O	17	nsubj
3	for	for	IN	O	5	case
4	our	we	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	food	food	NN	O	2	nmod
6	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
7	be	be	VB	O	9	cop
8	`	`	``	O	9	punct
9	organic	organic	JJ	O	5	acl
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	local	local	JJ	O	9	dep
12	,	,	,	O	9	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
14	slow	slow	VB	O	9	conj
15	'	'	''	O	14	punct
16	has	have	VBZ	O	17	aux
17	overtaken	overtake	VBN	O	0	ROOT
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	American	american	JJ	MISC	20	amod
20	population	population	NN	O	17	dobj
21	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
22	has	have	VBZ	O	23	aux
23	developed	develop	VBN	O	17	conj
24	an	a	DT	O	26	det
25	elitist	elitist	JJ	O	26	amod
26	attitude	attitude	NN	O	23	dobj
27	about	about	IN	O	31	mark
28	where	where	WRB	O	31	advmod
29	food	food	NN	O	31	nsubj
30	is	be	VBZ	O	31	aux
31	coming	come	VBG	O	23	advcl
32	from	from	IN	O	31	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Paarlberg	paarlberg	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
4	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	evokes	evoke	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	sense	sense	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	pity	pity	NN	O	4	nmod
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	this	this	DT	O	6	nmod
9	because	because	IN	O	14	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	people	people	NNS	O	14	nsubj
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	11	nmod
14	grow	grow	VB	O	2	advcl
15	their	they	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	food	food	NN	O	14	dobj
17	organic	organic	JJ	O	16	amod
18	,	,	,	O	16	punct
19	local	local	JJ	O	16	amod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
22	slow	slow	JJ	O	19	conj
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	gotten	get	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	them	they	PRP	O	3	xcomp
5	nowhere	nowhere	RB	O	4	advmod
6	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	3	nsubj
2	are	be	VBP	O	3	aux
3	earning	earn	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	only	only	RB	O	5	advmod
5	$	$	$	MONEY	3	dobj
6	1	1	CD	MONEY	5	nummod
7	a	a	DT	DURATION	8	det
8	day	day	NN	DURATION	5	dep
9	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
10	continue	continue	VB	O	3	conj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	starve	starve	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	argues	argue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
4	if	if	IN	O	8	mark
5	this	this	DT	O	8	nsubj
6	has	have	VBZ	O	8	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	gotten	get	VBN	O	2	advcl
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	African	african	JJ	MISC	11	amod
11	people	people	NNS	O	8	dobj
12	anywhere	anywhere	RB	O	13	advmod
13	then	then	RB	O	8	advmod
14	why	why	WRB	O	19	advmod
15	is	be	VBZ	O	19	cop
16	this	this	DT	O	19	det:predet
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	primary	primary	JJ	O	19	amod
19	focus	focus	NN	O	13	acl:relcl
20	in	in	IN	O	23	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	23	compound
23	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	19	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	explains	explain	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
6	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
7	as	as	IN	O	11	mark
8	if	if	IN	O	7	mwe
9	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	11	nsubj
10	has	have	VBZ	O	11	aux
11	tried	try	VBN	O	5	advcl
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	increase	increase	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	their	they	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	quality	quality	NN	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	living	living	NN	O	15	nmod
18	but	but	CC	O	11	cc
19	rather	rather	RB	O	21	advmod
20	are	be	VBP	O	21	aux
21	lacking	lack	VBG	O	11	conj
22	international	international	JJ	O	23	amod
23	support	support	NN	O	21	dobj
24	from	from	IN	O	27	case
25	many	many	JJ	O	27	amod
26	wealthy	wealthy	JJ	O	27	amod
27	nations	nation	NNS	O	21	nmod
28	including	include	VBG	O	31	case
29	the	the	DT	O	31	det
30	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	31	compound
31	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	27	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	explains	explain	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	`	`	``	O	2	punct
5	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	7	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	aux
7	failing	fail	VBG	O	2	ccomp
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	keep	keep	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	up	up	RP	O	9	compound:prt
11	with	with	IN	O	13	case
12	population	population	NN	O	13	compound
13	growth	growth	NN	O	9	nmod
14	not	not	RB	O	18	dep
15	because	because	IN	O	18	mark
16	it	it	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	has	have	VBZ	O	18	aux
18	exhausted	exhaust	VBN	O	9	advcl
19	its	its	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	potential	potential	NN	O	18	dobj
21	,	,	,	O	18	punct
22	but	but	CC	O	23	cc
23	instead	instead	RB	O	18	cc
24	because	because	IN	O	29	mark
25	too	too	RB	O	26	advmod
26	little	little	JJ	O	29	nsubjpass
27	has	have	VBZ	O	29	aux
28	been	be	VBN	O	29	auxpass
29	invested	invest	VBN	O	18	conj
30	in	in	IN	O	31	mark
31	reaching	reach	VBG	O	29	advcl
32	that	that	IN	O	33	case
33	potential	potential	JJ	O	31	nmod
34	'	'	''	O	2	punct
35	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	36	punct
36	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	dep
37	,	,	,	O	36	punct
38	151	151	CD	NUMBER	36	dep
39	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	36	punct
40	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Developing	develop	VBG	O	2	amod
2	nations	nation	NNS	O	8	nsubj
3	alike	alike	RB	O	8	advmod
4	to	to	TO	O	5	case
5	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod
6	do	do	VBP	O	8	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	have	have	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	opportunities	opportunity	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
12	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
13	prosperous	prosperous	JJ	O	8	ccomp
14	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
15	are	be	VBP	O	16	aux
16	struggling	struggle	VBG	O	8	conj
17	simply	simply	RB	O	16	advmod
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	survive	survive	VB	O	16	xcomp
20	each	each	DT	SET	21	det
21	day	day	NN	SET	19	nmod:tmod
22	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	implores	implore	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	how	how	WRB	O	8	advmod
4	we	we	PRP	O	8	nsubj
5	can	can	MD	O	8	aux
6	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
7	solely	solely	RB	O	8	advmod
8	sit	sit	VB	O	2	ccomp
9	back	back	RB	O	8	advmod
10	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
11	focus	focus	VB	O	8	conj
12	on	on	IN	O	14	case
13	our	we	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	elite	elite	NN	O	11	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	selfish	selfish	JJ	O	17	amod
17	ways	way	NNS	O	14	conj
18	when	when	WRB	O	22	advmod
19	money	money	NN	O	22	nsubjpass
20	could	could	MD	O	22	aux
21	be	be	VB	O	22	auxpass
22	spent	spend	VBN	O	11	advcl
23	elsewhere	elsewhere	RB	O	22	advmod
24	on	on	IN	O	25	mark
25	helping	help	VBG	O	22	advcl
26	others	other	NNS	O	27	nsubj
27	survive	survive	VBP	O	25	ccomp
28	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	illustrates	illustrate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	desperate	desperate	JJ	O	5	amod
5	need	need	NN	O	2	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	help	help	VB	O	5	acl
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	African	african	JJ	MISC	10	amod
10	people	people	NNS	O	7	dobj
11	because	because	IN	O	15	mark
12	one	one	CD	NUMBER	15	nsubj
13	will	will	MD	O	15	aux
14	never	never	RB	O	15	neg
15	know	know	VB	O	7	advcl
16	what	what	WP	O	18	dobj
17	it	it	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	15	ccomp
19	like	like	IN	O	21	mark
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	starve	starve	VB	O	18	advcl
22	on	on	IN	O	25	case
23	a	a	DT	O	25	det
24	daily	daily	JJ	SET	25	amod
25	basis	basis	NN	O	21	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	demonstrates	demonstrate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	through	through	IN	O	6	case
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	pathetic	pathetic	JJ	O	6	amod
6	appeal	appeal	NN	O	2	nmod
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	devastating	devastating	JJ	O	9	amod
9	effects	effect	NNS	O	2	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	lack	lack	NN	O	9	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	food	food	NN	O	12	nmod
15	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubj
16	is	be	VBZ	O	17	aux
17	happening	happen	VBG	O	9	acl:relcl
18	in	in	IN	O	19	case
19	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	17	nmod
20	when	when	WRB	O	29	advmod
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	people	people	NNS	O	29	nsubj
23	in	in	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	26	compound
26	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	22	nmod
27	are	be	VBP	O	29	cop
28	too	too	RB	O	29	advmod
29	busy	busy	JJ	O	17	advcl
30	questioning	question	VBG	O	29	dep
31	whether	whether	IN	O	35	mark
32	their	they	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	food	food	NN	O	35	nsubj
34	is	be	VBZ	O	35	cop
35	organic	organic	JJ	O	29	ccomp
36	enough	enough	RB	O	35	advmod
37	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Throughout	throughout	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	article	article	NN	O	12	nmod
4	`	`	``	O	3	punct
5	Attention	attention	NN	O	6	compound
6	Wholefood	wholefood	NN	O	3	dep
7	Shoppers	shopper	NNS	O	6	nmod:poss
8	'	'	POS	O	7	case
9	,	,	,	O	12	punct
10	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
11	effectively	effectively	RB	O	12	advmod
12	argues	argue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	insignificance	insignificance	NN	O	12	dobj
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	organic	organic	JJ	O	17	amod
17	food	food	NN	O	14	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	necessity	necessity	NN	O	17	conj
21	as	as	IN	O	23	case
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	nation	nation	NN	O	12	nmod
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	shift	shift	VB	O	23	acl
26	our	we	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
27	focus	focus	NN	O	25	dobj
28	back	back	RB	O	25	advmod
29	to	to	TO	O	30	mark
30	supporting	support	VBG	O	28	advcl
31	developing	develop	VBG	O	32	amod
32	countries	country	NNS	O	30	dobj
33	with	with	IN	O	35	case
34	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	35	amod
35	aid	aid	NN	O	30	nmod
36	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	3	compound
3	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	4	nsubj
4	intends	intend	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	well	well	RB	O	4	advmod
6	on	on	IN	O	7	mark
7	taking	take	VBG	O	4	advcl
8	charge	charge	NN	O	7	dobj
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	healthy	healthy	JJ	O	11	amod
11	eating	eating	NN	O	8	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
13	growing	grow	VBG	O	7	conj
14	local	local	JJ	O	17	amod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	organic	organic	JJ	O	14	conj
17	foods	food	NNS	O	13	dobj
18	;	;	:	O	4	punct
19	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
20	has	have	VBZ	O	21	aux
21	neglected	neglect	VBN	O	4	conj
22	its	its	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	duty	duty	NN	O	21	dobj
24	as	as	IN	O	26	case
25	a	a	DT	O	26	det
26	nation	nation	NN	O	21	nmod
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	support	support	VB	O	26	acl
29	those	those	DT	O	28	dobj
30	in	in	IN	O	31	case
31	Africa	Africa	NNP	LOCATION	29	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	other	other	JJ	O	3	amod
3	parts	part	NNS	O	13	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	world	world	NN	O	3	nmod
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	idea	idea	NN	O	13	nsubj
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	organic	organic	JJ	O	11	amod
11	food	food	NN	O	8	nmod
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
13	nonexistent	nonexistent	JJ	O	0	ROOT
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	margin	margin	NN	O	20	nsubj
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	survival	survival	NN	O	16	nmod
19	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
20	small	small	JJ	O	13	conj
21	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Paarlberg	Paarlberg	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	implores	implore	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
4	it	it	PRP	O	6	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
6	time	time	NN	O	2	ccomp
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	revert	revert	VB	O	6	acl
9	back	back	RB	O	8	advmod
10	to	to	TO	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	time	time	NN	O	8	nmod
13	where	where	WRB	O	19	advmod
14	sending	send	VBG	O	19	csubj
15	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	16	amod
16	aid	aid	NN	O	14	dobj
17	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
18	a	a	DT	O	19	det
19	priority	priority	NN	O	8	advcl
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	an	a	DT	O	23	det
22	elitist	elitist	JJ	O	23	amod
23	attitude	attitude	NN	O	26	nsubj
24	did	do	VBD	O	26	aux
25	not	not	RB	O	26	neg
26	revolve	revolve	VB	O	19	conj
27	around	around	IN	O	28	case
28	food	food	NN	O	26	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	2	punct

