1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	2001	2001	CD	DATE	25	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	25	punct
4	as	as	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	measure	measure	NN	O	25	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	security	security	NN	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	safety	safety	NN	O	8	conj
11	following	follow	VBG	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	9/11	9/11	CD	NUMBER	14	nummod
14	attacks	attack	NNS	O	6	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	25	punct
16	President	President	NNP	O	17	compound
17	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
18	with	with	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	approval	approval	NN	O	17	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	107th	107th	JJ	ORGANIZATION	24	amod
24	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	nmod
25	passed	pass	VBD	O	0	ROOT
26	the	the	DT	O	30	det
27	2001	2001	CD	DATE	30	nummod
28	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	30	compound
29	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	30	compound
30	ACT	ACT	NNP	O	25	dobj
31	.	.	.	O	25	punct

1	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	3	compound
2	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Act	Act	NNP	O	6	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
5	an	a	DT	O	6	det
6	acronym	acronym	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	11	case
8	Uniting	Uniting	NNP	O	11	compound
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	Strengthening	Strengthening	NNP	LOCATION	8	conj
11	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
12	by	by	IN	O	16	case
13	Providing	Providing	NNP	O	16	compound
14	Appropriate	Appropriate	NNP	O	16	compound
15	Tools	Tools	NNP	O	16	compound
16	Required	Required	NNP	O	11	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	Intercept	intercept	VB	O	6	acl
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	Obstruct	obstruct	VB	O	18	conj
21	Terrorism	Terrorism	NNP	O	18	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	6	punct
23	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
24	it	it	PRP	O	27	nsubjpass
25	is	be	VBZ	O	27	auxpass
26	better	better	RB	O	27	advmod
27	known	know	VBN	O	6	conj
28	as	as	IN	O	30	case
29	simply	simply	RB	O	30	advmod
30	the	the	DT	O	27	nmod
31	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	32	compound
32	Act	Act	NNP	O	30	dep
33	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	7	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	purpose	purpose	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	act	act	NN	O	3	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	28	csubj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	intercept	intercept	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	counter	counter	VB	O	9	conj
12	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	13	amod
13	threats	threat	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	both	both	CC	O	15	cc:preconj
15	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	13	amod
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	15	conj
18	,	,	,	O	13	punct
19	its	its	PRP$	O	13	appos
20	'	'	''	O	11	punct
21	legality	legality	NN	O	11	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	effectiveness	effectiveness	NN	O	21	conj
24	,	,	,	O	21	punct
25	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
26	use	use	NN	O	21	conj
27	has	have	VBZ	O	28	aux
28	become	become	VBN	O	0	ROOT
29	a	a	DT	O	32	det
30	heavy	heavy	JJ	O	32	amod
31	debate	debate	NN	O	32	compound
32	topic	topic	NN	O	28	xcomp
33	among	among	IN	O	34	case
34	members	member	NNS	O	28	nmod
35	of	of	IN	O	36	case
36	congress	congress	NN	O	34	nmod
37	and	and	CC	O	36	cc
38	the	the	DT	O	40	det
39	American	american	JJ	MISC	40	amod
40	people	people	NNS	O	36	conj
41	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	people	people	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	believe	believe	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	Patriot	patriot	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	Acts	act	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
8	provisions	provision	NNS	O	21	nsubj
9	allowing	allow	VBG	O	8	acl
10	unwarranted	unwarranted	JJ	O	11	amod
11	wire	wire	NN	O	9	dobj
12	tapping	tap	VBG	O	11	acl
13	on	on	IN	O	14	case
14	its	its	PRP$	O	12	nmod
15	'	'	''	O	12	punct
16	own	own	JJ	O	17	amod
17	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	12	dobj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	21	cop
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	direct	direct	JJ	O	21	amod
21	violation	violation	NN	O	7	ccomp
22	of	of	IN	O	27	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	American	american	JJ	MISC	25	amod
25	people	people	NNS	O	27	nmod:poss
26	's	's	POS	O	25	case
27	privacy	privacy	NN	O	21	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
29	freedoms	freedom	NNS	O	27	conj
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Other	other	JJ	O	2	nsubj
2	argue	argue	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	6	compound
6	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	10	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	10	amod
10	line	line	NN	O	2	ccomp
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	defense	defense	NN	O	10	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	14	mark
14	keeping	keep	VBG	O	12	acl
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	American	american	JJ	MISC	17	amod
17	people	people	NNS	O	14	dobj
18	safe	safe	JJ	O	17	amod
19	from	from	IN	O	20	case
20	attacks	attack	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	committed	commit	VBN	O	20	acl
22	by	by	IN	O	23	case
23	terrorists	terrorist	NNS	O	21	nmod
24	both	both	CC	O	23	dep
25	at	at	IN	O	26	case
26	home	home	NN	O	23	conj
27	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
28	abroad	abroad	RB	O	18	advmod
29	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Those	those	DT	O	18	nsubj
2	who	who	WP	O	3	nsubj
3	argue	argue	VBP	O	1	acl:relcl
4	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	8	det
6	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
7	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Act	Act	NNP	O	12	nsubj
9	has	have	VBZ	O	12	aux
10	been	be	VBN	O	12	cop
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	staple	staple	NN	O	3	ccomp
13	in	in	IN	O	14	mark
14	keeping	keep	VBG	O	12	acl
15	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	16	nsubj
16	free	free	JJ	O	14	xcomp
17	from	from	IN	O	16	nmod
18	argue	argue	VBP	O	21	ccomp
19	,	,	,	O	21	punct
20	would	would	MD	O	21	aux
21	cite	cite	VB	O	0	ROOT
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	arrest	arrest	NN	O	21	dobj
24	of	of	IN	O	25	case
25	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	23	nmod
26	born	bear	VBN	O	25	acl
27	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	30	amod
28	Jefferey	Jefferey	NNP	PERSON	30	compound
29	Leon	Leon	NNP	PERSON	30	compound
30	Battle	Battle	NNP	PERSON	21	nsubj
31	in	in	IN	O	32	case
32	2002	2002	CD	DATE	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	7	advmod
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	6	case
5	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nmod
7	became	become	VBD	O	15	advcl
8	suspicious	suspicious	JJ	O	7	xcomp
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	Battle	battle	NN	O	12	nmod:poss
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	activities	activity	NNS	O	7	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	they	they	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	requested	request	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	were	be	VBD	O	18	auxpass
18	granted	grant	VBN	O	15	conj
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	wiretap	wiretap	NN	O	18	dobj
21	from	from	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	nmod
24	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	25	case
25	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	nmod
26	under	under	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	provisions	provision	NNS	O	18	nmod
29	of	of	IN	O	32	case
30	the	the	DT	O	32	det
31	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	32	compound
32	Act	Act	NNP	O	28	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Thanks	thanks	NNS	O	5	nsubj
2	to	to	TO	O	4	case
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	wiretap	wiretap	NN	O	1	nmod
5	allowed	allow	VBN	O	13	advcl
6	by	by	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	act	act	NN	O	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	13	punct
10	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
11	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	officials	official	NNS	O	13	nsubj
13	recorded	record	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	Battle	battle	NN	O	13	dobj
15	calling	call	VBG	O	14	acl
16	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	15	iobj
17	unbelievers	unbeliever	NNS	O	15	dobj
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	pigs	pig	NNS	O	17	conj
20	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	conversion	conversion	NN	O	20	nsubjpass
3	regarding	regard	VBG	O	2	dep
4	Battle	battle	NN	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	plans	plan	NNS	O	3	dobj
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	join	join	VB	O	6	acl
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	ranks	rank	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	Al-Qaeda	Al-Qaeda	NNP	MISC	10	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
14	becoming	become	VBG	O	3	conj
15	an	a	DT	O	17	det
16	Islamic	islamic	JJ	MISC	17	amod
17	martyr	martyr	NN	O	14	xcomp
18	were	be	VBD	O	20	auxpass
19	also	also	RB	O	20	advmod
20	detected	detect	VBN	O	0	ROOT
21	in	in	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	recorded	record	VBN	O	24	amod
24	conversation	conversation	NN	O	20	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	Aspects	aspect	NNS	O	9	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	6	case
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	conversation	conversation	NN	O	6	compound
5	present	present	JJ	DATE	6	amod
6	evidence	evidence	NN	O	1	nmod
7	that	that	IN	O	8	case
8	Battle	battle	NN	O	6	nmod
9	planned	plan	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	on	on	IN	O	11	mark
11	centralizing	centralize	VBG	O	9	advcl
12	attacks	attack	NNS	O	11	dobj
13	at	at	IN	O	14	case
14	synagogues	synagogue	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	on	on	IN	O	21	case
17	the	the	DT	O	21	det
18	Israeli	israeli	JJ	MISC	21	amod
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	Jewish	jewish	JJ	MISC	18	conj
21	community	community	NN	O	14	conj
22	in	in	IN	O	23	case
23	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	21	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Battle	battle	NN	O	3	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	auxpass
3	quoted	quote	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	as	as	IN	O	5	mark
5	saying	say	VBG	O	3	advcl
6	``	``	``	O	38	punct
7	If	if	IN	O	12	mark
8	every	every	DT	O	9	det
9	time	time	NN	O	12	nmod:tmod
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	Israelites	Israelites	NNPS	MISC	12	nsubj
12	hurt	hurt	VBD	O	38	advcl
13	or	or	CC	O	12	cc
14	harm	harm	VB	O	12	conj
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	Muslim	muslim	JJ	MISC	24	dobj
17	over	over	IN	O	18	case
18	there	there	EX	O	16	nmod
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
20	In	in	IN	O	21	case
21	Palestine	Palestine	NNP	LOCATION	24	dep
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
23	you	you	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	go	go	VBP	O	14	ccomp
25	into	into	IN	O	27	case
26	a	a	DT	O	27	det
27	synagogue	synagogue	NN	O	24	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
29	hurt	hurt	VB	O	14	conj
30	one	one	CD	NUMBER	29	dobj
31	over	over	IN	O	32	case
32	here	here	RB	O	29	nmod
33	,	,	,	O	29	punct
34	okay	okay	JJ	O	29	xcomp
35	,	,	,	O	38	punct
36	they	they	PRP	O	38	nsubj
37	're	be	VBP	O	38	aux
38	going	go	VBG	O	5	ccomp
39	to	to	TO	O	40	mark
40	say	say	VB	O	38	xcomp
41	`	`	``	O	52	punct
42	Wait	wait	VB	O	52	ccomp
43	a	a	DT	DURATION	44	det
44	minute	minute	NN	DURATION	42	dobj
45	we	we	PRP	O	46	nsubj
46	got	get	VBD	O	44	acl:relcl
47	to	to	TO	O	48	mark
48	stop	stop	VB	O	46	xcomp
49	,	,	,	O	52	punct
50	we	we	PRP	O	52	nsubj
51	're	be	VBP	O	52	aux
52	seeing	see	VBG	O	40	ccomp
53	a	a	DT	O	54	det
54	connection	connection	NN	O	52	dobj
55	here	here	RB	O	52	advmod
56	.	.	.	O	3	punct
57	'	'	''	O	3	punct

1	Okay	okay	UH	O	0	ROOT
2	''	''	''	O	1	punct
3	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	4	punct
4	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
5	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	3	mark
2	closely	closely	RB	O	3	advmod
3	monitoring	monitor	VBG	O	18	advcl
4	Battle	battle	NN	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	activity	activity	NN	O	3	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	11	case
8	the	the	DT	DURATION	11	det
9	next	next	JJ	DURATION	11	amod
10	few	few	JJ	DURATION	11	amod
11	weeks	week	NNS	DURATION	6	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	18	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	nsubj
15	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	17	case
16	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod
18	issued	issue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	warrant	warrant	NN	O	18	dobj
21	for	for	IN	O	23	case
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	arrest	arrest	NN	O	20	nmod
24	for	for	IN	O	25	mark
25	attempting	attempt	VBG	O	18	advcl
26	to	to	TO	O	28	case
27	wage	wage	NN	O	28	compound
28	war	war	NN	O	25	nmod
29	against	against	IN	O	32	case
30	the	the	DT	O	32	det
31	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	32	compound
32	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	28	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	Jefferey	Jefferey	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
2	Leon	Leon	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Battle	Battle	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	tried	try	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	convicted	convict	VBN	O	5	conj
8	,	,	,	O	5	punct
9	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
10	is	be	VBZ	O	12	aux
11	now	now	RB	DATE	12	advmod
12	serving	serve	VBG	O	5	conj
13	time	time	NN	O	12	dobj
14	in	in	IN	O	17	case
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	federal	federal	JJ	O	17	amod
17	prison	prison	NN	O	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	4	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	convicted	convict	VBN	O	7	advcl
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	Battle	Battle	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	in	in	IN	O	11	case
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	later	later	JJ	O	11	advmod
11	interview	interview	NN	O	7	nmod
12	``	``	``	O	11	punct
13	We	we	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	were	be	VBD	O	15	cop
15	willing	willing	JJ	O	11	dep
16	to	to	TO	O	17	case
17	murder	murder	NN	O	15	nmod
18	at	at	IN	O	19	case
19	least	least	JJS	O	20	nmod:npmod
20	100	100	CD	NUMBER	17	dep
21	or	or	CC	O	17	cc
22	1,000	1,000	CD	NUMBER	17	conj
23	of	of	IN	O	24	case
24	them	they	PRP	O	22	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	24	punct
26	big	big	JJ	O	27	amod
27	numbers	number	NNS	O	24	appos
28	''	''	''	O	11	punct
29	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	30	punct
30	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	11	appos
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	30	punct
32	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Because	because	IN	O	6	case
2	of	of	IN	O	6	case
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	6	compound
5	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Act	Act	NNP	O	14	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	14	punct
8	thousands	thousand	NNS	O	14	nsubjpass
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	American	american	JJ	MISC	11	amod
11	lives	life	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	were	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
13	perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	14	advmod
14	saved	save	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	government	government	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	monitor	monitor	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	Battle	battle	NN	O	5	dobj
7	under	under	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	5	nmod
11	when	when	WRB	O	14	advmod
12	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubjpass
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	tipped	tip	VBN	O	5	advcl
15	off	off	RP	O	14	compound:prt
16	by	by	IN	O	19	case
17	an	a	DT	O	19	det
18	electronic	electronic	JJ	O	19	amod
19	trail	trail	NN	O	14	nmod
20	left	leave	VBN	O	19	acl
21	by	by	IN	O	22	case
22	Battle	battle	NN	O	20	nmod
23	that	that	WDT	O	24	nsubj
24	connected	connect	VBD	O	22	acl:relcl
25	him	he	PRP	O	24	dobj
26	to	to	TO	O	30	case
27	an	a	DT	O	30	det
28	American	american	JJ	MISC	30	amod
29	terror	terror	NN	O	30	compound
30	ring	ring	NN	O	24	nmod
31	known	know	VBN	O	30	acl
32	as	as	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	Squad	Squad	NNP	O	31	nmod
35	of	of	IN	O	36	case
36	Death	Death	NNP	O	34	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	wiring	wiring	NN	O	33	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	money	money	NN	O	2	nmod
5	sent	send	VBN	O	4	acl
6	to	to	TO	O	7	case
7	Afghanistan	Afghanistan	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
8	from	from	IN	O	11	case
9	Portland	Portland	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
10	,	,	,	O	11	punct
11	Oregon	Oregon	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
12	by	by	IN	O	13	case
13	Squad	Squad	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
14	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	16	case
15	Death	Death	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
16	members	member	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	19	case
18	Al-Qaeda	Al-Qaeda	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
19	commanders	commander	NNS	O	5	nmod
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	help	help	VB	O	5	xcomp
22	aid	aid	NN	O	31	nsubj
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	their	they	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	war	war	NN	O	22	nmod
26	against	against	IN	O	25	acl
27	the	the	DT	O	31	det
28	``	``	``	O	31	punct
29	unbelieving	unbelieving	JJ	O	31	amod
30	''	''	''	O	31	punct
31	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	21	xcomp
32	,	,	,	O	33	punct
33	caught	catch	VBD	O	0	ROOT
34	the	the	DT	O	35	det
35	eye	eye	NN	O	33	dobj
36	of	of	IN	O	38	case
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	nmod
39	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	41	case
40	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	41	compound
41	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	38	nmod
42	.	.	.	O	33	punct

1	Due	due	JJ	O	3	case
2	in	in	IN	O	3	case
3	part	part	NN	O	7	nmod
4	to	to	TO	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	provisions	provision	NNS	O	3	nmod
7	allowed	allow	VBN	O	17	advcl
8	under	under	IN	O	12	case
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
11	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	12	compound
12	Act	Act	NNP	O	7	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	17	punct
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	DHS	dhs	NN	ORGANIZATION	17	nsubj
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	cop
17	able	able	JJ	O	0	ROOT
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	monitor	monitor	VB	O	17	xcomp
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	activity	activity	NN	O	19	dobj
22	of	of	IN	O	23	case
23	Battle	battle	NN	O	21	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	21	punct
25	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
26	all	all	DT	O	27	det
27	Squad	squad	NN	MISC	21	conj
28	of	of	IN	MISC	30	case
29	Death	death	NN	MISC	30	compound
30	members	member	NNS	O	27	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	scenario	scenario	NN	O	10	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	10	punct
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	7	compound
7	Act	Act	NNP	O	10	nsubj
8	not	not	RB	O	9	dep
9	only	only	RB	O	10	advmod
10	saved	save	VBD	O	0	ROOT
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	lives	life	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	Americans	american	NNS	MISC	12	nmod
15	at	at	IN	O	16	case
16	home	home	NN	O	14	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	14	punct
18	but	but	CC	O	14	cc
19	also	also	RB	O	20	advmod
20	those	those	DT	O	14	conj
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	American	american	JJ	MISC	23	amod
23	soldiers	soldier	NNS	O	20	nmod
24	overseas	overseas	RB	O	10	advmod
25	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Those	those	DT	O	15	nsubj
2	who	who	WP	O	4	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	aux
4	using	use	VBG	O	1	acl:relcl
5	technology	technology	NN	O	4	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	their	they	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	attempts	attempt	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	harm	harm	VB	O	8	acl
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	American	american	JJ	MISC	13	amod
13	people	people	NNS	O	10	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	15	punct
15	pose	pose	VBP	O	0	ROOT
16	one	one	CD	NUMBER	15	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	21	case
18	the	the	DT	O	21	det
19	most	most	RBS	O	20	advmod
20	dangerous	dangerous	JJ	O	21	amod
21	threats	threat	NNS	O	16	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	24	case
23	our	we	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
24	nation	nation	NN	O	15	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Technological	technological	JJ	O	2	amod
2	warfare	warfare	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	still	still	RB	O	6	advmod
5	fairly	fairly	RB	O	6	advmod
6	new	new	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	government	government	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	an	a	DT	O	5	dobj
7	inside	inside	IN	O	8	case
8	track	track	NN	O	6	nmod
9	in	in	IN	O	10	mark
10	countering	counter	VBG	O	8	acl
11	technological	technological	JJ	O	12	amod
12	warfare	warfare	NN	O	10	dobj
13	with	with	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	provisions	provision	NNS	O	10	nmod
16	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	19	compound
19	Act	Act	NNP	O	20	nsubj
20	allows	allow	VBZ	O	10	ccomp
21	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	``	``	``	O	6	punct
2	Wire	wire	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	electronic	electronic	JJ	O	5	amod
5	communications	communication	NNS	O	2	conj
6	relating	relate	VBG	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	case
8	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	use	use	NN	O	16	nsubjpass
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	chemical	chemical	NN	O	14	compound
14	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	were	be	VBD	O	16	auxpass
16	added	add	VBN	O	6	conj
17	as	as	IN	O	18	case
18	felonies	felony	NNS	O	16	nmod
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	they	they	PRP	O	18	conj
21	too	too	RB	O	25	advmod
22	,	,	,	O	25	punct
23	may	may	MD	O	25	aux
24	be	be	VB	O	25	auxpass
25	intercepted	intercept	VBN	O	20	acl:relcl
26	''	''	''	O	25	punct
27	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	28	punct
28	Ebenger	Ebenger	NNP	O	20	appos
29	,	,	,	O	28	punct
30	p.	p.	NN	O	28	dep
31	49	49	CD	NUMBER	30	nummod
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	28	punct
33	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	one	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	instance	instance	NN	O	8	nmod
4	an	a	DT	O	5	det
5	interception	interception	NN	O	8	nsubj
6	of	of	IN	O	7	case
7	e-mails	e-mail	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	prevented	prevent	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	serious	serious	JJ	O	11	amod
11	threat	threat	NN	O	8	dobj
12	against	against	IN	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	15	compound
15	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	8	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
17	it	it	PRP	O	19	nsubj
18	's	be	VBZ	O	19	cop
19	people	people	NNS	O	8	conj
20	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	``	``	``	O	23	punct
2	In	in	IN	O	3	case
3	2002	2002	CD	DATE	23	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	23	punct
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	9	case
8	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	nmod
10	foiled	foiled	JJ	O	9	dep
11	an	a	DT	O	12	det
12	attempt	attempt	NN	O	10	dobj
13	by	by	IN	O	21	case
14	affluent	affluent	JJ	O	21	amod
15	software	software	NN	O	21	compound
16	engineer	engineer	NN	O	21	compound
17	Maher	Maher	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
18	`	`	``	O	21	punct
19	Mike	Mike	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
20	'	'	''	PERSON	21	punct
21	Hawash	Hawash	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	aid	aid	VB	O	0	ROOT
24	Squad	Squad	NNP	O	23	dobj
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	Death	Death	NNP	O	27	compound
27	members	member	NNS	O	24	nmod
28	who	who	WP	O	31	nsubj
29	were	be	VBD	O	31	aux
30	overseas	overseas	JJ	O	31	advmod
31	trying	try	VBG	O	24	acl:relcl
32	to	to	TO	O	33	mark
33	make	make	VB	O	31	xcomp
34	their	they	PRP$	O	35	nmod:poss
35	way	way	NN	O	33	dobj
36	into	into	IN	O	37	case
37	Pakistan	Pakistan	NNP	LOCATION	33	nmod
38	so	so	IN	O	23	dep
39	they	they	PRP	O	41	nsubj
40	could	could	MD	O	41	aux
41	join	join	VB	O	23	parataxis
42	the	the	DT	O	43	det
43	forces	force	NNS	O	41	dobj
44	of	of	IN	O	45	case
45	Al-Qaeda	Al-Qaeda	NNP	MISC	43	nmod
46	''	''	''	O	43	punct
47	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	48	punct
48	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	43	appos
49	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	48	punct
50	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	mark
2	order	order	NN	O	1	mwe
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	get	get	VB	O	22	advcl
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	border	border	NN	O	7	compound
7	guards	guard	NNS	O	4	dobj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	grant	grant	VB	O	4	xcomp
10	members	member	NNS	O	9	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Squad	squad	NN	O	10	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	Death	death	NN	O	16	compound
16	entry	entry	NN	O	13	nmod
17	into	into	IN	O	18	case
18	Pakistan	Pakistan	NNP	LOCATION	9	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	22	punct
20	Hawash	Hawash	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubjpass
21	was	be	VBD	O	22	auxpass
22	supposed	suppose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	wire	wire	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	guards	guard	NNS	O	28	nsubj
27	a	a	DT	O	28	det
28	payment	payment	NN	O	24	xcomp
29	of	of	IN	O	32	case
30	somewhere	somewhere	RB	O	32	advmod
31	between	between	IN	O	32	advmod
32	2,000	2,000	CD	NUMBER	28	nmod
33	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
34	6,000	6,000	CD	MONEY	35	nummod
35	dollars	dollar	NNS	MONEY	28	conj
36	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	details	detail	NNS	O	19	nsubjpass
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	payment	payment	NN	O	2	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
8	process	process	NN	O	5	conj
9	in	in	IN	O	10	case
10	which	which	WDT	O	16	nmod
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	Squad	squad	NN	LOCATION	16	nsubj
13	of	of	IN	LOCATION	14	case
14	Death	death	NN	LOCATION	12	nmod
15	would	would	MD	O	16	aux
16	enter	enter	VB	O	5	acl:relcl
17	Pakistan	Pakistan	NNP	LOCATION	16	dobj
18	were	be	VBD	O	19	auxpass
19	discussed	discuss	VBN	O	0	ROOT
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	depth	depth	NN	O	19	nmod
22	in	in	IN	O	23	case
23	e-mails	e-mail	NNS	O	19	nmod
24	sent	send	VBN	O	23	acl
25	between	between	IN	O	26	case
26	Hawash	Hawash	NNP	PERSON	24	nmod
27	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
28	one	one	CD	NUMBER	26	conj
29	of	of	IN	O	31	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	guards	guard	NNS	O	28	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	nsubjpass
3	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	6	mark
4	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	nsubj
6	intercepted	intercept	VBD	O	2	acl
7	these	these	DT	O	8	det
8	e-mails	e-mail	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
10	they	they	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	were	be	VBD	O	12	cop
12	able	able	JJ	O	6	conj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	freeze	freeze	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	Hawash	Hawash	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod:poss
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	back	back	JJ	O	18	amod
18	account	account	NN	O	14	dobj
19	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
20	all	all	PDT	O	22	det:predet
21	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	assets	asset	NNS	O	6	conj
23	before	before	IN	O	25	case
24	any	any	DT	O	25	det
25	transfer	transfer	NN	O	22	dep
26	of	of	IN	O	27	case
27	money	money	NN	O	25	nmod
28	could	could	MD	O	30	aux
29	be	be	VB	O	30	auxpass
30	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
31	.	.	.	O	30	punct

1	Within	within	IN	O	2	case
2	hours	hour	NNS	DURATION	7	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	7	punct
4	an	a	DT	O	5	det
5	arrest	arrest	NN	O	7	nsubjpass
6	was	be	VBD	O	7	auxpass
7	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
10	eventually	eventually	RB	O	12	advmod
11	Hawash	Hawash	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
12	pled	plead	VBD	O	7	conj
13	guilty	guilty	JJ	O	12	xcomp
14	to	to	TO	O	16	case
15	two	two	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
16	counts	count	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	conspiracy	conspiracy	NN	O	16	nmod
19	as	as	RB	O	12	cc
20	well	well	RB	O	19	mwe
21	as	as	IN	O	19	mwe
22	attempting	attempt	VBG	O	12	conj
23	to	to	TO	O	25	case
24	wage	wage	NN	O	25	compound
25	war	war	NN	O	22	nmod
26	on	on	IN	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	29	compound
29	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	5	advmod
2	in	in	IN	O	5	case
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	fictional	fictional	JJ	O	5	amod
5	universe	universe	NN	O	11	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	11	punct
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	9	compound
9	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	11	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
11	able	able	JJ	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	counter	counter	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	15	amod
15	attacks	attack	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	6	case
2	the	the	DT	O	6	det
3	Showtime	Showtime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
4	series	series	NN	O	6	compound
5	``	``	``	O	6	punct
6	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	O	11	nmod
7	''	''	''	O	6	punct
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	CIA	CIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	nsubj
11	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	video	video	NN	O	13	compound
13	surveillance	surveillance	NN	O	11	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	phone	phone	NN	O	16	compound
16	taps	tap	NNS	O	13	conj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	monitor	monitor	VB	O	11	xcomp
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	activities	activity	NNS	O	18	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	Sergeant	Sergeant	NNP	O	24	compound
23	Nicholas	Nicholas	NNP	PERSON	24	compound
24	Brody	Brody	NNP	PERSON	20	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Brody	Brody	NNP	PERSON	20	nsubj
2	believed	believe	VBN	O	1	acl
3	by	by	IN	O	4	case
4	many	many	JJ	O	2	nmod
5	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
6	be	be	VB	O	9	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	war	war	NN	O	9	compound
9	hero	hero	NN	O	2	xcomp
10	who	who	WP	O	11	nsubj
11	endured	endure	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
12	eight	eight	CD	DURATION	13	nummod
13	years	year	NNS	DURATION	11	nmod:tmod
14	as	as	IN	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	POW	pow	NN	O	11	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	20	punct
18	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
19	actually	actually	RB	O	20	advmod
20	a	a	DT	O	0	ROOT
21	turned	turn	VBN	O	20	acl
22	American	American	NNP	MISC	21	dobj
23	who	who	WP	O	26	nsubj
24	is	be	VBZ	O	26	aux
25	now	now	RB	DATE	26	advmod
26	working	work	VBG	O	22	acl:relcl
27	as	as	IN	O	30	case
28	a	a	DT	O	30	det
29	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	30	amod
30	terrorist	terrorist	NN	O	26	nmod
31	for	for	IN	O	32	case
32	Al-Qaeda	Al-Qaeda	NNP	MISC	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	2	mark
2	monitoring	monitor	VBG	O	10	advcl
3	him	he	PRP	O	2	dobj
4	for	for	IN	O	6	case
5	some	some	DT	O	6	det
6	time	time	NN	O	2	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	10	punct
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	CIA	CIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	nsubj
10	learns	learn	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
11	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
12	Brody	Brody	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	14	aux
14	planning	plan	VBG	O	10	ccomp
15	on	on	IN	O	16	mark
16	detonating	detonate	VBG	O	14	advcl
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	bomb	bomb	NN	O	16	dobj
19	while	while	IN	O	22	case
20	in	in	IN	O	22	case
21	a	a	DT	O	22	det
22	bunker	bunker	NN	O	16	nmod
23	with	with	IN	O	25	case
24	many	many	JJ	O	25	amod
25	Senators	Senators	NNPS	O	22	nmod
26	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
27	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	25	conj
28	inside	inside	IN	O	22	case
29	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	22	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	22	punct
3	since	since	IN	O	7	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	CIA	CIA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
7	aware	aware	JJ	O	22	advcl
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	plan	plan	NN	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	Carrie	Carrie	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Mathison	Mathison	NNP	PERSON	10	appos
14	,	,	,	O	22	punct
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	agent	agent	NN	O	22	nsubj
17	assigned	assign	VBN	O	16	acl
18	to	to	TO	O	21	case
19	Brody	Brody	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod:poss
20	's	's	POS	O	19	case
21	case	case	NN	O	17	nmod
22	calls	call	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
23	his	he	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	daughter	daughter	NN	O	25	compound
25	Dana	Dana	NNP	PERSON	22	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	Dana	Dana	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	auxpass
3	told	tell	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	what	what	WP	O	10	dobj
5	her	she	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	father	father	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	aux
8	about	about	IN	O	3	ccomp
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	do	do	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	,	,	,	O	3	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
13	calls	call	VBZ	O	3	conj
14	him	he	PRP	O	13	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	convince	convince	VB	O	13	xcomp
17	him	he	PRP	O	16	dobj
18	not	not	RB	O	20	neg
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	do	do	VB	O	16	xcomp
21	it	it	PRP	O	20	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	20	punct
23	thus	thus	RB	O	24	advmod
24	saving	save	VBG	O	20	advcl
25	hundreds	hundred	NNS	O	24	dobj
26	of	of	IN	O	27	case
27	lives	life	NNS	O	25	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	6	punct
2	``	``	``	O	6	punct
3	Marine	Marine	NNP	O	6	nsubj
4	One	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
5	''	''	''	O	6	punct
6	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	0	ROOT
7	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	DATE	4	det
3	last	last	JJ	DATE	4	amod
4	decade	decade	NN	DATE	9	nmod
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	7	compound
7	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	9	nsubj
8	has	have	VBZ	O	9	aux
9	helped	help	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	save	save	VB	O	9	ccomp
11	many	many	JJ	O	12	amod
12	lives	life	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	,	,	,	O	9	punct
14	however	however	RB	O	21	advmod
15	on	on	IN	O	16	case
16	occasion	occasion	NN	O	21	nmod
17	it	it	PRP	O	21	nsubjpass
18	has	have	VBZ	O	21	aux
19	also	also	RB	O	21	advmod
20	been	be	VBN	O	21	auxpass
21	used	use	VBN	O	9	parataxis
22	wrongfully	wrongfully	RB	O	21	advmod
23	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Since	since	IN	O	6	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	4	compound
4	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	6	nsubjpass
5	was	be	VBD	O	6	auxpass
6	passed	pass	VBN	O	16	advcl
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	2001	2001	CD	DATE	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	16	punct
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	nsubj
12	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	13	case
13	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	nmod
14	has	have	VBZ	O	16	aux
15	been	be	VBN	O	16	aux
16	taking	take	VBG	O	0	ROOT
17	advantage	advantage	NN	O	16	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	22	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	law	law	NN	O	22	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	provision	provision	NN	O	17	nmod
23	allowing	allow	VBG	O	22	dep
24	unwarranted	unwarranted	JJ	O	25	amod
25	wiretaps	wiretap	NNS	O	23	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	DOJ	DOJ	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	4	aux
4	wiretapped	wiretap	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	monitored	monitor	VBN	O	4	conj
7	people	people	NNS	O	4	dobj
8	who	who	WP	O	10	dobj
9	they	they	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	suspect	suspect	VBP	O	7	acl:relcl
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	criminal	criminal	JJ	O	13	amod
13	cases	case	NNS	O	4	nmod
14	that	that	WDT	O	18	nsubj
15	are	be	VBP	O	18	cop
16	not	not	RB	O	18	neg
17	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	18	nmod:npmod
18	related	related	JJ	O	13	acl:relcl
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	``	``	``	O	6	punct
2	The	the	DT	O	3	det
3	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	5	case
5	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nmod
6	requested	request	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	won	win	VBD	O	6	conj
9	approval	approval	NN	O	6	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	1,754	1,754	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	wiretaps	wiretap	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	2004	2004	CD	DATE	12	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	9	punct
16	following	follow	VBG	O	17	case
17	1,724	1,724	CD	NUMBER	9	nmod
18	granted	grant	VBN	O	17	acl
19	requests	request	NNS	O	18	dobj
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	2003	2003	CD	DATE	19	nmod
22	''	''	''	O	19	punct
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	Barr	barr	NN	O	19	appos
25	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
26	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	2008	2008	CD	DATE	9	nmod
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Act	Act	NNP	O	9	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
7	on	on	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	floor	floor	NN	O	0	ROOT
10	of	of	IN	O	11	case
11	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	9	punct
13	awaiting	await	VBG	O	9	xcomp
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	vote	vote	NN	O	13	dobj
16	on	on	IN	O	17	case
17	weather	weather	NN	O	13	nmod
18	or	or	CC	O	9	cc
19	not	not	RB	O	24	neg
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	law	law	NN	O	24	nsubjpass
22	would	would	MD	O	24	aux
23	be	be	VB	O	24	auxpass
24	renewed	renew	VBN	O	9	conj
25	back	back	RB	O	24	advmod
26	into	into	IN	O	27	case
27	action	action	NN	O	24	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	lawmakers	lawmaker	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	argued	argue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	against	against	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	bill	bill	NN	O	3	nmod
7	granting	grant	VBG	O	6	acl
8	even	even	RB	O	9	advmod
9	more	more	RBR	O	11	amod
10	government	government	NN	O	11	compound
11	access	access	NN	O	7	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	personal	personal	JJ	O	14	amod
14	records	record	NNS	O	7	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	which	which	WDT	O	18	nsubj
17	would	would	MD	O	18	aux
18	include	include	VB	O	14	acl:relcl
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	DNA	dna	NN	MISC	21	compound
21	history	history	NN	O	18	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	financial	financial	JJ	O	24	amod
24	records	record	NNS	O	21	conj
25	,	,	,	O	21	punct
26	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
27	purchase	purchase	NN	O	28	compound
28	history	history	NN	O	21	conj
29	of	of	IN	O	30	case
30	anyone	anyone	NN	O	28	nmod
31	who	who	WP	O	36	nsubj
32	was	be	VBD	O	36	cop
33	a	a	DT	O	36	det
34	suspected	suspect	VBN	O	36	amod
35	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	36	amod
36	terrorist	terrorist	NN	O	28	acl:relcl
37	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	``	``	``	O	5	punct
2	It	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	might	might	MD	O	5	aux
4	also	also	RB	O	5	advmod
5	include	include	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	protesters	protester	NNS	O	5	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	or	or	CC	O	6	cc
9	anyone	anyone	NN	O	6	conj
10	else	else	RB	O	13	advmod
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	government	government	NN	O	13	compound
13	dislikes	dislikes	NN	O	9	dep
14	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Remember	remember	VB	O	8	ccomp
2	,	,	,	O	8	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	7	det
4	original	original	JJ	O	7	amod
5	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	7	compound
6	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	7	compound
7	Act	Act	NNP	O	8	nsubj
8	defined	define	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	new	new	JJ	O	11	amod
11	crime	crime	NN	O	8	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	15	case
13	`	`	``	O	15	punct
14	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	15	amod
15	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	11	nmod
16	'	'	''	O	15	punct
17	broadly	broadly	RB	O	20	advmod
18	,	,	,	O	20	punct
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	encompass	encompass	VB	O	15	dep
21	`	`	``	O	20	punct
22	any	any	DT	O	23	det
23	action	action	NN	O	20	dobj
24	that	that	WDT	O	25	nsubj
25	endangers	endanger	VBZ	O	23	acl:relcl
26	human	human	JJ	O	27	amod
27	life	life	NN	O	25	dobj
28	that	that	WDT	O	31	nsubj
29	is	be	VBZ	O	31	cop
30	a	a	DT	O	31	det
31	violation	violation	NN	O	27	acl:relcl
32	of	of	IN	O	37	case
33	any	any	DT	O	37	det
34	federal	federal	JJ	O	37	amod
35	or	or	CC	O	34	cc
36	state	state	NN	O	34	conj
37	law	law	NN	O	31	nmod
38	'	'	''	O	20	punct
39	''	''	''	O	15	punct
40	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	41	punct
41	Ramasastry	Ramasastry	NNP	PERSON	15	appos
42	,	,	,	O	41	punct
43	p.	p.	NN	O	41	dep
44	8	8	CD	NUMBER	43	nummod
45	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	41	punct
46	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	2	mark
2	debating	debate	VBG	O	11	advcl
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	act	act	NN	O	2	dobj
5	,	,	,	O	11	punct
6	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	8	compound
7	Bob	Bob	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
9	from	from	IN	O	10	case
10	Georgia	Georgia	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
11	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	``	``	``	O	11	punct
14	The	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	16	compound
16	administration	administration	NN	O	19	nsubj
17	has	have	VBZ	O	19	aux
18	repeatedly	repeatedly	RB	O	19	advmod
19	stated	state	VBN	O	11	ccomp
20	its	its	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	intention	intention	NN	O	19	dobj
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	expand	expand	VB	O	21	acl
24	the	the	DT	O	27	det
25	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	27	compound
26	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	27	compound
27	Act	Act	NNP	O	23	dobj
28	,	,	,	O	19	punct
29	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
30	has	have	VBZ	O	31	aux
31	floated	float	VBN	O	19	conj
32	various	various	JJ	O	33	amod
33	pieces	piece	NNS	O	31	dobj
34	of	of	IN	O	35	case
35	legislation	legislation	NN	O	33	nmod
36	that	that	WDT	O	38	nsubj
37	would	would	MD	O	38	aux
38	do	do	VB	O	35	acl:relcl
39	so	so	RB	O	38	advmod
40	''	''	''	O	39	punct
41	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	42	punct
42	Barr	barr	NN	PERSON	35	appos
43	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	42	punct
44	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	argument	argument	NN	O	16	nsubj
3	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
4	President	President	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	abused	abuse	VBD	O	2	dep
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	power	power	NN	O	6	dobj
9	under	under	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	12	compound
12	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	6	nmod
13	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
14	not	not	RB	O	16	neg
15	an	a	DT	O	16	det
16	uncommon	uncommon	JJ	O	0	ROOT
17	one	one	CD	NUMBER	16	nmod:tmod
18	,	,	,	O	16	punct
19	``	``	``	O	59	punct
20	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	59	dep
21	relied	rely	VB	O	20	dep
22	on	on	IN	O	25	case
23	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
24	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	advisers	adviser	NNS	O	21	nmod
26	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
27	legal	legal	JJ	O	28	amod
28	interpretations	interpretation	NNS	O	25	conj
29	by	by	IN	O	31	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	nmod
32	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	35	case
33	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	nmod:poss
34	's	's	POS	ORGANIZATION	33	case
35	Office	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	nmod
36	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	38	case
37	Legal	Legal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	38	compound
38	Counsel	Counsel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	nmod
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	OLC	OLC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	38	appos
41	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct
42	to	to	TO	O	43	mark
43	bolster	bolster	VB	O	21	xcomp
44	his	he	PRP$	O	46	nmod:poss
45	presidential	presidential	JJ	O	46	amod
46	powers	power	NNS	O	43	dobj
47	under	under	IN	O	49	case
48	Article	Article	NNP	O	49	compound
49	II	II	NNP	O	43	nmod
50	of	of	IN	O	52	case
51	the	the	DT	O	52	det
52	Constitution	Constitution	NNP	O	49	nmod
53	and	and	CC	O	43	cc
54	expand	expand	VB	O	43	conj
55	them	they	PRP	O	54	dobj
56	unilaterally	unilaterally	RB	O	54	advmod
57	''	''	''	O	59	punct
58	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	59	punct
59	Banks	bank	NNS	O	16	appos
60	,	,	,	O	59	punct
61	p.	p.	NN	O	59	dep
62	7	7	CD	NUMBER	61	nummod
63	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	59	punct
64	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	also	also	RB	O	4	advmod
4	stated	state	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	belief	belief	NN	O	4	dobj
7	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	12	nsubj
11	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
12	ineffective	ineffective	JJ	O	4	ccomp
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	argued	argue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	7	compound
7	Act	Act	NNP	O	8	nsubj
8	was	be	VBD	O	2	ccomp
9	yet	yet	RB	O	8	advmod
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	prevent	prevent	VB	O	8	xcomp
12	a	a	DT	O	15	det
13	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	15	amod
14	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	15	amod
15	attack	attack	NN	O	11	dobj
16	,	,	,	O	2	punct
17	citing	cite	VBG	O	2	xcomp
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	Squad	squad	NN	MISC	17	dobj
20	of	of	IN	MISC	23	case
21	Death	Death	NNP	MISC	23	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	attempt	attempt	NN	O	19	nmod
24	as	as	IN	O	25	case
25	more	more	JJR	O	17	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	29	case
27	a	a	DT	O	29	det
28	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	29	amod
29	threat	threat	NN	O	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	4	advmod
2	Barr	barr	NN	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	also	also	RB	O	4	advmod
4	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	``	``	``	O	7	punct
6	I	I	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	grant	grant	VBP	O	4	ccomp
8	we	we	PRP	O	11	nsubj
9	have	have	VBP	O	11	aux
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	suffered	suffer	VBN	O	7	ccomp
12	another	another	DT	O	15	det
13	major	major	JJ	O	15	amod
14	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	15	amod
15	attack	attack	NN	O	11	dobj
16	since	since	IN	O	17	case
17	9/11	9/11	CD	NUMBER	11	nmod
18	''	''	''	O	4	punct
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
20	Barr	barr	NN	PERSON	4	dep
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	4	nsubj
2	could	could	MD	O	4	aux
3	also	also	RB	O	4	advmod
4	look	look	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	Boston	Boston	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	Bombings	bombing	NNS	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
9	as	as	IN	O	13	case
10	a	a	DT	O	13	det
11	more	more	RBR	O	12	advmod
12	recent	recent	JJ	O	13	amod
13	example	example	NN	O	4	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	19	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	17	compound
17	Act	Act	NNP	O	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	ineffectiveness	ineffectiveness	NN	O	13	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	5	case
4	Homeland	Homeland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
6	failed	fail	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	counter	counter	VB	O	6	xcomp
9	an	a	DT	O	10	det
10	attack	attack	NN	O	8	dobj
11	at	at	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	Boston	Boston	NNP	LOCATION	14	compound
14	Marathon	Marathon	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
15	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubjpass
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	auxpass
17	carried	carry	VBN	O	14	acl:relcl
18	out	out	RP	O	17	compound:prt
19	by	by	IN	O	22	case
20	two	two	CD	NUMBER	22	nummod
21	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	22	amod
22	terrorists	terrorist	NNS	O	17	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	3	compound
2	Peter	Peter	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	King	King	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	6	compound
6	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	3	punct
8	Head	Head	NNP	O	3	appos
9	of	of	IN	O	13	case
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
12	Security	Security	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	Committee	Committee	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	3	punct
15	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	there	there	EX	O	17	expl
17	was	be	VBD	O	15	ccomp
18	``	``	``	O	17	punct
19	no	no	DT	O	20	neg
20	intelligence	intelligence	NN	O	17	nsubj
21	that	that	WDT	O	22	nsubj
22	seemed	seem	VBD	O	20	acl:relcl
23	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
24	be	be	VB	O	29	cop
25	out	out	IN	O	29	case
26	there	there	RB	O	29	advmod
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	indicated	indicate	VBN	O	29	amod
29	something	something	NN	O	22	xcomp
30	like	like	IN	O	33	mark
31	this	this	DT	O	33	nsubjpass
32	was	be	VBD	O	33	auxpass
33	planned	plan	VBN	O	29	advcl
34	to	to	TO	O	35	mark
35	take	take	VB	O	33	xcomp
36	place	place	NN	O	35	dobj
37	''	''	''	O	35	punct
38	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	39	punct
39	Muskal	Muskal	NNP	PERSON	35	dep
40	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	39	punct
41	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	8	advmod
2	a	a	DT	O	3	dep
3	more	more	RBR	O	8	advmod
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	depth	depth	NN	O	6	compound
6	investigation	investigation	NN	O	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	8	punct
8	revealed	reveal	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	two	two	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	men	man	NNS	O	14	nsubj
13	had	have	VBD	O	14	aux
14	taken	take	VBN	O	8	ccomp
15	part	part	NN	O	14	dobj
16	in	in	IN	O	19	case
17	a	a	DT	O	19	det
18	great	great	JJ	O	19	amod
19	deal	deal	NN	O	14	nmod
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	suspicious	suspicious	JJ	O	22	amod
22	activity	activity	NN	O	19	nmod
23	involving	involve	VBG	O	14	dep
24	travels	travels	NNS	O	23	dobj
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	money	money	NN	O	27	compound
27	transfers	transfer	NNS	O	24	conj
28	that	that	IN	O	31	mark
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	government	government	NN	O	31	nsubj
31	failed	fail	VBD	O	23	ccomp
32	to	to	TO	O	33	mark
33	pick	pick	VB	O	31	xcomp
34	up	up	RP	O	33	compound:prt
35	on	on	IN	O	33	nmod
36	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	argument	argument	NN	O	17	nsubj
3	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubjpass
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	auxpass
5	made	make	VBN	O	2	acl:relcl
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	support	support	NN	O	5	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	the	the	DT	O	7	nmod
10	repealing	repeal	VBG	O	9	amod
11	or	or	CC	O	9	cc
12	amending	amend	VBG	O	9	conj
13	of	of	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	16	compound
16	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	9	nmod
17	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	whom	whom	WP	O	21	dobj
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	government	government	NN	O	21	nsubj
21	deems	deem	VBZ	O	17	ccomp
22	a	a	DT	O	24	det
23	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	24	amod
24	group	group	NN	O	21	dobj
25	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	provision	provision	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	6	amod
6	renewal	renewal	NN	O	2	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	O	6	nmod
11	allows	allow	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	those	those	DT	O	11	dobj
13	who	who	WP	O	15	nsubjpass
14	are	be	VBP	O	15	auxpass
15	involved	involve	VBN	O	12	acl:relcl
16	in	in	IN	O	20	case
17	any	any	DT	O	20	det
18	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	20	amod
19	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	20	amod
20	activity	activity	NN	O	15	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	weather	weather	NN	O	20	appos
23	it	it	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	is	be	VBZ	O	22	acl:relcl
25	knowingly	knowingly	RB	O	24	advmod
26	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
27	unknowingly	unknowingly	RB	O	30	advmod
28	can	can	MD	O	30	aux
29	be	be	VB	O	30	auxpass
30	deported	deport	VBN	O	11	conj
31	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
32	stripped	strip	VBN	O	30	conj
33	of	of	IN	O	35	case
34	their	they	PRP$	O	35	nmod:poss
35	citizenship	citizenship	NN	O	30	nmod
36	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Suppose	suppose	VB	O	0	ROOT
3	you	you	PRP	O	9	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	9	punct
5	as	as	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	citizen	citizen	NN	O	9	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	9	punct
9	attended	attend	VBD	O	2	ccomp
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	legal	legal	JJ	O	12	amod
12	protest	protest	NN	O	9	dobj
13	for	for	IN	O	14	case
14	which	which	WDT	O	26	nmod
15	one	one	CD	NUMBER	26	nsubj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	hosts	host	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	15	punct
20	unbeknownst	unbeknownst	NN	O	15	appos
21	to	to	TO	O	22	case
22	you	you	PRP	O	20	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	15	punct
24	is	be	VBZ	O	26	cop
25	an	a	DT	O	26	det
26	organization	organization	NN	O	12	acl:relcl
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	government	government	NN	O	30	nsubj
29	has	have	VBZ	O	30	aux
30	listed	list	VBN	O	26	acl:relcl
31	as	as	IN	O	32	case
32	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Under	under	IN	O	2	case
2	Patriot	patriot	NN	O	8	nmod
3	II	ii	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	you	you	PRP	O	8	nsubjpass
6	may	may	MD	O	8	aux
7	be	be	VB	O	8	auxpass
8	deported	deport	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	no	no	RB	O	11	neg
11	longer	longer	RBR	O	12	advmod
12	deemed	deem	VBD	O	8	conj
13	an	a	DT	O	15	det
14	American	american	JJ	MISC	15	amod
15	citizen	citizen	NN	O	12	dobj
16	''	''	''	O	15	punct
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	Ramasastry	Ramasastry	NNP	PERSON	15	appos
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	p.	p.	NN	O	18	dep
21	11	11	CD	NUMBER	20	nummod
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
23	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	3	compound
3	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	5	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	signed	sign	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	back	back	RB	O	5	advmod
7	into	into	IN	O	8	case
8	effect	effect	NN	O	5	nmod
9	through	through	IN	O	12	case
10	at	at	IN	O	11	case
11	least	least	JJS	O	12	advmod
12	2015	2015	CD	DATE	5	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	May	May	NNP	DATE	5	nmod
16	of	of	IN	DATE	17	case
17	2011	2011	CD	DATE	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	``	``	``	O	5	punct
2	President	President	NNP	O	4	compound
3	Barack	Barack	NNP	PERSON	4	compound
4	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	signed	sign	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	legislation	legislation	NN	O	5	dobj
7	Thursday	Thursday	NNP	DATE	8	compound
8	evening	evening	NN	TIME	5	nmod:tmod
9	extending	extend	VBG	O	5	xcomp
10	several	several	JJ	O	12	amod
11	key	key	JJ	O	12	amod
12	provisions	provision	NNS	O	9	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	16	compound
16	Act	Act	NNP	O	12	nmod
17	''	''	''	O	12	punct
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	19	punct
19	Cohen	Cohen	NNP	PERSON	12	appos
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	19	punct
21	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	bill	bill	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
4	resurface	resurface	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	on	on	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	floor	floor	NN	O	4	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
10	this	this	DT	O	12	det
11	upcoming	upcome	VBG	O	12	amod
12	May	May	NNP	DATE	4	dobj
13	for	for	IN	O	14	case
14	renewal	renewal	NN	O	12	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	current	current	JJ	DATE	4	amod
4	threat	threat	NN	O	10	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	ISIS	ISIS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
7	growing	grow	VBG	O	6	amod
8	,	,	,	O	10	punct
9	many	many	JJ	O	10	nsubj
10	believe	believe	VBP	O	0	ROOT
11	members	member	NNS	O	18	nsubj
12	of	of	IN	O	16	case
13	the	the	DT	O	16	det
14	Islamic	islamic	JJ	MISC	16	amod
15	fundamentalist	fundamentalist	JJ	O	16	amod
16	group	group	NN	O	11	nmod
17	have	have	VBP	O	18	aux
18	found	find	VBN	O	10	ccomp
19	their	they	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	way	way	NN	O	18	dobj
21	into	into	IN	O	22	case
22	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	18	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	prompted	prompt	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	many	many	JJ	O	5	amod
5	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	lawmakers	lawmaker	NNS	O	5	conj
8	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
9	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
10	only	only	RB	O	11	advmod
11	renew	renew	VB	O	3	xcomp
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	bill	bill	NN	O	11	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	11	punct
15	but	but	CC	O	11	cc
16	further	further	RB	O	17	advmod
17	expand	expand	VB	O	11	conj
18	its	its	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	provisions	provision	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	12	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	those	those	DT	O	4	det
4	lawmakers	lawmaker	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
6	believes	believe	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
7	this	this	DT	O	6	dobj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
9	Texas	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
10	Senator	Senator	NNP	O	12	compound
11	Ted	Ted	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Cruz	Cruz	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
13	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	a	a	DT	O	4	det
3	press	press	NN	O	4	compound
4	conference	conference	NN	O	21	nmod
5	announcing	announce	VBG	O	21	csubj
6	his	he	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	intent	intent	NN	O	5	dobj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	put	put	VB	O	7	acl
10	expanded	expanded	JJ	O	11	amod
11	provisions	provision	NNS	O	9	dobj
12	in	in	IN	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	proposed	propose	VBN	O	15	amod
15	renewal	renewal	NN	O	9	nmod
16	of	of	IN	O	20	case
17	the	the	DT	O	20	det
18	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	20	compound
19	Act	Act	NNP	O	20	compound
20	Cruz	Cruz	NNP	PERSON	15	nmod
21	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	``	``	``	O	21	punct
24	If	if	IN	O	28	mark
25	we	we	PRP	O	28	nsubj
26	do	do	VBP	O	28	aux
27	not	not	RB	O	28	neg
28	pass	pass	VB	O	52	advcl
29	this	this	DT	O	30	det
30	legislation	legislation	NN	O	28	dobj
31	,	,	,	O	52	punct
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	consequence	consequence	NN	O	52	nsubj
34	will	will	MD	O	52	aux
35	be	be	VB	O	52	aux
36	that	that	IN	O	43	mark
37	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	43	nsubj
38	fighting	fight	VBG	O	37	acl
39	alongside	alongside	IN	O	40	case
40	ISIS	ISIS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	38	nmod
41	today	today	NN	DATE	38	nmod:tmod
42	may	may	MD	DATE	43	aux
43	come	come	VB	O	52	ccomp
44	home	home	NN	O	45	compound
45	tomorrow	tomorrow	NN	DATE	43	nmod:tmod
46	with	with	IN	O	49	case
47	a	a	DT	O	49	det
48	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	49	compound
49	passport	passport	NN	O	43	nmod
50	,	,	,	O	52	punct
51	may	may	MD	O	52	aux
52	come	come	VB	O	21	xcomp
53	home	home	NN	O	52	dobj
54	to	to	TO	O	56	case
55	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	56	compound
56	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	52	nmod
57	or	or	CC	O	56	cc
58	Los	Los	NNP	LOCATION	59	compound
59	Angeles	Angeles	NNP	LOCATION	56	conj
60	or	or	CC	O	59	cc
61	Houston	Houston	NNP	LOCATION	59	conj
62	or	or	CC	O	61	cc
63	Chicago	Chicago	NNP	LOCATION	61	conj
64	and	and	CC	O	52	cc
65	innocent	innocent	JJ	O	66	amod
66	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	69	nsubjpass
67	may	may	MD	O	69	aux
68	be	be	VB	O	69	auxpass
69	murdered	murder	VBN	O	52	conj
70	if	if	IN	O	75	mark
71	the	the	DT	O	72	det
72	Senate	Senate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	75	nsubj
73	does	do	VBZ	O	75	aux
74	not	not	RB	O	75	neg
75	act	act	VB	O	69	advcl
76	today	today	NN	DATE	75	nmod:tmod
77	''	''	''	O	75	punct
78	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	79	punct
79	Sherfinski	Sherfinski	NNP	PERSON	75	dep
80	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	79	punct
81	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	fact	fact	NN	O	12	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	12	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	6	compound
6	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	12	nsubj
7	are	be	VBP	O	12	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	only	only	JJ	O	11	amod
11	ones	one	NNS	O	8	nmod:npmod
12	taking	take	VBG	O	0	ROOT
13	preemptive	preemptive	JJ	O	14	amod
14	strikes	strike	NNS	O	12	dobj
15	against	against	IN	O	17	case
16	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	17	amod
17	threats	threat	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	from	from	IN	O	19	case
19	ISIS	ISIS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	European	European	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	Union	Union	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	at	at	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	proposal	proposal	NN	O	3	nmod
8	by	by	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	Kingdom	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	3	punct
13	is	be	VBZ	O	14	aux
14	drafting	draft	VBG	O	0	ROOT
15	it	it	PRP	O	18	nsubj
16	's	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
17	own	own	JJ	O	18	amod
18	version	version	NN	O	14	ccomp
19	of	of	IN	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	22	compound
22	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	18	nmod
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	ward	ward	VB	O	18	acl
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	27	amod
27	threats	threat	NNS	O	24	nmod
28	from	from	IN	O	29	case
29	ISIS	ISIS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Europe	Europe	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	counter	counter	NN	O	5	compound
4	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	5	compound
5	law	law	NN	O	6	nsubj
6	includes	include	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	language	language	NN	O	6	dobj
8	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
10	fairly	fairly	RB	O	11	advmod
11	similar	similar	JJ	O	7	acl:relcl
12	to	to	TO	O	13	case
13	that	that	DT	O	11	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
17	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	``	``	``	O	8	punct
2	The	the	DT	O	5	det
3	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
4	surveillance	surveillance	NN	O	5	compound
5	laws	law	NNS	O	8	nsubj
6	were	be	VBD	O	8	cop
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	predecessor	predecessor	NN	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	European	european	JJ	MISC	11	amod
11	legislation	legislation	NN	O	8	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Section	section	NN	O	27	nsubj
2	215	215	CD	NUMBER	1	nummod
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	6	compound
6	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	1	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	1	punct
8	which	which	WDT	O	10	nsubjpass
9	was	be	VBD	O	10	auxpass
10	passed	pass	VBN	O	1	acl:relcl
11	on	on	IN	O	12	case
12	October	October	NNP	DATE	10	nmod
13	26	26	CD	DATE	12	nummod
14	,	,	,	DATE	12	punct
15	2001	2001	CD	DATE	12	nummod
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	define	define	VB	O	10	xcomp
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	legislative	legislative	JJ	O	20	amod
20	framework	framework	NN	O	17	dobj
21	for	for	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	war	war	NN	O	17	nmod
24	on	on	IN	O	25	case
25	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	23	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	1	punct
27	established	establish	VBD	O	0	ROOT
28	that	that	IN	O	37	mark
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	collection	collection	NN	O	37	nsubjpass
31	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
32	surveillance	surveillance	NN	O	30	conj
33	of	of	IN	O	34	case
34	communications	communication	NNS	O	30	nmod
35	could	could	MD	O	37	aux
36	be	be	VB	O	37	auxpass
37	made	make	VBN	O	27	ccomp
38	for	for	IN	O	41	case
39	a	a	DT	O	41	det
40	limited	limited	JJ	O	41	amod
41	period	period	NN	O	37	nmod
42	of	of	IN	O	43	case
43	time	time	NN	O	41	nmod
44	without	without	IN	O	49	case
45	a	a	DT	O	49	det
46	warrant	warrant	NN	O	49	compound
47	or	or	CC	O	46	cc
48	court	court	NN	O	46	conj
49	order	order	NN	O	43	nmod
50	''	''	''	O	43	punct
51	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	52	punct
52	Paye	Paye	NNP	PERSON	43	appos
53	,	,	,	O	52	punct
54	p.	p.	NN	O	52	dep
55	128	128	CD	NUMBER	54	nummod
56	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	52	punct
57	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	Despite	despite	IN	O	3	case
2	its	its	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	flaws	flaw	NNS	O	10	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	10	punct
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	7	compound
7	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	10	nsubjpass
8	should	should	MD	O	10	aux
9	be	be	VB	O	10	auxpass
10	signed	sign	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	back	back	RB	O	10	advmod
12	into	into	IN	O	13	case
13	effect	effect	NN	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	9/11	9/11	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
4	attacks	attack	NNS	O	9	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	9	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	government	government	NN	O	9	nsubj
8	should	should	MD	O	9	aux
9	get	get	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	full	full	JJ	O	12	amod
12	vow	vow	NN	O	9	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	confidence	confidence	NN	O	12	nmod
15	from	from	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	American	american	JJ	MISC	18	amod
18	people	people	NNS	O	9	nmod
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	do	do	VB	O	9	advcl
21	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	23	nsubj
22	is	be	VBZ	O	23	cop
23	necessary	necessary	JJ	O	20	ccomp
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	keep	keep	VB	O	23	xcomp
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	nation	nation	NN	O	28	nsubj
28	safe	safe	JJ	O	25	xcomp
29	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	People	people	NNS	O	3	nsubj
2	often	often	RB	O	3	advmod
3	forget	forget	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
5	in	in	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	DURATION	8	det
7	immediate	immediate	JJ	DURATION	8	amod
8	years	year	NNS	DURATION	21	nsubj
9	following	follow	VBG	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	9/11	9/11	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	attacks	attack	NNS	O	8	nmod
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	strong	strong	JJ	O	15	amod
15	majority	majority	NN	O	12	dep
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	country	country	NN	O	15	nmod
19	was	be	VBD	O	21	cop
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	favor	favor	NN	O	3	ccomp
22	of	of	IN	O	27	case
23	the	the	DT	O	27	det
24	2001	2001	CD	DATE	27	nummod
25	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	27	compound
26	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	27	compound
27	Act	Act	NNP	O	21	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	as	as	IN	O	4	amod
4	time	time	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	goes	go	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	by	by	IN	O	8	case
7	our	we	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	fears	fear	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	fade	fade	VB	O	8	dep
10	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
11	we	we	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	tend	tend	VBP	O	5	conj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	forget	forget	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
16	we	we	PRP	O	19	nsubj
17	do	do	VBP	O	19	aux
18	indeed	indeed	RB	O	19	advmod
19	have	have	VB	O	14	ccomp
20	enemies	enemy	NNS	O	19	dobj
21	both	both	CC	O	23	dep
22	at	at	IN	O	23	case
23	home	home	NN	O	19	nmod
24	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
25	abroad	abroad	RB	O	23	conj
26	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	unfortunate	unfortunate	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
6	it	it	PRP	O	8	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
8	true	true	JJ	O	3	conj
9	there	there	EX	O	10	expl
10	are	be	VBP	O	8	ccomp
11	people	people	NNS	O	10	nsubj
12	out	out	IN	O	13	case
13	there	there	RB	O	11	nmod
14	with	with	IN	O	19	case
15	intent	intent	NN	O	19	amod
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	do	do	VB	O	15	xcomp
18	us	we	PRP	O	17	dobj
19	harm	harm	NN	O	11	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	2	case
2	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	12	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	12	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	last	last	JJ	O	6	amod
6	three	three	CD	NUMBER	12	nsubj
7	or	or	CC	O	6	cc
8	four	four	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
9	generations	generation	NNS	O	6	conj
10	have	have	VBP	O	12	aux
11	been	be	VBN	O	12	cop
12	lucky	lucky	JJ	O	0	ROOT
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	live	live	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	in	in	IN	O	17	case
16	this	this	DT	O	17	det
17	country	country	NN	O	14	nmod
18	for	for	IN	O	20	case
19	so	so	RB	O	20	advmod
20	long	long	RB	O	14	advcl
21	,	,	,	O	12	punct
22	without	without	IN	O	23	mark
23	having	have	VBG	O	12	advcl
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	worry	worry	VB	O	23	xcomp
26	about	about	IN	O	28	case
27	a	a	DT	O	28	det
28	war	war	NN	O	25	nmod
29	being	be	VBG	O	30	auxpass
30	fought	fight	VBN	O	28	acl
31	on	on	IN	O	33	case
32	American	american	JJ	MISC	33	amod
33	soil	soil	NN	O	30	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	4	advmod
2	as	as	IN	O	4	mark
3	ISIS	isis	NN	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubj
4	progresses	progress	VBZ	O	18	advcl
5	into	into	IN	O	7	case
6	western	western	JJ	O	7	amod
7	nations	nation	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	such	such	JJ	O	11	case
10	as	as	IN	O	9	mwe
11	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	18	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	proper	proper	JJ	O	15	amod
15	precautions	precaution	NNS	O	18	nsubjpass
16	must	must	MD	O	18	aux
17	be	be	VB	O	18	auxpass
18	taken	take	VBN	O	0	ROOT
19	in	in	IN	O	20	mark
20	making	make	VBG	O	18	advcl
21	sure	sure	JJ	O	20	xcomp
22	that	that	IN	O	30	mark
23	all	all	DT	O	25	det
24	future	future	JJ	DATE	25	amod
25	generations	generation	NNS	O	30	nsubj
26	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
27	come	come	VB	O	25	acl
28	will	will	MD	O	30	aux
29	never	never	RB	O	30	neg
30	see	see	VB	O	20	ccomp
31	a	a	DT	O	32	det
32	war	war	NN	O	33	nsubj
33	fought	fight	VBD	O	30	ccomp
34	on	on	IN	O	36	case
35	American	american	JJ	MISC	36	amod
36	soil	soil	NN	O	33	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	Attorney	Attorney	NNP	O	4	compound
4	General	General	NNP	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	RFK	RFK	NNP	LOCATION	7	nsubj
7	granted	grant	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	wiretaps	wiretap	NNS	O	7	iobj
9	himself	himself	PRP	O	7	dobj
10	on	on	IN	O	11	case
11	those	those	DT	O	7	nmod
12	suspected	suspect	VBN	O	11	acl
13	of	of	IN	O	15	mark
14	being	be	VBG	O	15	auxpass
15	involved	involve	VBN	O	12	advcl
16	in	in	IN	O	17	mark
17	organize	organize	VB	O	15	advcl
18	crime	crime	NN	O	17	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	war	war	NN	O	14	nsubj
3	on	on	IN	O	4	case
4	terror	terror	NN	O	2	nmod
5	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	war	war	NN	O	2	conj
8	on	on	IN	O	10	case
9	organized	organized	JJ	O	10	amod
10	crime	crime	NN	O	7	nmod
11	are	be	VBP	O	14	cop
12	certainly	certainly	RB	O	14	advmod
13	very	very	RB	O	14	advmod
14	different	different	JJ	O	0	ROOT
15	from	from	IN	O	17	case
16	each	each	DT	O	17	det
17	other	other	JJ	O	14	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	14	punct
19	however	however	RB	O	21	advmod
20	there	there	EX	O	21	expl
21	is	be	VBZ	O	14	parataxis
22	one	one	CD	NUMBER	23	nummod
23	way	way	NN	O	21	nsubj
24	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
25	they	they	PRP	O	27	nsubj
26	are	be	VBP	O	27	cop
27	similar	similar	JJ	O	23	dep
28	,	,	,	O	23	punct
29	in	in	IN	O	30	case
30	which	which	WDT	O	34	nmod
31	we	we	PRP	O	34	nsubj
32	do	do	VBP	O	34	aux
33	n't	not	RB	O	34	neg
34	know	know	VB	O	23	acl:relcl
35	who	who	WP	O	38	dobj
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	enemy	enemy	NN	O	38	nsubj
38	is	be	VBZ	O	34	ccomp
39	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	DATE	3	det
3	past	past	NN	DATE	17	nmod
4	when	when	WRB	O	9	advmod
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	7	compound
7	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	9	nsubj
8	has	have	VBZ	O	9	aux
9	fought	fight	VBN	O	3	acl:relcl
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	wars	war	NNS	O	9	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	17	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	enemy	enemy	NN	O	17	nsubj
15	was	be	VBD	O	17	cop
16	always	always	RB	O	17	advmod
17	clear-cut	clear-cut	JJ	O	0	ROOT
18	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	American	american	JJ	ORGANIZATION	3	amod
3	Army	Army	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	aux
5	fighting	fight	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	against	against	IN	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	British	british	JJ	ORGANIZATION	9	amod
9	Army	Army	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	The	the	DT	O	13	det
12	German	german	JJ	ORGANIZATION	13	amod
13	Army	Army	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	conj
14	,	,	,	O	9	punct
15	or	or	CC	O	9	cc
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	Korean	korean	JJ	ORGANIZATION	18	amod
18	Army	Army	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	conj
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	cop
3	war	war	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	between	between	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	militaries	military	NNS	O	3	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	nations	nation	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
11	its	its	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	people	people	NNS	O	8	appos
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	's	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	sad	sad	JJ	O	5	amod
5	fact	fact	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
7	American	american	JJ	MISC	8	amod
8	civilians	civilian	NNS	O	10	nsubjpass
9	are	be	VBP	O	10	auxpass
10	put	put	VBN	O	5	ccomp
11	at	at	IN	O	12	case
12	risk	risk	NN	O	10	nmod
13	as	as	IN	O	18	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	war	war	NN	O	18	nsubj
16	on	on	IN	O	17	case
17	terror	terror	NN	O	15	nmod
18	continues	continue	VBZ	O	10	advcl
19	,	,	,	O	5	punct
20	but	but	CC	O	5	cc
21	we	we	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	have	have	VBP	O	5	conj
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	means	means	NNS	O	22	dobj
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	do	do	VB	O	22	ccomp
27	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	29	dobj
28	it	it	PRP	O	29	nsubj
29	is	be	VBZ	O	26	ccomp
30	to	to	TO	O	31	mark
31	keep	keep	VB	O	29	xcomp
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	American	american	JJ	MISC	34	amod
34	people	people	NNS	O	35	nsubj
35	safe	safe	JJ	O	31	xcomp
36	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	3	mark
2	that	that	DT	O	3	nsubj
3	includes	include	VBZ	O	19	csubj
4	leaving	leave	VBG	O	3	xcomp
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	option	option	NN	O	4	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	government	government	NN	O	6	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	tap	tap	VB	O	9	acl
12	into	into	IN	O	16	case
13	e-mail	e-mail	NN	O	16	compound
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	phone	phone	NN	O	13	conj
16	records	record	NNS	O	11	nmod
17	so	so	RB	O	11	advmod
18	be	be	VB	O	19	cop
19	it	it	PRP	O	0	ROOT
20	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	majority	majority	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	2	nmod
5	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
6	nothing	nothing	NN	O	5	advmod
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	hide	hide	VB	O	5	xcomp
9	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	country	country	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	can	can	MD	O	13	aux
13	feel	feel	VB	O	5	conj
14	safer	safer	JJR	O	13	xcomp
15	knowing	know	VBG	O	13	xcomp
16	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	government	government	NN	O	19	nsubj
19	has	have	VBZ	O	15	ccomp
20	eyes	eye	NNS	O	19	dobj
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	ears	ear	NNS	O	20	conj
23	on	on	IN	O	24	case
24	those	those	DT	O	20	nmod
25	who	who	WP	O	27	nsubj
26	do	do	VBP	O	27	aux
27	have	have	VB	O	24	acl:relcl
28	something	something	NN	O	27	dobj
29	to	to	TO	O	30	mark
30	hide	hide	VB	O	27	advcl
31	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	American	american	JJ	MISC	3	amod
3	people	people	NNS	O	6	nsubj
4	are	be	VBP	O	6	cop
5	surely	surely	RB	O	6	advmod
6	better	better	JJR	O	0	ROOT
7	off	off	RP	O	6	dep
8	safe	safe	JJ	O	6	advmod
9	than	than	IN	O	10	case
10	sorry	sorry	JJ	O	8	advcl
11	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
2	will	will	MD	O	3	aux
3	continue	continue	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	debate	debate	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	reauthorization	reauthorization	NN	O	5	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Act	Act	NNP	O	7	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	DATE	15	det
14	coming	coming	JJ	DATE	15	amod
15	year	year	NN	DATE	5	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Regardless	regardless	RB	O	13	advmod
2	of	of	IN	O	3	case
3	methods	method	NNS	O	1	nmod
4	or	or	CC	O	3	cc
5	tactics	tactic	NNS	O	3	conj
6	,	,	,	O	13	punct
7	at	at	IN	O	9	case
8	its	its	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	heart	heart	NN	O	13	nmod
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	12	compound
12	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	13	nsubj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
14	only	only	RB	O	13	advmod
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	trying	try	VBG	O	14	advcl
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	keep	keep	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	20	nsubj
20	safe	safe	JJ	O	18	xcomp
21	.	.	.	O	13	punct

