1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	2001	2001	CD	DATE	25	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	25	punct
4	as	as	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	measure	measure	NN	O	25	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	security	security	NN	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	safety	safety	NN	O	8	conj
11	following	follow	VBG	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	9/11	9/11	CD	NUMBER	14	nummod
14	attacks	attack	NNS	O	6	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	25	punct
16	President	President	NNP	O	17	compound
17	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
18	with	with	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	approval	approval	NN	O	17	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	107th	107th	JJ	ORGANIZATION	24	amod
24	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	nmod
25	passed	pass	VBD	O	0	ROOT
26	the	the	DT	O	30	det
27	2001	2001	CD	DATE	30	nummod
28	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	30	compound
29	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	30	compound
30	ACT	ACT	NNP	O	25	dobj
31	.	.	.	O	25	punct

1	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	3	compound
2	PATRIOT	PATRIOT	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Act	Act	NNP	O	6	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
5	an	a	DT	O	6	det
6	acronym	acronym	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	11	case
8	Uniting	Uniting	NNP	O	11	compound
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	Strengthening	Strengthening	NNP	LOCATION	8	conj
11	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
12	by	by	IN	O	16	case
13	Providing	Providing	NNP	O	16	compound
14	Appropriate	Appropriate	NNP	O	16	compound
15	Tools	Tools	NNP	O	16	compound
16	Required	Required	NNP	O	11	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	Intercept	intercept	VB	O	6	acl
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	Obstruct	obstruct	VB	O	18	conj
21	Terrorism	Terrorism	NNP	O	18	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	6	punct
23	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
24	it	it	PRP	O	27	nsubjpass
25	is	be	VBZ	O	27	auxpass
26	better	better	RB	O	27	advmod
27	known	know	VBN	O	6	conj
28	as	as	IN	O	30	case
29	simply	simply	RB	O	30	advmod
30	the	the	DT	O	27	nmod
31	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	32	compound
32	Act	Act	NNP	O	30	dep
33	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	7	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	purpose	purpose	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	act	act	NN	O	3	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	28	csubj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	intercept	intercept	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	counter	counter	VB	O	9	conj
12	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	13	amod
13	threats	threat	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	both	both	CC	O	15	cc:preconj
15	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	13	amod
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	15	conj
18	,	,	,	O	13	punct
19	its	its	PRP$	O	13	appos
20	'	'	''	O	11	punct
21	legality	legality	NN	O	11	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	effectiveness	effectiveness	NN	O	21	conj
24	,	,	,	O	21	punct
25	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
26	use	use	NN	O	21	conj
27	has	have	VBZ	O	28	aux
28	become	become	VBN	O	0	ROOT
29	a	a	DT	O	32	det
30	heavy	heavy	JJ	O	32	amod
31	debate	debate	NN	O	32	compound
32	topic	topic	NN	O	28	xcomp
33	among	among	IN	O	34	case
34	members	member	NNS	O	28	nmod
35	of	of	IN	O	36	case
36	congress	congress	NN	O	34	nmod
37	and	and	CC	O	36	cc
38	the	the	DT	O	40	det
39	American	american	JJ	MISC	40	amod
40	people	people	NNS	O	36	conj
41	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	people	people	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	believe	believe	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	Patriot	patriot	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	Acts	act	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
8	provisions	provision	NNS	O	21	nsubj
9	allowing	allow	VBG	O	8	acl
10	unwarranted	unwarranted	JJ	O	11	amod
11	wire	wire	NN	O	9	dobj
12	tapping	tap	VBG	O	11	acl
13	on	on	IN	O	14	case
14	its	its	PRP$	O	12	nmod
15	'	'	''	O	12	punct
16	own	own	JJ	O	17	amod
17	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	12	dobj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	21	cop
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	direct	direct	JJ	O	21	amod
21	violation	violation	NN	O	7	ccomp
22	of	of	IN	O	27	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	American	american	JJ	MISC	25	amod
25	people	people	NNS	O	27	nmod:poss
26	's	's	POS	O	25	case
27	privacy	privacy	NN	O	21	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
29	freedoms	freedom	NNS	O	27	conj
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Other	other	JJ	O	2	nsubj
2	argue	argue	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	6	compound
6	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	10	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	10	amod
10	line	line	NN	O	2	ccomp
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	defense	defense	NN	O	10	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	14	mark
14	keeping	keep	VBG	O	12	acl
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	American	american	JJ	MISC	17	amod
17	people	people	NNS	O	14	dobj
18	safe	safe	JJ	O	17	amod
19	from	from	IN	O	20	case
20	attacks	attack	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	committed	commit	VBN	O	20	acl
22	by	by	IN	O	23	case
23	terrorists	terrorist	NNS	O	21	nmod
24	both	both	CC	O	23	dep
25	at	at	IN	O	26	case
26	home	home	NN	O	23	conj
27	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
28	abroad	abroad	RB	O	18	advmod
29	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	controversial	controversial	JJ	O	3	amod
3	nature	nature	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	this	this	DT	O	6	det
6	issue	issue	NN	O	3	nmod
7	has	have	VBZ	O	8	aux
8	garnered	garner	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	heavy	heavy	JJ	O	11	amod
10	rhetorical	rhetorical	JJ	O	11	amod
11	argument	argument	NN	O	8	dobj
12	on	on	IN	O	14	case
13	both	both	DT	O	14	det
14	sides	side	NNS	O	8	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	issue	issue	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	writer	writer	NN	O	13	nsubj
3	who	who	WP	O	4	nsubj
4	wrote	write	VBD	O	2	ccomp
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	favor	favor	NN	O	4	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	6	nmod
11	was	be	VBD	O	13	cop
12	Terrence	Terrence	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Jeffery	Jeffery	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	both	both	DT	O	4	cc:preconj
4	logos	logo	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	pathos	pathos	NNS	O	4	conj
7	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
8	effectively	effectively	RB	O	9	advmod
9	get	get	VB	O	2	xcomp
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	message	message	NN	O	9	dobj
12	across	across	IN	O	15	case
13	to	to	TO	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	reader	reader	NN	O	9	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	his	he	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	article	article	NN	O	15	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	22	case
20	Human	human	JJ	O	22	amod
21	Events	event	NNS	O	22	compound
22	Magazine	magazine	NN	O	9	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	logos	logo	NNS	O	2	dobj
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	description	description	NN	O	3	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	13	mark
8	how	how	WRB	O	13	advmod
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	11	compound
11	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	13	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	13	cop
13	effective	effective	JJ	O	6	acl
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	a	a	DT	O	13	nmod
16	preventing	prevent	VBG	O	15	acl
17	a	a	DT	O	20	det
18	potential	potential	JJ	O	20	amod
19	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	20	amod
20	plot	plot	NN	O	16	dobj
21	in	in	IN	O	22	case
22	2002	2002	CD	DATE	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	2	advmod
2	discussing	discuss	VBG	O	17	advcl
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	failed	fail	VBN	O	6	amod
5	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	6	amod
6	attempt	attempt	NN	O	2	dobj
7	an	a	DT	O	9	det
8	American	american	JJ	MISC	9	amod
9	citizen	citizen	NN	O	17	nsubj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
12	Leon	Leon	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Battle	Battle	NNP	PERSON	9	appos
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	Terrence	Terrence	NNP	PERSON	16	compound
16	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	13	appos
17	writes	write	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	about	about	IN	O	25	mark
19	how	how	WRB	O	25	advmod
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	22	compound
22	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	24	nmod:poss
23	's	's	POS	O	22	case
24	provisions	provision	NNS	O	25	nsubj
25	allowed	allow	VBD	O	17	advcl
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	government	government	NN	O	25	dobj
28	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
29	monitor	monitor	VB	O	25	xcomp
30	Battle	battle	NN	O	29	dobj
31	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
32	recorded	record	VBD	O	25	conj
33	a	a	DT	O	34	dep
34	an	a	DT	O	32	dobj
35	incriminating	incriminate	VBG	O	32	xcomp
36	conversation	conversation	NN	O	35	dobj
37	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	describes	describe	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	conversation	conversation	NN	O	2	dobj
5	in	in	IN	O	7	case
6	his	he	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	articles	article	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
9	he	he	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	writes	write	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	``	``	``	O	10	punct
13	He	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	explained	explain	VBD	O	10	ccomp
15	to	to	TO	O	17	case
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	friend	friend	NN	O	14	nmod
18	how	how	WRB	O	30	advmod
19	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
20	`	`	``	O	22	punct
21	burning	burn	VBG	O	22	amod
22	desire	desire	NN	O	30	nsubj
23	'	'	''	O	22	punct
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	become	become	VB	O	22	acl
26	an	a	DT	O	28	det
27	Islamic	islamic	JJ	MISC	28	amod
28	martyr	martyr	NN	O	25	xcomp
29	had	have	VBD	O	30	aux
30	inspired	inspire	VBN	O	14	ccomp
31	his	he	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
32	aborted	aborted	JJ	O	33	amod
33	quest	quest	NN	O	30	dobj
34	to	to	TO	O	35	mark
35	join	join	VB	O	30	advcl
36	forces	force	NNS	O	35	dobj
37	with	with	IN	O	39	case
38	al	al	NNP	ORGANIZATION	39	compound
39	Qaeda	Qaeda	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	nmod
40	in	in	IN	O	41	case
41	Afghanistan	Afghanistan	NNP	LOCATION	39	nmod
42	,	,	,	O	35	punct
43	where	where	WRB	O	46	advmod
44	he	he	PRP	O	46	nsubj
45	could	could	MD	O	46	aux
46	kill	kill	VB	O	35	advcl
47	American	american	JJ	MISC	48	amod
48	troops	troops	NNS	O	46	dobj
49	.	.	.	O	2	punct
50	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	goes	go	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	on	on	IN	O	3	compound:prt
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	say	say	VB	O	3	xcomp
7	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
8	Battle	battle	NN	PERSON	10	nsubj
9	was	be	VBD	O	10	aux
10	arrested	arrest	VBN	O	6	ccomp
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	tried	try	VBD	O	10	dep
13	,	,	,	O	10	punct
14	convicted	convict	VBN	O	10	dep
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
17	sentenced	sentence	VBN	O	14	conj
18	to	to	TO	O	20	case
19	18	18	CD	DURATION	20	nummod
20	years	year	NNS	DURATION	17	nmod
21	in	in	IN	O	22	case
22	prison	prison	NN	O	20	nmod
23	for	for	IN	O	24	mark
24	attempting	attempt	VBG	O	17	advcl
25	to	to	TO	O	27	case
26	wage	wage	NN	O	27	compound
27	war	war	NN	O	24	nmod
28	on	on	IN	O	31	case
29	the	the	DT	O	31	det
30	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	31	compound
31	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	27	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct

1	Terrence	Terrence	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	successfully	successfully	RB	O	4	advmod
4	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	logos	logo	NNS	O	4	dobj
6	because	because	IN	O	8	mark
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	raises	raise	VBZ	O	4	advcl
9	a	a	DT	O	12	det
10	thoroughly	thoroughly	RB	O	11	advmod
11	logical	logical	JJ	O	12	amod
12	statement	statement	NN	O	8	dobj
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	support	support	NN	O	12	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	18	compound
18	Act	Act	NNP	O	14	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Pathos	pathos	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	auxpass
3	also	also	RB	O	4	advmod
4	evoked	evoke	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	in	in	IN	O	9	case
6	Terrence	Terrence	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	9	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	article	article	NN	O	4	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	which	which	WDT	O	13	nmod
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	defends	defend	VBZ	O	9	acl:relcl
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	16	compound
16	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	13	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	pathos	pathos	NNS	O	2	dobj
4	by	by	IN	O	5	mark
5	explaining	explain	VBG	O	2	advcl
6	to	to	TO	O	8	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	audience	audience	NN	O	5	nmod
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	frightening	frightening	JJ	O	11	amod
11	reality	reality	NN	O	5	dobj
12	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
13	there	there	EX	O	14	expl
14	are	be	VBP	O	11	dep
15	people	people	NNS	O	14	nsubj
16	out	out	IN	O	17	case
17	there	there	RB	O	14	advmod
18	,	,	,	O	14	punct
19	in	in	IN	O	22	case
20	our	we	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
21	own	own	JJ	O	22	amod
22	country	country	NN	O	14	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	who	who	WP	O	25	nsubj
25	want	want	VBP	O	22	acl:relcl
26	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
27	do	do	VB	O	25	xcomp
28	us	we	PRP	O	27	iobj
29	harm	harm	NN	O	27	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	certainly	certainly	RB	O	3	advmod
3	evokes	evoke	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	fear	fear	NN	O	3	dobj
5	in	in	IN	O	7	case
6	his	he	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	audience	audience	NN	O	3	nmod
8	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
9	he	he	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	writes	write	VBZ	O	3	advcl
11	about	about	IN	O	19	mark
12	how	how	WRB	O	19	advmod
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	case	case	NN	O	19	nsubj
15	with	with	IN	O	18	case
16	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
17	Leon	Leon	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
18	Battle	Battle	NNP	PERSON	14	nmod
19	took	take	VBD	O	10	advcl
20	place	place	NN	O	19	dobj
21	in	in	IN	O	24	case
22	Portland	Portland	NNP	LOCATION	24	compound
23	,	,	,	O	24	punct
24	Oregon	Oregon	NNP	LOCATION	19	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	all	all	DT	O	27	det
27	places	place	NNS	O	24	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	writes	write	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	``	``	``	O	2	punct
5	After	after	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	9/11	9/11	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
8	attacks	attack	NNS	O	21	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	21	punct
10	however	however	RB	O	21	advmod
11	,	,	,	O	21	punct
12	Battle	battle	NN	PERSON	21	nsubj
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	five	five	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
15	other	other	JJ	O	16	amod
16	members	member	NNS	O	12	conj
17	of	of	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	Portland	Portland	NNP	LOCATION	20	compound
20	ring	ring	NN	O	16	nmod
21	decided	decide	VBD	O	2	parataxis
22	that	that	IN	O	31	mark
23	rather	rather	RB	O	25	advmod
24	than	than	IN	O	25	case
25	attack	attack	NN	O	31	advcl
26	inside	inside	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	25	nmod
29	they	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
30	would	would	MD	O	31	aux
31	travel	travel	VB	O	21	ccomp
32	via	via	IN	O	33	case
33	China	China	NNP	LOCATION	31	nmod
34	and	and	CC	O	33	cc
35	Pakistan	Pakistan	NNP	LOCATION	33	conj
36	to	to	TO	O	37	case
37	Afghanistan	Afghanistan	NNP	LOCATION	31	nmod
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	join	join	VB	O	31	xcomp
40	forces	force	NNS	O	39	dobj
41	with	with	IN	O	43	case
42	al	al	NNP	O	43	compound
43	Qaeda	Qaeda	NNP	O	39	nmod
44	there	there	RB	O	39	advmod
45	.	.	.	O	2	punct
46	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	scary	scary	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	knowing	know	VBG	O	3	xcomp
5	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
6	people	people	NNS	O	17	nsubj
7	in	in	IN	O	10	case
8	our	we	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	own	own	JJ	O	10	amod
10	country	country	NN	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	states	state	NNS	O	10	conj
13	,	,	,	O	10	punct
14	or	or	CC	O	10	cc
15	cities	city	NNS	O	10	conj
16	could	could	MD	O	17	aux
17	hurt	hurt	VB	O	4	ccomp
18	us	we	PRP	O	17	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Terrence	Terrence	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Jeffrey	Jeffrey	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	an	a	DT	O	6	det
5	excellent	excellent	JJ	O	6	amod
6	job	job	NN	O	3	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	mark
8	getting	get	VBG	O	6	acl
9	that	that	DT	O	10	det
10	point	point	NN	O	8	dobj
11	across	across	IN	O	14	case
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	audience	audience	NN	O	8	nmod
15	with	with	IN	O	18	case
16	his	he	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
17	powerful	powerful	JJ	O	18	amod
18	use	use	NN	O	14	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	pathos	pathos	NN	O	18	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
2	rhetorical	rhetorical	JJ	O	3	amod
3	argument	argument	NN	O	13	nsubj
4	published	publish	VBN	O	3	acl
5	that	that	DT	O	10	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
7	against	against	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	O	4	ccomp
11	was	be	VBD	O	13	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	speech	speech	NN	O	0	ROOT
14	made	make	VBN	O	13	acl
15	by	by	IN	O	18	case
16	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	18	compound
17	Bob	Bob	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
18	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	14	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	a	a	DT	O	21	det
21	Democrat	Democrat	NNP	MISC	18	appos
22	from	from	IN	O	23	case
23	Georgia	Georgia	NNP	LOCATION	21	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	18	punct
25	on	on	IN	O	27	case
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	floor	floor	NN	O	14	nmod
28	of	of	IN	O	29	case
29	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	2008	2008	CD	DATE	6	nmod
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Act	Act	NNP	O	6	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	up	up	RB	O	6	advmod
8	for	for	IN	O	9	case
9	renewal	renewal	NN	O	7	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
4	one	one	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	many	many	JJ	O	8	amod
8	politicians	politician	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	who	who	WP	O	12	nsubj
10	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	favor	favor	NN	O	8	acl:relcl
13	of	of	IN	O	14	mark
14	voting	vote	VBG	O	12	acl
15	against	against	IN	O	16	case
16	renewal	renewal	NN	O	14	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
18	allowing	allow	VBG	O	14	conj
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	provisions	provision	NNS	O	18	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	24	compound
24	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	20	nmod
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	sunset	sunset	VB	O	18	xcomp
27	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	powerful	powerful	JJ	O	5	amod
5	argument	argument	NN	O	2	dobj
6	on	on	IN	O	14	mark
7	why	why	WRB	O	14	advmod
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	14	nsubjpass
11	should	should	MD	O	14	aux
12	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
13	be	be	VB	O	14	auxpass
14	renewed	renew	VBN	O	5	acl
15	,	,	,	O	5	punct
16	effectively	effectively	RB	O	17	advmod
17	incorporating	incorporate	VBG	O	5	acl
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	rhetorical	rhetorical	JJ	O	20	amod
20	strategies	strategy	NNS	O	17	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	logos	logo	NNS	O	20	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	ethos	ethos	NN	O	22	conj
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	use	use	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	logos	logo	NNS	O	2	nmod
5	lies	lie	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	heavily	heavily	RB	O	5	advmod
7	in	in	IN	O	9	mark
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nsubj
9	citing	cite	VBG	O	5	advcl
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	straight	straight	JJ	O	12	amod
12	facts	fact	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	statistics	statistics	NNS	O	12	conj
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	2	case
2	instance	instance	NN	O	23	nmod
3	when	when	WRB	O	4	advmod
4	discussing	discuss	VBG	O	2	acl:relcl
5	how	how	WRB	O	12	advmod
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nsubj
8	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	9	case
9	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
10	has	have	VBZ	O	12	aux
11	been	be	VBN	O	12	aux
12	taking	take	VBG	O	4	ccomp
13	advantage	advantage	NN	O	12	dobj
14	of	of	IN	O	18	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	law	law	NN	O	18	nmod:poss
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	provision	provision	NN	O	13	nmod
19	allowing	allow	VBG	O	18	dep
20	unwarranted	unwarranted	JJ	O	21	amod
21	wiretaps	wiretap	NNS	O	19	dobj
22	he	he	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
24	,	,	,	O	23	punct
25	``	``	``	O	23	punct
26	The	the	DT	O	27	det
27	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	nsubj
28	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	29	case
29	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	nmod
30	requested	request	VBD	O	23	ccomp
31	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
32	won	win	VBD	O	30	conj
33	approval	approval	NN	O	30	dobj
34	of	of	IN	O	36	case
35	1,754	1,754	CD	NUMBER	36	nummod
36	wiretaps	wiretap	NNS	O	33	nmod
37	in	in	IN	O	38	case
38	2004	2004	CD	DATE	36	nmod
39	,	,	,	O	33	punct
40	following	follow	VBG	O	41	case
41	1,724	1,724	CD	NUMBER	33	nmod
42	granted	grant	VBN	O	41	acl
43	requests	request	NNS	O	42	dobj
44	in	in	IN	O	45	case
45	2003	2003	CD	DATE	43	nmod
46	''	''	''	O	23	punct
47	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	48	punct
48	Barr	barr	NN	O	23	dep
49	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	48	punct
50	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	cites	cite	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	specific	specific	JJ	O	6	amod
6	example	example	NN	O	3	dobj
7	when	when	WRB	O	11	advmod
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	11	nsubj
11	failed	fail	VBD	O	6	acl:relcl
12	,	,	,	O	3	punct
13	when	when	WRB	O	25	advmod
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	2008	2008	CD	DATE	25	nmod
16	Brandon	Brandon	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Mayfield	Mayfield	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubjpass
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	an	a	DT	O	21	det
20	Oregon	Oregon	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
21	lawyer	lawyer	NN	O	17	appos
22	,	,	,	O	17	punct
23	was	be	VBD	O	25	auxpass
24	wrongfully	wrongfully	RB	O	25	advmod
25	made	make	VBN	O	3	advcl
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	lead	lead	NN	O	28	compound
28	suspect	suspect	NN	O	25	dobj
29	in	in	IN	O	32	case
30	the	the	DT	O	32	det
31	Madrid	Madrid	NNP	LOCATION	32	compound
32	bombings	bombing	NNS	O	25	nmod
33	because	because	IN	O	35	mark
34	he	he	PRP	O	35	nsubj
35	had	have	VBD	O	25	advcl
36	the	the	DT	O	38	det
37	same	same	JJ	O	38	amod
38	name	name	NN	O	35	dobj
39	as	as	IN	O	41	case
40	a	a	DT	O	41	det
41	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	38	nmod
42	based	base	VBN	O	41	acl
43	Islamic	islamic	JJ	MISC	45	amod
44	fundamentalist	fundamentalist	JJ	O	45	amod
45	leader	leader	NN	O	42	dobj
46	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	goes	go	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	even	even	RB	O	5	advmod
5	further	further	JJ	O	3	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	discuss	discuss	VB	O	3	advcl
8	how	how	WRB	O	14	advmod
9	Mayfield	Mayfield	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	home	home	NN	O	14	nsubjpass
12	was	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
13	extensively	extensively	RB	O	14	advmod
14	searched	search	VBN	O	7	ccomp
15	without	without	IN	O	17	case
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	warrant	warrant	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	describes	describe	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	situation	situation	NN	O	3	dobj
6	when	when	WRB	O	8	advmod
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	says	say	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	``	``	``	O	8	punct
11	The	the	DT	O	13	det
12	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nsubj
14	acknowledged	acknowledge	VBD	O	8	ccomp
15	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
16	during	during	IN	O	19	case
17	a	a	DT	O	19	det
18	covert	covert	JJ	O	19	amod
19	search	search	NN	O	25	nmod
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	home	home	NN	O	19	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	25	punct
24	agents	agent	NNS	O	25	nsubj
25	copied	copy	VBD	O	14	ccomp
26	computer	computer	NN	O	29	compound
27	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
28	paper	paper	NN	O	26	conj
29	files	file	NNS	O	25	dobj
30	,	,	,	O	25	punct
31	took	take	VBD	O	25	dep
32	355	355	CD	NUMBER	34	nummod
33	digital	digital	JJ	O	34	amod
34	photographs	photograph	NNS	O	31	dobj
35	,	,	,	O	25	punct
36	seized	seize	VBD	O	25	dep
37	six	six	CD	NUMBER	39	nummod
38	cigarette	cigarette	NN	O	39	compound
39	butts	butt	NNS	O	36	dobj
40	for	for	IN	O	42	case
41	DNA	dna	NN	MISC	42	compound
42	analysis	analysis	NN	O	36	nmod
43	,	,	,	O	36	punct
44	and	and	CC	O	36	cc
45	used	use	VBN	O	36	conj
46	cotton	cotton	NN	O	47	compound
47	swabs	swab	NNS	O	45	dobj
48	to	to	TO	O	49	mark
49	obtain	obtain	VB	O	45	advcl
50	other	other	JJ	O	52	amod
51	DNA	dna	NN	O	52	compound
52	evidence	evidence	NN	O	49	dobj
53	''	''	''	O	8	punct
54	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	55	punct
55	Barr	Barr	NNP	O	8	dep
56	.	.	.	O	55	punct
57	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	55	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	2	neg
2	only	only	RB	O	6	dep
3	does	do	VBZ	O	6	aux
4	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	evoke	evoke	VB	O	16	dep
7	strong	strong	JJ	O	8	amod
8	arguments	argument	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	based	base	VBN	O	11	case
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	logos	logo	NNS	O	6	advcl
12	,	,	,	O	16	punct
13	he	he	PRP	O	16	nsubj
14	also	also	RB	O	16	advmod
15	powerfully	powerfully	RB	O	16	advmod
16	demonstrates	demonstrate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	use	use	NN	O	16	dobj
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	ethos	ethos	NN	O	18	nmod
21	in	in	IN	O	23	case
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	discussion	discussion	NN	O	20	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	ethics	ethic	NNS	O	23	nmod
27	of	of	IN	O	30	case
28	the	the	DT	O	30	det
29	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	30	compound
30	Act	Act	NNP	O	26	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Barr	Barr	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	in	in	IN	O	5	case
5	depth	depth	NN	O	3	nmod
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	dangers	danger	NNS	O	3	dobj
8	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Act	Act	NNP	O	12	nsubj
12	poses	pose	VBZ	O	7	dep
13	to	to	TO	O	16	case
14	our	we	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	Constitutional	Constitutional	NNP	O	16	compound
16	freedoms	freedom	NNS	O	12	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	notes	note	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Constitutional	Constitutional	NNP	O	6	compound
6	freedoms	freedom	NNS	O	19	nsubjpass
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	speech	speech	NN	O	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	assembly	assembly	NN	O	8	conj
11	,	,	,	O	8	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
13	protection	protection	NN	O	8	conj
14	from	from	IN	O	16	case
15	warrantless	warrantless	JJ	O	16	amod
16	searches	search	NNS	O	8	nmod
17	are	be	VBP	O	19	auxpass
18	all	all	DT	O	19	advmod
19	threatened	threaten	VBN	O	2	ccomp
20	by	by	IN	O	21	case
21	provisions	provision	NNS	O	19	nmod
22	under	under	IN	O	25	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	25	compound
25	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	21	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Barr	barr	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	closes	close	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	his	he	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	speech	speech	NN	O	2	dobj
5	by	by	IN	O	6	mark
6	saying	say	VBG	O	2	advcl
7	,	,	,	O	2	punct
8	``	``	``	O	2	punct
9	In	in	IN	O	21	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	name	name	NN	O	21	nsubj
12	of	of	IN	O	13	mark
13	fighting	fight	VBG	O	11	acl
14	``	``	``	O	15	punct
15	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	13	dobj
16	''	''	''	O	15	punct
17	or	or	CC	O	15	cc
18	any	any	DT	O	20	det
19	other	other	JJ	O	20	amod
20	threat	threat	NN	O	15	conj
21	posed	pose	VBD	O	33	advcl
22	to	to	TO	O	25	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	good	good	JJ	O	25	amod
25	order	order	NN	O	21	nmod
26	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
27	safety	safety	NN	O	25	conj
28	of	of	IN	O	30	case
29	our	we	PRP$	O	30	nmod:poss
30	society	society	NN	O	25	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	33	punct
32	we	we	PRP	O	33	nsubj
33	show	show	VBP	O	2	dep
34	disdain	disdain	NN	O	33	dobj
35	for	for	IN	O	38	case
36	the	the	DT	O	38	det
37	fundamental	fundamental	JJ	O	38	amod
38	underpinning	underpinning	NN	O	34	nmod
39	of	of	IN	O	42	case
40	our	we	PRP$	O	42	nmod:poss
41	constitutional	constitutional	JJ	O	42	amod
42	form	form	NN	O	38	nmod
43	of	of	IN	O	44	case
44	government	government	NN	O	42	nmod
45	and	and	CC	O	38	cc
46	the	the	DT	O	47	det
47	freedoms	freedom	NNS	O	38	conj
48	it	it	PRP	O	49	nsubj
49	enshrines	enshrine	VBZ	O	47	acl:relcl
50	''	''	''	O	2	punct
51	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	52	punct
52	Barr	barr	NN	O	2	dep
53	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	52	punct
54	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	13	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	6	case
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	most	most	RBS	O	5	advmod
5	passionate	passionate	JJ	O	6	amod
6	opponents	opponent	NNS	O	1	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	6	nmod
11	is	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
12	Anita	Anita	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Ramasastry	Ramasastry	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	zealous	zealous	JJ	O	5	amod
5	argument	argument	NN	O	2	dobj
6	against	against	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	renewal	renewal	NN	O	5	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	12	compound
12	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	8	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	her	she	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	articles	article	NNS	O	5	nmod
16	published	publish	VBN	O	15	acl
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	Knowledge	Knowledge	NNP	O	16	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	Technology	Technology	NNP	O	18	conj
21	,	,	,	O	18	punct
22	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
23	Policy	policy	NN	O	18	conj
24	,	,	,	O	5	punct
25	``	``	``	O	5	punct
26	Patriot	patriot	NN	O	5	dep
27	II	ii	CD	NUMBER	26	nummod
28	:	:	:	O	5	punct
29	Why	why	WRB	O	33	advmod
30	It	it	PRP	O	33	nsubj
31	's	be	VBZ	O	33	cop
32	Even	even	RB	O	33	advmod
33	Scarier	scarier	JJR	O	5	acl:relcl
34	Than	than	IN	O	38	case
35	the	the	DT	O	38	det
36	First	First	NNP	ORDINAL	38	compound
37	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	38	compound
38	Act	Act	NNP	O	33	nmod
39	.	.	.	O	2	punct
40	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
2	her	she	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
3	article	article	NN	O	4	compound
4	Ramasastry	ramasastry	NN	PERSON	6	nsubj
5	heavily	heavily	RB	O	6	advmod
6	relies	rely	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	on	on	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	use	use	NN	O	6	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	11	case
11	Pathos	pathos	NN	O	9	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	make	make	VB	O	6	xcomp
14	her	she	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	argument	argument	NN	O	13	dobj
16	to	to	TO	O	19	case
17	her	she	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	reading	reading	NN	O	19	compound
19	audience	audience	NN	O	13	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	strategy	strategy	NN	O	13	nsubj
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	she	she	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	uses	use	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
6	that	that	DT	O	9	nsubjpass
7	is	be	VBZ	O	9	auxpass
8	heavily	heavily	RB	O	9	advmod
9	based	base	VBN	O	5	ccomp
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	Pathos	pathos	NN	O	9	nmod
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	aux
13	presenting	present	VBG	O	0	ROOT
14	possible	possible	JJ	O	15	amod
15	scenarios	scenario	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	that	that	WDT	O	18	nsubj
17	could	could	MD	O	18	aux
18	happen	happen	VB	O	15	acl:relcl
19	to	to	TO	O	18	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
21	American	american	JJ	MISC	22	amod
22	citizen	citizen	NN	O	15	conj
23	under	under	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	26	compound
26	Act	Act	NNP	O	22	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	8	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	scenarios	scenario	NNS	O	8	nsubj
4	she	she	PRP	O	5	nmod:npmod
5	present	present	JJ	DATE	3	amod
6	have	have	VBP	O	8	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	happened	happen	VBN	O	17	advcl
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	DATE	11	det
11	past	past	NN	DATE	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	17	punct
13	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	writing	writing	NN	O	17	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	17	cop
16	still	still	RB	O	17	advmod
17	persuasive	persuasive	JJ	O	0	ROOT
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	because	because	IN	O	22	mark
20	she	she	PRP	O	22	nsubj
21	is	be	VBZ	O	22	aux
22	presenting	present	VBG	O	17	advcl
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	scenarios	scenario	NNS	O	22	dobj
25	in	in	IN	O	27	case
26	a	a	DT	O	27	det
27	sense	sense	NN	O	22	nmod
28	that	that	WDT	O	38	dobj
29	while	while	IN	O	35	mark
30	they	they	PRP	O	35	nsubj
31	may	may	MD	O	35	aux
32	not	not	RB	O	35	neg
33	have	have	VB	O	35	aux
34	already	already	RB	O	35	advmod
35	happened	happen	VBN	O	38	advcl
36	they	they	PRP	O	38	nsubj
37	will	will	MD	O	38	aux
38	happen	happen	VB	O	27	acl:relcl
39	if	if	IN	O	41	mark
40	we	we	PRP	O	41	nsubj
41	renew	renew	VBP	O	38	advcl
42	the	the	DT	O	44	det
43	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	44	compound
44	Act	Act	NNP	O	41	dobj
45	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
2	possible	possible	JJ	O	3	amod
3	scenario	scenario	NN	O	15	nsubj
4	she	she	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	describes	describe	VBZ	O	3	acl:relcl
6	that	that	DT	O	7	nsubj
7	has	have	VBZ	O	5	ccomp
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	powerful	powerful	JJ	O	10	amod
10	effect	effect	NN	O	7	dobj
11	on	on	IN	O	13	case
12	her	she	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	audience	audience	NN	O	10	nmod
14	is	be	VBZ	O	15	cop
15	one	one	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
16	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubj
17	includes	include	VBZ	O	15	acl:relcl
18	losing	lose	VBG	O	17	xcomp
19	your	you	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
20	American	american	JJ	MISC	21	amod
21	citizenship	citizenship	NN	O	18	dobj
22	over	over	IN	O	23	case
23	something	something	NN	O	21	nmod
24	as	as	IN	O	25	case
25	minor	minor	JJ	O	18	advcl
26	as	as	IN	O	27	mark
27	attending	attend	VBG	O	18	advcl
28	a	a	DT	O	29	det
29	protest	protest	NN	O	27	dobj
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Ramasastry	ramasastry	NN	PERSON	29	appos
32	11	11	CD	NUMBER	31	nummod
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
34	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Suppose	suppose	VB	O	0	ROOT
3	you	you	PRP	O	9	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	9	punct
5	as	as	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	citizen	citizen	NN	O	9	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	9	punct
9	attended	attend	VBD	O	2	ccomp
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	legal	legal	JJ	O	12	amod
12	protest	protest	NN	O	9	dobj
13	for	for	IN	O	14	case
14	which	which	WDT	O	26	nmod
15	one	one	CD	NUMBER	26	nsubj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	hosts	host	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	15	punct
20	unbeknownst	unbeknownst	NN	O	15	appos
21	to	to	TO	O	22	case
22	you	you	PRP	O	20	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	15	punct
24	is	be	VBZ	O	26	cop
25	an	a	DT	O	26	det
26	organization	organization	NN	O	12	acl:relcl
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	government	government	NN	O	30	nsubj
29	has	have	VBZ	O	30	aux
30	listed	list	VBN	O	26	acl:relcl
31	as	as	IN	O	32	case
32	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Under	under	IN	O	2	case
2	Patriot	patriot	NN	O	8	nmod
3	II	ii	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	you	you	PRP	O	8	nsubjpass
6	may	may	MD	O	8	aux
7	be	be	VB	O	8	auxpass
8	deported	deport	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	no	no	RB	O	11	neg
11	longer	longer	RBR	O	12	advmod
12	deemed	deem	VBD	O	8	conj
13	an	a	DT	O	15	det
14	American	american	JJ	MISC	15	amod
15	citizen	citizen	NN	O	12	dobj
16	''	''	''	O	15	punct
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	Ramasastry	Ramasastry	NNP	PERSON	15	appos
19	11	11	CD	NUMBER	18	nummod
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
21	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Ramasastry	Ramasastry	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	passionate	passionate	JJ	O	4	amod
4	article	article	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	successfully	successfully	RB	O	7	advmod
7	impacts	impact	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	her	she	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	audience	audience	NN	O	7	xcomp
10	because	because	IN	O	13	mark
11	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	shrewdly	shrewdly	RB	O	13	advmod
13	uses	use	VBZ	O	7	advcl
14	pathos	pathos	NNS	O	13	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	discuss	discuss	VB	O	13	xcomp
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	explicit	explicit	JJ	O	19	amod
19	dangers	danger	NNS	O	16	dobj
20	that	that	WDT	O	22	nsubj
21	could	could	MD	O	22	aux
22	happen	happen	VB	O	19	acl:relcl
23	to	to	TO	O	26	case
24	any	any	DT	O	26	det
25	unsuspecting	unsuspecting	JJ	O	26	amod
26	American	american	JJ	MISC	22	nmod
27	under	under	IN	O	30	case
28	the	the	DT	O	30	det
29	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	30	compound
30	Act	Act	NNP	O	22	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	event	event	NN	O	20	nsubj
3	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
4	has	have	VBZ	O	5	aux
5	raised	raise	VBN	O	2	ccomp
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	lot	lot	NN	O	5	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	debate	debate	NN	O	7	nmod
10	over	over	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	effectiveness	effectiveness	NN	O	5	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	16	compound
16	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	12	nmod
17	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	Boston	Boston	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
20	Bombings	bombing	NNS	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
21	in	in	IN	O	22	case
22	2012	2012	CD	DATE	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	Michael	Michael	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Muskal	Muskal	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	7	case
4	the	the	DT	O	7	det
5	Los	Los	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
6	Angeles	Angeles	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	Times	Times	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
8	took	take	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	opportunity	opportunity	NN	O	8	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	raise	raise	VB	O	10	acl
13	points	point	NNS	O	12	dobj
14	regarding	regard	VBG	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	failure	failure	NN	O	13	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	20	compound
20	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	16	nmod
21	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
22	successfully	successfully	RB	O	23	advmod
23	counter	counter	VB	O	12	advcl
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	attack	attack	NN	O	23	dobj
26	on	on	IN	O	27	case
27	Boston	Boston	NNP	LOCATION	25	nmod
28	,	,	,	O	25	punct
29	in	in	IN	O	31	case
30	his	he	PRP$	O	31	nmod:poss
31	articles	article	NNS	O	25	nmod
32	``	``	``	O	25	punct
33	Krystle	Krystle	NNP	PERSON	36	compound
34	M.	M.	NNP	PERSON	36	compound
35	Campbell	Campbell	NNP	PERSON	36	compound
36	Mourned	Mourned	NNP	PERSON	25	dep
37	as	as	IN	O	41	case
38	2nd	2nd	JJ	ORGANIZATION	41	amod
39	Boston	Boston	NNP	ORGANIZATION	41	compound
40	Bombing	Bombing	NNP	ORGANIZATION	41	compound
41	Victim	Victim	NNP	ORGANIZATION	36	nmod
42	.	.	.	O	8	punct
43	''	''	''	O	8	punct

1	Based	base	VBN	O	4	case
2	on	on	IN	O	4	case
3	time	time	NN	O	4	compound
4	table	table	NN	O	36	advcl
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	events	event	NNS	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	Muskal	Muskal	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	6	appos
10	from	from	IN	O	11	case
11	Kairos	Kairos	NNP	LOCATION	9	nmod
12	by	by	IN	O	13	mark
13	writing	write	VBG	O	11	acl
14	to	to	TO	O	15	case
15	audience	audience	NN	O	13	nmod
16	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubj
17	wants	want	VBZ	O	15	acl:relcl
18	answers	answer	NNS	O	17	dobj
19	as	as	IN	O	24	mark
20	to	to	TO	O	19	mwe
21	how	how	WRB	O	24	advmod
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	government	government	NN	O	24	nsubj
24	failed	fail	VBD	O	18	acl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	prevent	prevent	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	bombings	bombing	NNS	O	26	dobj
29	with	with	IN	O	32	case
30	all	all	PDT	O	32	det:predet
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	provisions	provision	NNS	O	26	nmod
33	the	the	DT	O	35	det
34	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	35	compound
35	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	36	nsubj
36	allows	allow	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
37	,	,	,	O	36	punct
38	for	for	IN	O	41	case
39	the	the	DT	O	41	det
40	sole	sole	JJ	O	41	amod
41	reason	reason	NN	O	36	nmod
42	of	of	IN	O	44	case
43	counter	counter	NN	O	44	compound
44	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	36	nmod
45	and	and	CC	O	44	cc
46	national	national	JJ	O	47	amod
47	defense	defense	NN	O	44	conj
48	.	.	.	O	36	punct

1	Perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	26	advmod
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	most	most	RBS	O	4	advmod
4	incriminating	incriminate	VBG	O	26	dep
5	quote	quote	NN	O	4	dobj
6	that	that	WDT	O	8	dobj
7	Muskal	Muskal	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	uses	use	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
9	in	in	IN	O	10	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod
11	questioning	question	VBG	O	10	amod
12	of	of	IN	O	16	mark
13	how	how	WRB	O	16	advmod
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	government	government	NN	O	16	nsubj
16	failed	fail	VBD	O	5	acl
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	pick	pick	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	up	up	RP	O	18	compound:prt
20	on	on	IN	O	23	case
21	this	this	DT	O	23	det
22	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	23	amod
23	plot	plot	NN	O	18	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	26	punct
25	is	be	VBZ	O	26	auxpass
26	given	give	VBN	O	0	ROOT
27	by	by	IN	O	30	case
28	Congressman	Congressman	NNP	O	30	compound
29	Peter	Peter	NNP	PERSON	30	compound
30	King	King	NNP	PERSON	26	nmod
31	of	of	IN	O	33	case
32	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	33	compound
33	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	30	nmod
34	``	``	``	O	36	punct
35	There	there	EX	O	36	expl
36	was	be	VBD	O	26	ccomp
37	``	``	``	O	36	punct
38	no	no	DT	O	39	neg
39	intelligence	intelligence	NN	O	36	nsubj
40	that	that	WDT	O	41	nsubj
41	seemed	seem	VBD	O	39	acl:relcl
42	to	to	TO	O	45	mark
43	be	be	VB	O	45	cop
44	out	out	IN	O	45	case
45	there	there	RB	O	41	xcomp
46	.	.	.	O	26	punct

1	Now	now	RB	DATE	4	advmod
2	people	people	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
4	look	look	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	back	back	RB	O	4	advmod
6	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
7	see	see	VB	O	4	conj
8	if	if	IN	O	11	mark
9	something	something	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
10	was	be	VBD	O	11	auxpass
11	missed	miss	VBN	O	7	advcl
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	4	aux
3	n't	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	know	know	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	if	if	IN	O	7	mark
6	there	there	EX	O	7	expl
7	was	be	VBD	O	4	advcl
8	or	or	CC	O	9	case
9	not	not	RB	O	7	nmod
10	''	''	''	O	7	punct
11	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	12	punct
12	Muskal	Muskal	NNP	PERSON	7	dep
13	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	12	punct
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	3	mark
2	Muskal	muskal	JJ	PERSON	3	amod
3	points	point	NNS	O	20	advcl
4	out	out	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	flaws	flaw	NNS	O	3	dep
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	O	6	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
12	its	its	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	failures	failure	NNS	O	6	conj
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	this	this	DT	O	16	det
16	situation	situation	NN	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	20	punct
18	he	he	PRP	O	20	nsubj
19	also	also	RB	O	20	advmod
20	notes	note	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
21	that	that	IN	O	26	mark
22	this	this	DT	O	26	nsubj
23	should	should	MD	O	26	aux
24	be	be	VB	O	26	cop
25	a	a	DT	O	26	det
26	wake	wake	NN	O	20	ccomp
27	up	up	IN	O	28	case
28	call	call	NN	O	26	nmod
29	that	that	IN	O	37	mark
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	fear	fear	NN	O	37	nsubj
32	of	of	IN	O	33	case
33	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	31	nmod
34	if	if	IN	O	35	dep
35	far	far	RB	O	33	amod
36	from	from	IN	O	35	nmod
37	eliminated	eliminate	VBN	O	28	dep
38	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	39	punct
39	Muska	muska	NN	PERSON	28	appos
40	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	39	punct
41	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	aspect	aspect	NN	O	16	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	6	compound
6	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	2	nmod
7	that	that	WDT	O	10	nsubj
8	has	have	VBZ	O	10	aux
9	been	be	VBN	O	10	cop
10	unclear	unclear	JJ	O	2	acl:relcl
11	since	since	IN	O	13	case
12	its	its	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	inception	inception	NN	O	10	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	2001	2001	CD	DATE	10	nmod
16	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
17	whom	whom	WP	O	20	dobj
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	government	government	NN	O	20	nsubj
20	defines	define	VBZ	O	16	ccomp
21	as	as	IN	O	24	case
22	an	a	DT	O	24	det
23	``	``	``	O	24	punct
24	enemy	enemy	NN	O	20	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	state	state	NN	O	24	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	16	punct
29	''	''	''	O	16	punct

1	French	french	JJ	MISC	4	amod
2	journalist	journalist	NN	O	4	compound
3	Jean-Claude	Jean-Claude	NNP	PERSON	4	compound
4	Paye	Paye	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
7	topic	topic	NN	O	5	dep
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	article	article	NN	O	7	dep
11	``	``	``	O	10	punct
12	Merging	merge	VBG	O	10	acl
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	Law	law	NN	MISC	12	dobj
15	of	of	IN	MISC	16	case
16	War	war	NN	MISC	14	nmod
17	with	with	IN	O	19	case
18	Criminal	Criminal	NNP	O	19	compound
19	War	War	NNP	O	10	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct
21	''	''	''	O	5	punct

1	Paye	Paye	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	article	article	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
4	is	be	VBZ	O	6	auxpass
5	deeply	deeply	RB	O	6	advmod
6	rooted	root	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	logos	logo	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	6	conj
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	act	act	NN	O	11	dobj
14	from	from	IN	O	17	case
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	global	global	JJ	O	17	amod
17	standpoint	standpoint	NN	O	11	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	way	way	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	evokes	evoke	VBZ	O	2	acl:relcl
5	logos	logo	NNS	O	4	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	article	article	NN	O	5	nmod
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
10	by	by	IN	O	11	case
11	sighting	sighting	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	whom	whom	WP	O	17	dobj
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	15	compound
15	States	States	NNP	LOCATION	17	nsubj
16	officially	officially	RB	O	17	advmod
17	declared	declare	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
18	war	war	NN	O	17	dobj
19	on	on	IN	O	21	case
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	2001	2001	CD	DATE	17	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	``	``	``	O	2	punct
4	The	the	DT	O	5	det
5	interpretation	interpretation	NN	O	14	nsubj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	resolution	resolution	NN	O	5	nmod
9	made	make	VBN	O	8	acl
10	by	by	IN	O	13	case
11	successive	successive	JJ	O	13	amod
12	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
13	administrations	administration	NNS	O	9	nmod
14	is	be	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
15	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	state	state	NN	O	20	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
19	at	at	IN	O	20	case
20	war	war	NN	O	14	ccomp
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	not	not	RB	O	25	neg
23	against	against	IN	O	25	case
24	other	other	JJ	O	25	amod
25	nations	nation	NNS	O	20	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	but	but	CC	O	25	cc
28	against	against	IN	O	29	case
29	organizations	organization	NNS	O	25	conj
30	that	that	WDT	O	33	nsubjpass
31	are	be	VBP	O	33	auxpass
32	not	not	RB	O	33	neg
33	linked	link	VBN	O	29	acl:relcl
34	to	to	TO	O	37	case
35	a	a	DT	O	37	det
36	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	37	amod
37	government	government	NN	O	33	nmod
38	,	,	,	O	37	punct
39	or	or	CC	O	37	cc
40	against	against	IN	O	42	case
41	private	private	JJ	O	42	amod
42	individuals	individual	NNS	O	37	conj
43	''	''	''	O	2	punct
44	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	45	punct
45	Paye	Paye	NNP	PERSON	2	dep
46	129	129	CD	NUMBER	45	nummod
47	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	45	punct
48	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	point	point	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	that	that	WDT	O	5	dobj
4	Paye	Paye	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	raises	raise	VBZ	O	2	acl:relcl
6	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	13	nsubjpass
11	was	be	VBD	O	13	auxpass
12	originally	originally	RB	O	13	advmod
13	supposed	suppose	VBN	O	6	ccomp
14	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
15	just	just	RB	O	20	advmod
16	be	be	VB	O	20	cop
17	a	a	DT	O	20	det
18	war	war	NN	O	20	compound
19	time	time	NN	O	20	compound
20	piece	piece	NN	O	13	xcomp
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	legislation	legislation	NN	O	20	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	that	that	WDT	O	30	nsubj
25	once	once	RB	DATE	30	advmod
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	war	war	NN	O	25	nmod:npmod
28	on	on	IN	O	29	case
29	terror	terror	NN	O	25	nmod
30	is	be	VBZ	O	22	acl:relcl
31	over	over	IN	O	36	mark
32	there	there	EX	O	36	expl
33	would	would	MD	O	36	aux
34	be	be	VB	O	36	cop
35	no	no	DT	O	36	neg
36	need	need	NN	O	30	advcl
37	keep	keep	VB	O	36	dep
38	the	the	DT	O	40	det
39	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	40	compound
40	Act	Act	NNP	O	37	dobj
41	in	in	IN	O	42	case
42	use	use	NN	O	40	nmod
43	because	because	IN	O	50	mark
44	their	they	PRP$	O	50	nsubj
45	would	would	MD	O	50	aux
46	no	no	RB	O	47	neg
47	longer	longer	RB	O	50	advmod
48	be	be	VB	O	50	cop
49	a	a	DT	O	50	det
50	war	war	NN	O	36	advcl
51	on	on	IN	O	53	case
52	private	private	JJ	O	53	amod
53	individuals	individual	NNS	O	50	nmod
54	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	cites	cite	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	fact	fact	NN	O	2	dobj
5	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
6	both	both	CC	O	7	cc:preconj
7	England	England	NNP	LOCATION	10	nsubj
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	France	France	NNP	LOCATION	7	conj
10	had	have	VBD	O	2	ccomp
11	legislation	legislation	NN	O	10	dobj
12	similar	similar	JJ	O	11	amod
13	to	to	TO	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	16	compound
16	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	12	nmod
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	place	place	NN	O	16	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	10	punct
20	but	but	CC	O	10	cc
21	abolished	abolish	VBD	O	10	conj
22	when	when	WRB	O	24	advmod
23	they	they	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	pulled	pull	VBD	O	21	advcl
25	out	out	RB	O	24	advmod
26	of	of	IN	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	Iraq	Iraq	NNP	O	29	compound
29	War	War	NNP	O	24	nmod
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Paye	Paye	NNP	PERSON	24	dep
32	129	129	CD	NUMBER	31	nummod
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
34	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Paye	Paye	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	an	a	DT	O	5	det
4	excellent	excellent	JJ	O	5	amod
5	job	job	NN	O	2	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	7	mark
7	educating	educate	VBG	O	5	acl
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	audience	audience	NN	O	7	dobj
10	on	on	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	circumstances	circumstance	NNS	O	7	nmod
13	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
14	surround	surround	VBP	O	12	acl:relcl
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	17	compound
17	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	14	dobj
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	use	use	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	logos	logo	NNS	O	2	nmod
5	effectively	effectively	RB	O	6	advmod
6	relays	relay	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	information	information	NN	O	6	dobj
8	to	to	TO	O	10	case
9	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	audience	audience	NN	O	6	nmod
11	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
12	presents	present	VBZ	O	6	dep
13	a	a	DT	O	16	det
14	more	more	RBR	O	15	advmod
15	clear	clear	JJ	O	16	amod
16	understanding	understanding	NN	O	12	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	who	who	WP	O	12	nmod
19	the	the	DT	O	22	det
20	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	22	compound
21	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	22	compound
22	targets	target	NNS	O	12	nsubj
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	aspect	aspect	NN	O	12	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	6	compound
6	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	2	nmod
7	that	that	IN	O	9	nsubj
8	constantly	constantly	RB	O	9	advmod
9	comes	come	VBZ	O	6	acl:relcl
10	under	under	IN	O	11	case
11	fire	fire	NN	O	9	nmod
12	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
13	where	where	WRB	O	16	advmod
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	lines	line	NNS	O	16	nsubj
16	need	need	VBP	O	12	advcl
17	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
18	be	be	VB	O	19	auxpass
19	drawn	draw	VBN	O	16	xcomp
20	monitoring	monitor	VBG	O	19	xcomp
21	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	22	amod
22	suspects	suspect	NNS	O	20	dobj
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	domestic	domestic	JJ	O	25	amod
25	suspects	suspect	NNS	O	22	conj
26	in	in	IN	O	27	mark
27	preventing	prevent	VBG	O	20	advcl
28	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	29	amod
29	attacks	attack	NNS	O	27	dobj
30	under	under	IN	O	33	case
31	the	the	DT	O	33	det
32	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	33	compound
33	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	27	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	Daniel	Daniel	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Lungren	Lungren	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	issue	issue	NN	O	3	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	10	case
7	the	the	DT	O	10	det
8	Notre	Notre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
9	Dame	Dame	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	Journal	Journal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	15	case
12	Law	Law	NNP	O	15	compound
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	Public	Public	NNP	O	12	conj
15	Policy	Policy	NNP	O	10	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	2	mark
2	discussing	discuss	VBG	O	7	advcl
3	this	this	DT	O	5	det
4	controversial	controversial	JJ	O	5	amod
5	issues	issue	NNS	O	2	dobj
6	Lungren	Lungren	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	rhetorical	rhetorical	JJ	O	9	amod
9	argument	argument	NN	O	7	dobj
10	strongly	strongly	RB	O	11	advmod
11	rooted	root	VBN	O	9	acl
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	ethos	ethos	NN	O	11	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	ethos	ethos	NN	O	2	dobj
4	when	when	WRB	O	6	advmod
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	discuses	discus	VBZ	O	3	acl:relcl
7	why	why	WRB	O	11	advmod
8	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
10	ethically	ethically	RB	O	11	advmod
11	okay	okay	JJ	O	6	advcl
12	for	for	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	government	government	NN	O	11	nmod
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	use	use	VB	O	11	xcomp
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	19	compound
19	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	16	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	monitor	monitor	VB	O	16	xcomp
22	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	21	dobj
23	suspected	suspect	VBN	O	22	acl
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	26	amod
26	activity	activity	NN	O	23	nmod
27	in	in	IN	O	30	case
28	counter	counter	JJ	O	30	amod
29	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	30	compound
30	cases	case	NNS	O	26	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	offers	offer	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	refreshing	refreshing	JJ	O	2	xcomp
4	take	take	NN	O	8	nsubj
5	on	on	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	issue	issue	NN	O	4	nmod
8	is	be	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
9	when	when	WRB	O	11	advmod
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	says	say	VBZ	O	8	advcl
12	``	``	``	O	14	punct
13	That	that	DT	O	14	nsubj
14	is	be	VBZ	O	11	ccomp
15	why	why	WRB	O	14	dep
16	,	,	,	O	2	punct
17	when	when	WRB	O	20	advmod
18	government	government	NN	O	20	nsubj
19	is	be	VBZ	O	20	aux
20	fighting	fight	VBG	O	2	advcl
21	terrorism	terrorism	NN	O	20	dobj
22	rather	rather	RB	O	25	case
23	than	than	IN	O	22	mwe
24	ordinary	ordinary	JJ	O	25	amod
25	crime	crime	NN	O	20	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	emphasis	emphasis	NN	O	29	compound
29	shifts	shift	NNS	O	25	appos
30	from	from	IN	O	31	case
31	punishment	punishment	NN	O	20	nmod
32	to	to	TO	O	33	case
33	prevention	prevention	NN	O	20	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	2	punct
35	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Lungren	lungren	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	428	428	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
4	.	.	.	O	2	punct
5	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct

1	Lungren	Lungren	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	defends	defend	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	ethics	ethic	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	8	compound
8	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	4	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	by	by	IN	O	11	mark
11	relating	relate	VBG	O	2	advcl
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	audience	audience	NN	O	11	nmod
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	fact	fact	NN	O	11	dobj
17	that	that	IN	O	22	mark
18	punishment	punishment	NN	O	22	nsubj
19	often	often	RB	O	22	advmod
20	does	do	VBZ	O	22	aux
21	not	not	RB	O	22	neg
22	deter	deter	VB	O	16	dep
23	those	those	DT	O	22	dobj
24	who	who	WP	O	25	nsubj
25	intend	intend	VBP	O	23	acl:relcl
26	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
27	commit	commit	VB	O	25	xcomp
28	acts	act	NNS	O	27	dobj
29	of	of	IN	O	30	case
30	terror	terror	NN	O	28	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	2	punct
32	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
33	the	the	DT	O	35	det
34	only	only	JJ	O	35	amod
35	way	way	NN	O	40	nsubj
36	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
37	stop	stop	VB	O	35	acl
38	these	these	DT	O	39	det
39	acts	act	NNS	O	37	dobj
40	is	be	VBZ	O	2	conj
41	to	to	TO	O	42	mark
42	prevent	prevent	VB	O	40	xcomp
43	them	they	PRP	O	42	dobj
44	from	from	IN	O	45	mark
45	happening	happen	VBG	O	42	advcl
46	in	in	IN	O	49	case
47	their	they	PRP$	O	49	nmod:poss
48	early	early	JJ	O	49	amod
49	stages	stage	NNS	O	45	nmod
50	of	of	IN	O	51	case
51	development	development	NN	O	49	nmod
52	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	53	punct
53	Lungren	lungren	NN	PERSON	51	appos
54	434	434	CD	NUMBER	53	nummod
55	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	53	punct
56	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Christopher	Christopher	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Banks	Banks	NNP	PERSON	20	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	author	author	NN	O	2	acl:relcl
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	article	article	NN	O	5	nmod
9	``	``	``	O	8	punct
10	Security	Security	NNP	O	8	dep
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	Freedom	Freedom	NNP	O	10	conj
13	After	after	IN	O	14	case
14	September	September	NNP	DATE	5	nmod
15	11	11	CD	DATE	14	nummod
16	,	,	,	O	2	punct
17	''	''	''	O	2	punct
18	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
19	strong	strong	JJ	O	20	amod
20	opponent	opponent	NN	O	0	ROOT
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	24	compound
24	Act	Act	NNP	O	20	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	argument	argument	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	reveals	reveal	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	strong	strong	JJ	O	6	amod
6	use	use	NN	O	3	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	pathos	pathos	NN	O	6	nmod
9	particularly	particularly	RB	O	12	advmod
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	criticism	criticism	NN	O	3	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	President	President	NNP	O	15	compound
15	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	12	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	tries	try	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	6	case
4	present	present	JJ	DATE	6	amod
5	President	President	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
7	to	to	TO	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	audience	audience	NN	O	2	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	15	case
11	a	a	DT	O	15	det
12	less	less	JJR	O	14	dep
13	than	than	IN	O	14	dep
14	flattering	flattering	JJ	O	15	amod
15	light	light	NN	O	9	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	2	dobj
4	by	by	IN	O	5	mark
5	playing	play	VBG	O	2	advcl
6	on	on	IN	O	8	case
7	their	they	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	emotions	emotion	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	by	by	IN	O	10	mark
10	trying	try	VBG	O	5	advcl
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	convince	convince	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	them	they	PRP	O	12	dobj
14	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
15	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	16	nsubj
16	overstepped	overstep	VBD	O	12	ccomp
17	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	Constitutional	Constitutional	NNP	O	19	compound
19	privilege	privilege	NN	O	16	dobj
20	because	because	IN	O	22	mark
21	he	he	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	wanted	want	VBD	O	16	advcl
23	more	more	JJR	O	24	amod
24	power	power	NN	O	22	dobj
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Banks	bank	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	argues	argue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	passed	pass	VBD	O	2	ccomp
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	8	compound
8	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	5	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	make	make	VB	O	5	xcomp
11	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	office	office	NN	O	14	nsubj
13	more	more	RBR	O	14	advmod
14	powerful	powerful	JJ	O	10	xcomp
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Banks	bank	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	writes	write	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	``	``	``	O	2	punct
4	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	relied	rely	VB	O	2	ccomp
6	on	on	IN	O	9	case
7	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
8	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	advisers	adviser	NNS	O	5	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	legal	legal	JJ	O	12	amod
12	interpretations	interpretation	NNS	O	9	conj
13	by	by	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
16	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	19	case
17	Justice	Justice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	ORGANIZATION	17	case
19	Office	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	nmod
20	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	22	case
21	Legal	Legal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
22	Counsel	Counsel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nmod
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	bolster	bolster	VB	O	5	xcomp
25	his	he	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
26	presidential	presidential	JJ	O	27	amod
27	powers	power	NNS	O	24	dobj
28	under	under	IN	O	30	case
29	Article	Article	NNP	O	30	compound
30	II	II	NNP	O	24	nmod
31	of	of	IN	O	33	case
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	Constitution	Constitution	NNP	O	30	nmod
34	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
35	expand	expand	VB	O	5	conj
36	them	they	PRP	O	35	dobj
37	unilaterally	unilaterally	RB	O	35	advmod
38	''	''	''	O	2	punct
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	Banks	Banks	NNP	O	2	dep
41	7	7	CD	NUMBER	40	dep
42	.	.	.	O	40	punct
43	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct

1	Banks	bank	NNS	O	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	notes	note	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	17	advmod
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	minimal	minimal	JJ	O	7	amod
7	checks	check	NNS	O	17	nsubj
8	on	on	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	Presidents	president	NNS	O	11	compound
11	authority	authority	NN	O	7	nmod
12	regarding	regard	VBG	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	15	compound
15	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	11	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	17	punct
17	allow	allow	VBP	O	3	ccomp
18	him	he	PRP	O	17	dobj
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	waive	waive	VB	O	17	xcomp
21	standard	standard	JJ	O	24	amod
22	criminal	criminal	JJ	O	24	amod
23	investigation	investigation	NN	O	24	compound
24	proceedings	proceedings	NNS	O	20	dobj
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	27	punct
26	Banks	bank	NNS	O	27	nsubj
27	2	2	LS	NUMBER	3	parataxis
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
29	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	talks	talk	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	about	about	IN	O	8	mark
5	President	President	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	failed	fail	VBD	O	3	advcl
9	attempt	attempt	NN	O	8	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	add	add	VB	O	8	advcl
12	even	even	RB	O	13	advmod
13	more	more	RBR	O	14	amod
14	provisions	provision	NNS	O	11	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	18	compound
18	Act	Act	NNP	O	11	nmod
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	21	amod
21	time	time	NN	O	8	nmod:tmod
22	it	it	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	was	be	VBD	O	21	acl:relcl
24	up	up	RB	O	23	advmod
25	for	for	IN	O	26	case
26	reneweal	reneweal	NN	O	24	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Banks	bank	NNS	O	24	dep
3	4	4	LS	NUMBER	2	dep
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	Though	though	IN	O	7	mark
6	Banks	bank	NNS	O	7	nsubj
7	does	do	VBZ	O	24	csubj
8	an	a	DT	O	10	det
9	good	good	JJ	O	10	amod
10	job	job	NN	O	7	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	12	mark
12	playing	play	VBG	O	10	acl
13	on	on	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	readers	reader	NNS	O	16	compound
16	emotions	emotion	NNS	O	12	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
18	convincing	convince	VBG	O	12	conj
19	them	they	PRP	O	18	dobj
20	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
21	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	23	nsubj
22	may	may	MD	O	23	aux
23	have	have	VB	O	18	ccomp
24	had	have	VBD	O	31	advcl
25	ulterior	ulterior	JJ	O	26	amod
26	motives	motive	NNS	O	24	dobj
27	,	,	,	O	31	punct
28	his	he	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	argument	argument	NN	O	31	nsubjpass
30	is	be	VBZ	O	31	auxpass
31	hurt	hurt	VBN	O	0	ROOT
32	by	by	IN	O	33	case
33	kairos	kairo	NNS	O	31	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	31	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	argument	argument	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	published	publish	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	2011	2011	CD	DATE	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	4	punct
8	by	by	IN	O	10	case
9	this	this	DT	O	10	det
10	time	time	NN	O	16	nmod
11	President	President	NNP	O	12	compound
12	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	16	nsubj
13	was	be	VBD	O	16	cop
14	out	out	IN	O	16	advmod
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	office	office	NN	O	4	conj
17	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
18	Barack	Barack	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	24	nsubj
20	was	be	VBD	O	24	cop
21	in	in	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	White	White	NNP	LOCATION	24	compound
24	House	House	NNP	LOCATION	4	conj
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Further	further	RB	O	2	advmod
2	more	more	RBR	O	4	advmod
3	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	fails	fail	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	mention	mention	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	May	May	NNP	DATE	16	nmod
10	of	of	IN	DATE	11	case
11	2010	2010	CD	DATE	9	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	16	punct
13	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubj
14	was	be	VBD	O	16	cop
15	President	President	NNP	O	16	compound
16	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	6	ccomp
17	who	who	WP	O	18	nsubj
18	signed	sign	VBD	O	16	acl:relcl
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	renewal	renewal	NN	O	18	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	24	compound
24	Act	Act	NNP	O	20	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Had	have	VBD	O	3	aux
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	written	write	VBD	O	33	dep
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	article	article	NN	O	3	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	2007	2007	CD	DATE	3	nmod
8	or	or	CC	O	7	cc
9	2008	2008	CD	DATE	7	conj
10	when	when	WRB	O	17	advmod
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	13	compound
13	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	17	nsubj
14	was	be	VBD	O	17	cop
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	hot	hot	JJ	O	17	amod
17	topic	topic	NN	O	3	advcl
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	President	President	NNP	O	20	compound
20	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	23	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	approval	approval	NN	O	23	compound
23	ratings	rating	NNS	O	25	nsubj
24	were	be	VBD	O	25	aux
25	bottoming	bottom	VBG	O	17	conj
26	out	out	RP	O	25	compound:prt
27	,	,	,	O	33	punct
28	his	he	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	argument	argument	NN	O	33	nsubjpass
30	may	may	MD	O	33	aux
31	have	have	VB	O	33	aux
32	been	be	VBN	O	33	auxpass
33	met	meet	VBN	O	0	ROOT
34	with	with	IN	O	36	case
35	more	more	JJR	O	36	amod
36	agreement	agreement	NN	O	33	nmod
37	from	from	IN	O	39	case
38	his	he	PRP$	O	39	nmod:poss
39	audience	audience	NN	O	36	nmod
40	.	.	.	O	33	punct

1	Tina	Tina	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Ebenger	Ebenger	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	7	advmod
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	O	7	compound
7	Act	Act	NNP	O	3	xcomp
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	how	how	WRB	O	10	advmod
10	it	it	PRP	O	7	conj
11	specially	specially	RB	O	12	advmod
12	effects	effect	NNS	O	10	acl:relcl
13	our	we	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
14	online	online	NN	O	15	compound
15	privacy	privacy	NN	O	12	dep
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	7	det
4	strong	strong	JJ	O	7	amod
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	well-timed	well-timed	JJ	O	4	conj
7	argument	argument	NN	O	2	dobj
8	using	use	VBG	O	7	dep
9	logos	logo	NNS	O	8	dobj
10	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
11	benefitting	benefit	VBG	O	8	conj
12	from	from	IN	O	13	case
13	kairos	kairos	FW	O	11	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	logos	logo	NNS	O	2	dobj
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	her	she	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	statement	statement	NN	O	3	nmod
7	as	as	IN	O	14	mark
8	to	to	TO	O	7	mwe
9	why	why	WRB	O	14	advmod
10	e-mail	e-mail	NN	O	14	nsubj
11	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	14	det
13	private	private	JJ	O	14	amod
14	service	service	NN	O	6	acl
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	``	``	``	O	2	punct
5	It	it	PRP	O	7	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
7	private	private	JJ	O	2	ccomp
8	technologically	technologically	RB	O	7	advmod
9	in	in	IN	O	13	mark
10	that	that	DT	O	11	det
11	encryption	encryption	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	can	can	MD	O	13	aux
13	keep	keep	VB	O	7	ccomp
14	prying	prying	JJ	O	15	amod
15	eyes	eye	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	from	from	IN	O	19	case
17	your	you	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	private	private	JJ	O	19	amod
19	e-mails	e-mail	NNS	O	13	nmod
20	''	''	''	O	2	punct
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	22	punct
22	Ebenger	Ebenger	NNP	PERSON	2	dep
23	48	48	CD	NUMBER	22	nummod
24	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	22	punct
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	cites	cite	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	new	new	JJ	O	5	amod
5	felonies	felony	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	added	add	VBN	O	5	acl
7	under	under	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	6	nmod
11	that	that	WDT	O	12	nsubj
12	include	include	VBP	O	10	acl:relcl
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	hacking	hacking	NN	O	5	conj
15	federal	federal	JJ	O	16	amod
16	systems	system	NNS	O	14	dep
17	,	,	,	O	5	punct
18	untraceable	untraceable	JJ	O	19	amod
19	transfers	transfer	NNS	O	5	conj
20	of	of	IN	O	21	case
21	funds	fund	NNS	O	19	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	5	punct
23	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
24	internet	internet	NN	O	25	compound
25	piracy	piracy	NN	O	5	conj
26	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	27	punct
27	Ebenger	ebenger	NN	PERSON	25	appos
28	52	52	CD	NUMBER	27	nummod
29	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Ebenger	ebenger	NN	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	good	good	JJ	O	5	amod
5	job	job	NN	O	2	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	7	mark
7	describing	describe	VBG	O	5	acl
8	to	to	TO	O	10	case
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	audience	audience	NN	O	7	nmod
11	what	what	WP	O	14	nsubj
12	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	government	government	NN	O	10	acl:relcl
15	considers	consider	VBZ	O	14	acl:relcl
16	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
17	be	be	VB	O	19	cop
18	terrorist	terrorist	JJ	O	19	amod
19	activity	activity	NN	O	15	xcomp
20	on	on	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	Internet	internet	NN	MISC	19	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Ebenger	Ebenger	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	argument	argument	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
5	strongly	strongly	RB	O	6	advmod
6	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	3	dep
7	from	from	IN	O	8	case
8	kairos	kairo	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	time	time	NN	DATE	6	nmod
4	it	it	PRP	O	6	nsubjpass
5	was	be	VBD	O	6	auxpass
6	written	write	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	social	social	JJ	O	8	amod
8	media	media	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
10	online	online	JJ	O	11	amod
11	activity	activity	NN	O	14	nsubj
12	were	be	VBD	O	14	cop
13	increasingly	increasingly	RB	O	14	advmod
14	popular	popular	JJ	O	6	conj
15	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Since	since	IN	O	6	mark
2	this	this	DT	O	6	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	new	new	JJ	O	6	amod
6	concept	concept	NN	O	10	advcl
7	,	,	,	O	10	punct
8	people	people	NNS	O	10	nsubj
9	were	be	VBD	O	10	cop
10	naive	naive	JJ	O	0	ROOT
11	as	as	IN	O	10	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	15	case
13	what	what	WP	O	15	nsubj
14	was	be	VBD	O	15	cop
15	private	private	JJ	O	10	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	what	what	WP	O	19	nsubj
18	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
19	public	public	JJ	O	15	conj
20	,	,	,	O	15	punct
21	as	as	RB	O	15	cc
22	well	well	RB	O	21	mwe
23	as	as	IN	O	28	mark
24	what	what	WP	O	28	dobj
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	government	government	NN	O	28	nsubj
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	hack	hack	VB	O	15	conj
29	into	into	IN	O	32	case
30	without	without	IN	O	32	mark
31	your	you	PRP$	O	32	nsubj
32	knowing	know	VBG	O	28	dep
33	under	under	IN	O	36	case
34	the	the	DT	O	36	det
35	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	36	compound
36	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	32	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	good	good	JJ	O	5	amod
5	job	job	NN	O	2	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	7	mark
7	using	use	VBG	O	5	acl
8	logos	logo	NNS	O	7	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	help	help	VB	O	7	advcl
11	clarify	clarify	VB	O	10	xcomp
12	that	that	DT	O	13	det
13	question	question	NN	O	11	dobj
14	for	for	IN	O	16	case
15	her	she	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	audience	audience	NN	O	13	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Tina	Tina	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Ebenger	Ebenger	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	presents	present	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	insightful	insightful	JJ	O	5	amod
5	take	take	NN	O	3	dobj
6	that	that	WDT	O	9	dobj
7	she	she	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	extensively	extensively	RB	O	9	advmod
9	supports	support	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
10	with	with	IN	O	12	case
11	factual	factual	JJ	O	12	amod
12	statements	statement	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	statistics	statistics	NNS	O	12	conj
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	10	mark
2	all	all	DT	O	10	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	articles	article	NNS	O	2	nmod
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	arguments	argument	NNS	O	5	conj
8	discussed	discuss	VBN	O	5	acl
9	above	above	IN	O	8	nmod
10	have	have	VBP	O	28	advcl
11	different	different	JJ	O	10	dobj
12	takes	take	VBZ	O	11	acl:relcl
13	on	on	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	16	compound
16	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	12	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	12	punct
18	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
19	use	use	VBP	O	12	conj
20	different	different	JJ	O	21	amod
21	strategies	strategy	NNS	O	19	dobj
22	in	in	IN	O	23	mark
23	discussing	discuss	VBG	O	19	advcl
24	them	they	PRP	O	23	dobj
25	,	,	,	O	28	punct
26	they	they	PRP	O	28	nsubj
27	all	all	DT	O	28	advmod
28	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
29	one	one	CD	NUMBER	30	nummod
30	thing	thing	NN	O	28	dobj
31	in	in	IN	O	32	case
32	common	common	JJ	O	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	5	nsubjpass
2	are	be	VBP	O	5	auxpass
3	all	all	RB	O	5	advmod
4	well	well	RB	O	5	advmod
5	written	write	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	do	do	VBP	O	5	conj
8	an	a	DT	O	10	det
9	excellent	excellent	JJ	O	10	amod
10	job	job	NN	O	7	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	13	mark
12	really	really	RB	O	13	advmod
13	getting	get	VBG	O	10	acl
14	through	through	IN	O	17	case
15	to	to	TO	O	17	case
16	their	they	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	audience	audience	NN	O	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	11	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	proponents	proponent	NNS	O	11	nsubj
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	opponents	opponent	NNS	O	3	conj
7	discussed	discuss	VBN	O	6	acl
8	above	above	IN	O	7	nmod
9	may	may	MD	O	11	aux
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	agree	agree	VB	O	22	advcl
12	on	on	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	use	use	NN	O	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	Patriot	Patriot	NNP	MISC	18	compound
18	Act	Act	NNP	MISC	14	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	22	punct
20	they	they	PRP	O	22	nsubj
21	all	all	DT	O	22	advmod
22	agree	agree	VBP	O	0	ROOT
23	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
24	they	they	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	have	have	VBP	O	22	ccomp
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	American	american	JJ	MISC	28	amod
28	peoples	people	NNS	O	25	dobj
29	best	best	JJS	O	30	amod
30	interest	interest	NN	O	25	nmod
31	at	at	IN	O	30	case
32	heart	heart	NN	O	30	dep
33	,	,	,	O	25	punct
34	however	however	RB	O	42	advmod
35	what	what	WP	O	42	dobj
36	those	those	DT	O	37	det
37	interests	interest	NNS	O	42	nsubj
38	are	be	VBP	O	42	aux
39	is	be	VBZ	O	42	cop
40	up	up	RP	O	42	advmod
41	for	for	IN	O	42	case
42	debate	debate	NN	O	25	dep
43	.	.	.	O	22	punct

