1	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	powerful	powerful	JJ	O	6	amod
6	poem	poem	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	12	case
8	the	the	DT	O	12	det
9	American	american	JJ	MISC	12	amod
10	poet	poet	NN	O	12	compound
11	Marge	Marge	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	written	write	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	at	at	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	time	time	NN	O	4	nmod
8	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
9	second-wave	second-wave	JJ	O	10	amod
10	feminism	feminism	NN	O	14	nsubj
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
13	was	be	VBD	O	14	aux
14	taking	take	VBG	O	4	ccomp
15	place	place	NN	O	14	dobj
16	obviously	obviously	RB	O	14	advmod
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	6	det
4	very	very	RB	O	5	advmod
5	active	active	JJ	O	6	amod
6	woman	woman	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	society	society	NN	O	6	nmod
10	aspects	aspect	NNS	O	9	dep
11	,	,	,	O	9	punct
12	especially	especially	RB	O	9	advmod
13	,	,	,	O	9	punct
14	women	woman	NNS	O	15	compound
15	movements	movement	NNS	O	9	appos
16	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	7	advmod
2	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
6	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	7	advmod
7	published	publish	VBN	O	11	advcl
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	had	have	VBD	O	11	aux
11	seen	see	VBN	O	26	ccomp
12	as	as	IN	O	14	case
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	result	result	NN	O	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	feminism	feminism	NN	O	14	nmod
18	that	that	WDT	O	20	nsubj
19	was	be	VBD	O	20	cop
20	dominant	dominant	JJ	O	17	acl:relcl
21	at	at	IN	O	23	case
22	that	that	DT	O	23	det
23	time	time	NN	O	20	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	26	punct
25	it	it	PRP	O	26	nsubj
26	talks	talk	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
27	about	about	IN	O	30	case
28	an	a	DT	O	30	det
29	ordinary	ordinary	JJ	O	30	amod
30	girl	girl	NN	O	26	nmod
31	being	be	VBG	O	32	auxpass
32	asked	ask	VBN	O	30	acl
33	to	to	TO	O	34	mark
34	play	play	VB	O	32	ccomp
35	with	with	IN	O	36	case
36	dolls	doll	NNS	O	34	nmod
37	and	and	CC	O	34	cc
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	act	act	VB	O	34	conj
40	in	in	IN	O	42	case
41	specific	specific	JJ	O	42	amod
42	ways	way	NNS	O	39	nmod
43	in	in	IN	O	46	mark
44	order	order	NN	O	43	mwe
45	to	to	TO	O	46	mark
46	please	please	VB	O	39	advcl
47	others	other	NNS	O	46	dobj
48	or	or	CC	O	34	cc
49	to	to	TO	O	51	mark
50	be	be	VB	O	51	cop
51	acceptable	acceptable	JJ	O	34	conj
52	in	in	IN	O	54	case
53	the	the	DT	O	54	det
54	society	society	NN	O	51	nmod
55	.	.	.	O	26	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	5	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	many	many	JJ	O	7	amod
7	symbols	symbol	NNS	O	5	dobj
8	that	that	WDT	O	9	nsubj
9	reflect	reflect	VBP	O	7	acl:relcl
10	feminism	feminism	NN	O	11	compound
11	manifestations	manifestation	NNS	O	9	dobj
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	society	society	NN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	The	the	DT	O	4	det
3	Carolina	Carolina	NNP	O	4	compound
4	Reader	Reader	NNP	O	8	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	writer	writer	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	clearly	clearly	RB	O	8	advmod
10	:	:	:	O	8	punct
11	``	``	``	O	8	punct
12	Although	although	IN	O	19	mark
13	``	``	``	O	19	punct
14	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	15	compound
15	Doll	Doll	NNP	O	19	nsubjpass
16	''	''	''	O	19	punct
17	might	might	MD	O	19	aux
18	be	be	VB	O	19	auxpass
19	understood	understand	VBN	O	8	parataxis
20	as	as	IN	O	22	case
21	a	a	DT	O	22	det
22	product	product	NN	O	19	dep
23	of	of	IN	O	25	case
24	1970s	1970s	CD	DATE	25	nummod
25	feminism	feminism	NN	O	22	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	22	punct
27	''	''	''	O	22	punct
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	22	appos
30	194	194	CD	NUMBER	29	nummod
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
32	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	15	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	15	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	acquaintance	acquaintance	NN	O	15	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	historical	historical	JJ	O	7	amod
7	period	period	NN	O	4	nmod
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	which	which	WDT	O	13	nmod
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	text	text	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	had	have	VBD	O	13	aux
13	written	write	VBN	O	7	acl:relcl
14	might	might	MD	O	15	aux
15	inspire	inspire	VB	O	0	ROOT
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	reader	reader	NN	O	15	dobj
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	know	know	VB	O	17	acl
20	what	what	WP	O	23	nsubj
21	is	be	VBZ	O	23	cop
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	writer	writer	NN	O	19	dobj
24	means	mean	VBZ	O	23	acl:relcl
25	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
26	what	what	WP	O	28	nsubj
27	is	be	VBZ	O	28	cop
28	he	he	PRP	O	23	conj
29	trying	try	VBG	O	28	acl
30	to	to	TO	O	31	mark
31	show	show	VB	O	29	xcomp
32	through	through	IN	O	34	case
33	his	he	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
34	text	text	NN	O	31	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Thus	thus	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
5	shape	shape	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	your	you	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	reading	reading	NN	O	5	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	text	text	NN	O	7	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
12	change	change	VB	O	5	conj
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	idea	idea	NN	O	12	dobj
15	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	reader	reader	NN	O	18	nsubj
18	thinks	think	VBZ	O	12	ccomp
19	about	about	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	text	text	NN	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Firstly	firstly	RB	O	8	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	8	punct
3	The	the	DT	O	5	det
4	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
5	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	8	nsubj
6	of	of	IN	LOCATION	7	case
7	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
8	suffered	suffer	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	from	from	IN	O	11	case
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	lack	lack	NN	O	8	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	feminism	feminism	NN	O	11	nmod
14	since	since	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	DATE	16	det
16	beginning	beginning	NN	DATE	8	nmod
17	of	of	IN	DATE	20	case
18	the	the	DT	DATE	20	det
19	19th	19th	JJ	DATE	20	amod
20	century	century	NN	DATE	16	nmod
21	;	;	:	O	8	punct
22	women	woman	NNS	O	24	nsubjpass
23	were	be	VBD	O	24	auxpass
24	treated	treat	VBN	O	8	conj
25	harshly	harshly	RB	O	26	advmod
26	and	and	CC	O	24	advmod
27	inhumanely	inhumanely	RB	O	26	advmod
28	because	because	IN	O	31	mark
29	they	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
30	were	be	VBD	O	31	aux
31	have	have	VBP	O	24	advcl
32	few	few	JJ	O	33	amod
33	rights	rights	NNS	O	31	dobj
34	;	;	:	O	8	punct
35	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	majority	majority	NN	O	42	nsubj
38	of	of	IN	O	39	case
39	rights	rights	NNS	O	37	nmod
40	were	be	VBD	O	42	cop
41	against	against	IN	O	42	case
42	them	they	PRP	O	8	conj
43	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Since	since	IN	O	4	mark
2	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	appeared	appear	VBD	O	11	advcl
5	in	in	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	second-wave	second-wave	JJ	O	8	amod
8	feminism	feminism	NN	O	4	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	11	punct
10	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	some	some	DT	O	11	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	values	value	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	that	that	WDT	O	18	nsubj
17	have	have	VBP	O	18	aux
18	changed	change	VBN	O	15	acl:relcl
19	from	from	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	first-wave	first-wave	JJ	O	18	nmod
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	values	value	NNS	O	21	conj
25	that	that	WDT	O	26	nsubj
26	remained	remain	VBD	O	24	acl:relcl
27	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	23	mark
2	a	a	DT	O	3	det
3	research	research	NN	O	23	nsubj
4	tilted	tilted	JJ	O	3	amod
5	``	``	``	O	3	punct
6	Lunacy	lunacy	NN	O	3	dep
7	in	in	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	DATE	10	det
9	19th	19th	JJ	DATE	10	amod
10	Century	Century	NNP	DATE	6	nmod
11	:	:	:	O	6	punct
12	Women	Women	NNP	O	14	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	admission	admission	NN	O	6	dep
15	to	to	TO	O	16	case
16	Asylums	asylum	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	in	in	IN	O	19	case
18	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	19	compound
19	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	16	nmod
20	of	of	IN	LOCATION	21	case
21	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	19	nmod
22	''	''	''	O	3	punct
23	written	write	VBN	O	36	advcl
24	by	by	IN	O	28	case
25	both	both	CC	O	28	cc:preconj
26	Dr.	Dr.	NNP	O	28	compound
27	Katherine	Katherine	NNP	PERSON	28	compound
28	Pouba	Pouba	NNP	PERSON	23	nmod
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	Dr.	Dr.	NNP	O	32	compound
31	Ashley	Ashley	NNP	PERSON	32	compound
32	Tianen	Tianen	NNP	PERSON	28	conj
33	,	,	,	O	36	punct
34	it	it	PRP	O	36	nsubjpass
35	is	be	VBZ	O	36	auxpass
36	said	say	VBN	O	0	ROOT
37	in	in	IN	O	39	case
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	research	research	NN	O	36	nmod
40	that	that	WDT	O	42	dobj
41	women	woman	NNS	O	42	nsubj
42	faced	face	VBD	O	39	acl:relcl
43	harassments	harassment	NNS	O	42	dobj
44	about	about	IN	O	46	case
45	their	they	PRP$	O	46	nmod:poss
46	bodies	body	NNS	O	42	nmod
47	and	and	CC	O	46	cc
48	shapes	shape	NNS	O	46	conj
49	.	.	.	O	36	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	6	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	6	punct
4	they	they	PRP	O	6	nsubj
5	were	be	VBD	O	6	cop
6	subject	subject	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	case
8	asylums	asylum	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	mental	mental	JJ	O	11	amod
11	institutions	institution	NNS	O	8	conj
12	if	if	IN	O	14	mark
13	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	behave	behave	VBP	O	6	advcl
15	in	in	IN	O	16	case
16	ways	way	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	men	man	NNS	O	21	nsubj
19	do	do	VBP	O	21	aux
20	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
21	like	like	VB	O	16	acl:relcl
22	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Furthermore	furthermore	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	there	there	EX	O	4	expl
4	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	symptoms	symptom	NNS	O	4	nsubj
6	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
7	if	if	IN	O	10	mark
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	woman	woman	NN	O	10	nsubj
10	had	have	VBD	O	12	csubj
11	it	it	PRP	O	10	dobj
12	considered	consider	VBD	O	5	dep
13	abnormal	abnormal	JJ	O	12	xcomp
14	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
15	insane	insane	JJ	O	13	conj
16	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	2	case
2	example	example	NN	O	5	nmod
3	:	:	:	O	5	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	sadness	sadness	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	depression	depression	NN	O	5	conj
8	due	due	JJ	O	12	amod
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	beloved	beloved	JJ	O	11	amod
11	one	one	CD	NUMBER	8	nmod
12	death	death	NN	O	5	dep
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	the	the	DT	O	5	appos
15	using	use	VBG	O	14	dep
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	offensive	offensive	NN	O	15	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	insulting	insulting	JJ	O	23	amod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
22	vulgar	vulgar	JJ	O	19	conj
23	language	language	NN	O	17	appos
24	,	,	,	O	17	punct
25	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
26	lacking	lack	VBG	O	15	conj
27	of	of	IN	O	29	case
28	menstrual	menstrual	JJ	O	29	amod
29	cycle	cycle	NN	O	26	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	2	neg
2	only	only	RB	O	4	cc:preconj
3	these	these	DT	O	4	det
4	symptoms	symptom	NNS	O	0	ROOT
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
7	also	also	RB	O	9	advmod
8	official	official	JJ	O	9	amod
9	diagnoses	diagnosis	NNS	O	4	conj
10	such	such	JJ	O	13	case
11	as	as	IN	O	10	mwe
12	neurological	neurological	JJ	O	13	amod
13	disorder	disorder	NN	O	9	nmod
14	what	what	WDT	O	15	nsubj
15	known	know	VBN	O	13	acl:relcl
16	as	as	IN	O	21	mark
17	epilepsy	epilepsy	NN	O	21	nsubj
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	nymphomania	nymphomania	NN	O	17	conj
20	were	be	VBD	O	21	cop
21	reasons	reason	NNS	O	15	advcl
22	for	for	IN	O	23	mark
23	admitting	admit	VBG	O	21	acl
24	women	woman	NNS	O	23	dobj
25	into	into	IN	O	27	case
26	mental	mental	JJ	O	27	amod
27	institutions	institution	NNS	O	23	nmod
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	Pouba	Pouba	NNP	LOCATION	13	dep
30	,	,	,	O	29	punct
31	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
32	Tianen	Tianen	NNP	O	29	conj
33	95-96	95-96	CD	NUMBER	29	dep
34	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
35	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	notice	notice	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	there	there	EX	O	5	expl
5	is	be	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
6	no	no	DT	O	7	neg
7	trace	trace	NN	O	5	nsubj
8	of	of	IN	O	11	case
9	such	such	JJ	O	11	amod
10	these	these	DT	O	11	det
11	symptoms	symptom	NNS	O	7	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	14	compound
14	Doll	Doll	NNP	O	11	nmod
15	;	;	:	O	2	punct
16	first-wave	first-wave	JJ	O	17	amod
17	feminism	feminism	NN	O	19	nsubj
18	has	have	VBZ	O	19	aux
19	gone	go	VBN	O	2	parataxis
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	reflects	reflect	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	7	det
5	miniature	miniature	JJ	O	7	amod
6	second-wave	second-wave	JJ	O	7	amod
7	feminism	feminism	NN	O	3	dobj
8	that	that	WDT	O	9	nsubj
9	took	take	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
10	place	place	NN	O	9	dobj
11	in	in	IN	O	15	case
12	the	the	DT	DATE	15	det
13	late	late	JJ	DATE	15	amod
14	20th	20th	JJ	DATE	15	amod
15	century	century	NN	DATE	9	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	On	on	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	contrary	contrary	NN	O	19	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	19	punct
5	in	in	IN	O	9	case
6	the	the	DT	O	9	compound
7	both	both	CC	O	6	dep
8	two	two	CD	NUMBER	6	conj
9	eras	era	NNS	O	19	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	19th	19th	JJ	ORDINAL	14	amod
12	and	and	CC	DATE	11	cc
13	20th	20th	JJ	DATE	11	conj
14	century	century	NN	DATE	9	appos
15	,	,	,	O	19	punct
16	women	woman	NNS	O	19	nsubj
17	did	do	VBD	O	19	aux
18	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
19	get	get	VB	O	0	ROOT
20	their	they	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	rights	rights	NNS	O	19	dobj
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	live	live	VB	O	19	advcl
24	simply	simply	RB	O	25	advmod
25	free	free	JJ	O	26	amod
26	live	live	JJ	O	23	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	have	have	VBP	O	13	ccomp
3	small	small	JJ	O	4	amod
4	rights	rights	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	just	just	RB	O	2	advmod
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	marriage	marriage	NN	O	2	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	working	working	NN	O	7	conj
10	,	,	,	O	13	punct
11	man	man	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	can	can	MD	O	13	aux
13	place	place	VB	O	0	ROOT
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	woman	woman	NN	O	13	dobj
16	as	as	IN	O	18	case
17	his	he	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	slave	slave	NN	O	13	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Nevertheless	nevertheless	RB	O	12	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	12	punct
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	marriage	marriage	NN	O	5	compound
5	statues	statue	NNS	O	12	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	12	punct
7	Katherine	Katherine	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Pouba	Pouba	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	Ashley	Ashley	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Tianen	Tianen	NNP	PERSON	8	conj
12	wrote	write	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	:	:	:	O	12	punct
14	``	``	``	O	12	punct
15	Males	male	NNS	O	18	nsubj
16	were	be	VBD	O	18	cop
17	more	more	RBR	O	18	advmod
18	likely	likely	JJ	O	12	ccomp
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	marry	marry	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	solely	solely	RB	O	20	advmod
22	for	for	IN	O	26	case
23	their	they	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
24	own	own	JJ	O	26	amod
25	personal	personal	JJ	O	26	amod
26	gratification	gratification	NN	O	20	nmod
27	or	or	CC	O	26	cc
28	for	for	IN	O	33	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	women	woman	NNS	O	33	nmod:poss
31	's	's	POS	O	30	case
32	reproduction	reproduction	NN	O	33	compound
33	abilities	ability	NNS	O	26	conj
34	.	.	.	O	12	punct
35	''	''	''	O	12	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	6	punct
2	Pouba	Pouba	NNP	LOCATION	6	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
5	Tianen	Tianen	NNP	PERSON	2	conj
6	97	97	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
7	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	6	punct
8	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
2	they	they	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	gave	give	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	an	a	DT	O	5	det
5	example	example	NN	O	3	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	13	mark
7	how	how	WRB	O	13	advmod
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	young	young	JJ	O	10	amod
10	girl	girl	NN	O	13	nsubjpass
11	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
12	be	be	VB	O	13	auxpass
13	treated	treat	VBN	O	5	acl
14	when	when	WRB	O	17	advmod
15	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	16	amod
16	time	time	NN	O	17	nsubj
17	married	marry	VBN	O	13	advcl
18	by	by	IN	O	19	mark
19	using	use	VBG	O	17	advcl
20	a	a	DT	O	22	det
21	one	one	CD	NUMBER	22	nummod
22	source	source	NN	O	19	dobj
23	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
24	they	they	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	explained	explain	VBD	O	17	conj
26	briefly	briefly	NN	O	25	advmod
27	that	that	IN	O	46	mark
28	a	a	DT	O	30	det
29	young	young	JJ	O	30	amod
30	girl	girl	NN	O	46	nsubj
31	without	without	IN	O	33	case
32	any	any	DT	O	33	det
33	experience	experience	NN	O	30	nmod
34	or	or	CC	O	33	cc
35	idea	idea	NN	O	33	conj
36	when	when	WRB	O	38	advmod
37	you	you	PRP	O	38	nsubj
38	gave	give	VBD	O	33	acl:relcl
39	her	she	PRP	O	38	dobj
40	to	to	TO	O	42	case
41	a	a	DT	O	42	det
42	man	man	NN	O	38	nmod
43	he	he	PRP	O	46	nsubj
44	will	will	MD	O	46	aux
45	be	be	VB	O	46	cop
46	amorous	amorous	JJ	O	25	ccomp
47	and	and	CC	O	46	cc
48	jealous	jealous	JJ	O	46	conj
49	and	and	CC	O	46	cc
50	he	he	PRP	O	51	nsubj
51	aims	aim	VBZ	O	46	conj
52	to	to	TO	O	53	mark
53	destroy	destroy	VB	O	51	xcomp
54	her	she	PRP$	O	55	nmod:poss
55	innocence	innocence	NN	O	53	dobj
56	and	and	CC	O	55	cc
57	her	she	PRP$	O	58	nmod:poss
58	affections	affection	NNS	O	55	conj
59	to	to	TO	O	60	mark
60	separate	separate	VB	O	53	xcomp
61	her	she	PRP$	O	60	dobj
62	from	from	IN	O	64	case
63	the	the	DT	O	64	det
64	world	world	NN	O	60	nmod
65	and	and	CC	O	46	cc
66	even	even	RB	O	46	advmod
67	from	from	IN	O	69	case
68	her	she	PRP$	O	69	nmod:poss
69	mother	mother	NN	O	3	nmod
70	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Katherine	Katherine	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pouba	Pouba	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	Ashley	Ashley	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Tianen	Tianen	NNP	PERSON	2	conj
6	commented	comment	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	on	on	IN	O	9	case
8	this	this	DT	O	9	det
9	example	example	NN	O	6	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
11	they	they	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	said	say	VBD	O	6	conj
13	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
14	this	this	DT	O	15	det
15	example	example	NN	O	16	nsubj
16	shows	show	VBZ	O	12	ccomp
17	``	``	``	O	16	punct
18	How	how	WRB	O	24	advmod
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	wife	wife	NN	O	23	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	sole	sole	JJ	O	23	amod
23	purpose	purpose	NN	O	24	nsubj
24	was	be	VBD	O	16	xcomp
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	please	please	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	man	man	NN	O	26	dobj
29	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	role	role	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	woman	woman	NN	O	2	nmod
6	once	once	IN	DATE	9	mark
7	she	she	PRP	O	9	nsubjpass
8	was	be	VBD	O	9	auxpass
9	married	marry	VBN	O	5	dep
10	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
11	from	from	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	role	role	NN	O	10	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	an	a	DT	O	16	det
16	individual	individual	JJ	O	13	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	21	case
18	her	she	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	husband	husband	NN	O	21	nmod:poss
20	's	's	POS	O	19	case
21	possession	possession	NN	O	10	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	10	punct
23	''	''	''	O	10	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	6	punct
2	Pouba	Pouba	NNP	LOCATION	6	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
5	Tianen	Tianen	NNP	PERSON	2	conj
6	97	97	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
7	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	6	punct
8	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Similar	similar	JJ	O	10	nsubj
2	to	to	TO	O	4	case
3	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	4	compound
4	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	1	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	male	male	JJ	O	8	amod
8	society	society	NN	O	4	appos
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	aux
10	looking	look	VBG	O	0	ROOT
11	at	at	IN	O	14	case
12	women	woman	NNS	O	14	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	charms	charm	NNS	O	10	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	``	``	``	O	2	punct
5	You	you	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	have	have	VBP	O	2	ccomp
7	a	a	DT	O	10	det
8	great	great	JJ	O	10	amod
9	big	big	JJ	O	10	amod
10	nose	nose	NN	O	6	dobj
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	fat	fat	JJ	O	13	amod
13	legs	leg	NNS	O	10	conj
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	/	/	:	O	4	punct
2	She	she	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
4	healthy	healthy	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	tested	test	VBN	O	4	acl
7	intelligent	intelligent	JJ	O	6	xcomp
8	,	,	,	O	4	punct
9	/	/	:	O	10	punct
10	Possessed	possess	VBN	O	4	dep
11	strong	strong	JJ	O	12	amod
12	arms	arm	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
14	back	back	RB	O	12	advmod
15	,	,	,	O	12	punct
16	/	/	:	O	10	punct
17	abundant	abundant	JJ	O	19	amod
18	sexual	sexual	JJ	O	19	amod
19	drive	drive	NN	O	4	dobj
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	manual	manual	NN	O	22	compound
22	dexterity	dexterity	NN	O	19	conj
23	.	.	.	O	19	punct
24	''	''	''	O	19	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Piercy	piercy	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	194	194	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	obvious	obvious	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	society	society	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	looks	look	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
8	for	for	IN	O	11	case
9	its	its	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
10	own	own	JJ	O	11	amod
11	gratification	gratification	NN	O	7	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	3	neg
2	only	only	RB	O	3	advmod
3	this	this	DT	O	8	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
6	also	also	RB	O	7	advmod
7	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
8	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	society	society	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	aux
13	asking	ask	VBG	O	8	ccomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	women	woman	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	do	do	VB	O	13	xcomp
18	many	many	JJ	O	19	amod
19	things	thing	NNS	O	21	nsubj
20	must	must	MD	O	21	aux
21	be	be	VB	O	17	ccomp
22	as	as	IN	O	25	mark
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	males	male	NNS	O	25	nsubj
25	want	want	VBP	O	21	advcl
26	her	she	PRP$	O	25	dobj
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	be	be	VB	O	25	xcomp
29	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	she	she	PRP	O	8	nsubj
6	must	must	MD	O	8	aux
7	be	be	VB	O	8	cop
8	shy	shy	JJ	O	0	ROOT
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	do	do	VBP	O	8	dep
11	exercises	exercise	NNS	O	10	dobj
12	,	,	,	O	8	punct
13	wheedle	wheedle	VB	O	8	dep
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	do	do	VB	O	13	conj
18	many	many	JJ	O	19	amod
19	things	thing	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Piercy	piercy	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	194	194	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	7	cc
2	at	at	IN	O	4	case
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	end	end	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	:	:	:	O	7	punct
9	``	``	``	O	7	punct
10	Does	do	VBZ	O	13	aux
11	n't	not	RB	O	13	neg
12	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	look	look	VB	O	7	parataxis
14	pretty	pretty	RB	O	13	advmod
15	?	?	.	O	13	punct

1	Everyone	everyone	NN	O	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	/	/	:	O	4	punct
4	Consummation	Consummation	NNP	O	2	dep
5	at	at	IN	O	13	mark
6	last	last	JJ	O	13	nsubj
7	/	/	:	O	10	punct
8	to	to	TO	O	10	case
9	every	every	DT	O	10	det
10	women	woman	NNS	O	6	nmod
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	happy	happy	JJ	O	6	amod
13	ending	end	VBG	O	4	dep
14	/	/	:	O	4	punct
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct
16	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Piercy	piercy	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	195	195	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	indicates	indicate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	something	something	NN	O	2	dobj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	which	which	WDT	O	8	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	society	society	NN	O	3	acl:relcl
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	aux
10	envenoming	envenome	VBG	O	8	acl:relcl
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	distorting	distort	VBG	O	10	conj
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	girls	girl	NNS	O	16	nmod:poss
15	'	'	POS	O	14	case
16	thinking	thinking	NN	O	12	dobj
17	just	just	RB	O	19	advmod
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	have	have	VB	O	12	advcl
20	a	a	DT	O	21	det
21	happy	happy	JJ	O	19	dobj
22	ending	end	VBG	O	21	acl
23	by	by	IN	O	26	case
24	girls	girl	NNS	O	26	nmod:poss
25	'	'	POS	O	24	case
26	death	death	NN	O	22	nmod
27	or	or	CC	O	10	cc
28	having	have	VBG	O	10	conj
29	sexual	sexual	JJ	O	30	amod
30	intercourse	intercourse	NN	O	28	dobj
31	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	To	to	TO	O	2	mark
2	sum	sum	VB	O	7	advcl
3	up	up	RP	O	2	compound:prt
4	,	,	,	O	7	punct
5	Women	woman	NNS	O	7	nsubj
6	must	must	MD	O	7	aux
7	change	change	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	many	many	JJ	O	9	amod
9	things	thing	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	in	in	IN	O	13	mark
11	order	order	NN	O	10	mwe
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	please	please	VB	O	7	advcl
14	men	man	NNS	O	13	dobj
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	fit	fit	NN	O	14	conj
17	in	in	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	society	society	NN	O	13	nmod
20	as	as	IN	O	21	mark
21	wanted	want	VBN	O	13	advcl
22	by	by	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	society	society	NN	O	21	nmod
25	itself	itself	PRP	O	24	advmod
26	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	clear	clear	JJ	O	5	amod
5	effect	effect	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	7	case
7	feminism	feminism	NN	O	5	nmod
8	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
9	did	do	VBD	O	11	aux
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	change	change	VB	O	5	acl:relcl
12	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
13	still	still	RB	O	16	advmod
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	problem	problem	NN	O	16	nsubj
16	bothers	bother	VBZ	O	5	conj
17	Marge	Marge	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
18	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	16	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	4	amod
4	place	place	NN	O	23	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	23	punct
6	knowing	know	VBG	O	23	csubj
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	historical	historical	JJ	O	9	amod
9	period	period	NN	O	6	dobj
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	cultural	cultural	JJ	O	13	amod
13	situation	situation	NN	O	9	conj
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	which	which	WDT	O	21	nmod
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	text	text	NN	O	21	nsubj
18	or	or	CC	O	17	cc
19	poem	poem	NN	O	17	conj
20	had	have	VBD	O	21	aux
21	written	write	VBN	O	13	acl:relcl
22	can	can	MD	O	23	aux
23	change	change	VB	O	0	ROOT
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	way	way	NN	O	27	nsubj
26	you	you	PRP	O	27	dep
27	analyzing	analyze	VBG	O	23	xcomp
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	text	text	NN	O	27	dobj
30	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
31	shape	shape	VB	O	23	conj
32	your	you	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	understanding	understanding	NN	O	31	dobj
34	into	into	IN	O	38	mark
35	what	what	WP	O	38	dobj
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	author	author	NN	O	38	nsubj
38	means	mean	VBZ	O	31	advcl
39	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	have	have	VBP	O	3	aux
3	shown	show	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
5	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Doll	Doll	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	implies	imply	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
8	to	to	TO	O	10	case
9	many	many	JJ	O	10	amod
10	symbols	symbol	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	manifestations	manifestation	NNS	O	10	conj
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	feminism	feminism	NN	O	10	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	2	case
2	Instance	Instance	NNP	O	11	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	11	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	girl	girl	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	Doll	Doll	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
9	had	have	VBD	O	11	aux
10	been	be	VBN	O	11	auxpass
11	presented	present	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	13	case
13	dolls	doll	NNS	O	11	nmod
14	:	:	:	O	11	punct
15	``	``	``	O	11	punct
16	And	and	CC	O	11	cc
17	presented	present	VBN	O	20	dep
18	dolls	doll	NNS	O	17	dobj
19	that	that	WDT	O	20	nsubj
20	did	do	VBD	O	11	conj
21	pee-pee	pee-pee	JJ	O	20	dobj
22	/	/	:	O	26	punct
23	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
24	miniature	miniature	JJ	O	26	amod
25	GE	GE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	compound
26	stoves	stove	NNS	O	21	dep
27	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
28	irons	iron	NNS	O	26	conj
29	/	/	:	O	26	punct
30	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
31	wee	wee	JJ	O	32	amod
32	lipsticks	lipstick	NNS	O	34	dep
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	color	color	NN	O	11	conj
35	of	of	IN	O	37	case
36	cherry	cherry	NN	O	37	compound
37	candy	candy	NN	O	34	nmod
38	.	.	.	O	11	punct
39	''	''	''	O	11	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Piercy	piercy	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	194	194	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Actually	actually	RB	O	11	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	11	punct
3	these	these	DT	O	4	det
4	dolls	doll	NNS	O	11	nsubj
5	that	that	WDT	O	6	nsubj
6	provided	provide	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
7	to	to	TO	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	girl	girl	NN	O	6	nmod
10	are	be	VBP	O	11	cop
11	symbols	symbol	NNS	O	0	ROOT
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	feminism	feminism	NN	O	11	nmod
14	which	which	WDT	O	17	dobj
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	family	family	NN	O	17	nsubj
17	want	want	VBP	O	11	acl:relcl
18	from	from	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	girl	girl	NN	O	17	nmod
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	grew	grow	VBD	O	20	acl
23	up	up	RP	O	22	compound:prt
24	into	into	IN	O	25	case
25	them	they	PRP	O	22	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	intend	intend	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	show	show	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	girl	girl	NN	O	4	dobj
7	what	what	WDT	O	10	dobj
8	she	she	PRP	O	10	nsubj
9	must	must	MD	O	10	aux
10	learn	learn	VB	O	6	acl:relcl
11	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
12	what	what	WP	O	14	nsubj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	work	work	VB	O	6	acl
15	,	,	,	O	6	punct
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	cocking	cocking	NN	O	6	conj
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	ironing	ironing	NN	O	17	conj
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Moreover	moreover	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	it	it	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	teaches	teach	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	girl	girl	NN	O	4	dobj
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	adjust	adjust	VB	O	6	acl
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	outfits	outfits	NN	O	8	dobj
11	in	in	IN	O	14	mark
12	order	order	NN	O	11	mwe
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	fit	fit	VB	O	8	advcl
15	on	on	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	society	society	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	male	male	JJ	O	3	amod
3	society	society	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
5	present	present	JJ	DATE	35	ccomp
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	poem	poem	NN	O	5	nmod
9	in	in	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	classmate	classmate	NN	O	12	compound
12	character	character	NN	O	8	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	classmate	classmate	NN	O	18	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	18	aux
18	asking	ask	VBG	O	5	conj
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	girl	girl	NN	O	18	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	act	act	VB	O	20	acl
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	behave	behave	VB	O	22	conj
25	in	in	IN	O	27	case
26	certain	certain	JJ	O	27	amod
27	ways	way	NNS	O	22	nmod
28	as	as	IN	O	30	mark
29	I	I	PRP	O	30	nsubj
30	mentioned	mention	VBD	O	22	advcl
31	previously	previously	RB	DATE	30	advmod
32	,	,	,	O	35	punct
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	society	society	NN	O	35	nsubj
35	want	want	VBP	O	0	ROOT
36	from	from	IN	O	38	case
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	girl	girl	NN	O	35	nmod
39	to	to	TO	O	41	mark
40	be	be	VB	O	41	cop
41	someone	someone	NN	O	38	acl
42	else	else	RB	O	41	advmod
43	rather	rather	RB	O	41	cc
44	than	than	IN	O	43	mwe
45	her	she	PRP$	O	47	nmod:poss
46	real	real	JJ	O	47	amod
47	character	character	NN	O	41	conj
48	.	.	.	O	35	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	last	last	JJ	O	4	amod
4	place	place	NN	O	8	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	poem	poem	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	titled	title	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	as	as	IN	O	12	case
10	``	``	``	O	12	punct
11	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	12	compound
12	Doll	Doll	NNP	O	8	nmod
13	''	''	''	O	12	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
15	no	no	DT	O	17	neg
16	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	17	compound
17	dolls	doll	NNS	O	18	nsubj
18	appear	appear	VBP	O	8	conj
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	poem	poem	NN	O	18	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	so	so	RB	O	25	advmod
24	what	what	WP	O	25	nsubj
25	is	be	VBZ	O	21	acl:relcl
26	that	that	DT	O	27	nsubj
27	means	mean	VBZ	O	25	ccomp
28	?	?	.	O	8	punct

1	An	a	DT	O	3	det
2	academic	academic	JJ	O	3	amod
3	research	research	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	called	call	VBN	O	3	acl
5	``	``	``	O	6	punct
6	Does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	10	compound
8	Make	Make	NNP	O	10	compound
9	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	10	compound
10	Want	Want	NNP	O	6	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
12	Be	be	VB	O	13	cop
13	Thin	Thin	NNP	O	6	xcomp
14	?	?	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Effect	effect	NN	O	49	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	Experimental	experimental	JJ	O	5	amod
5	Exposure	exposure	NN	O	2	nmod
6	to	to	TO	O	7	case
7	Images	image	NNS	O	5	acl
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	Dolls	doll	NNS	O	7	nmod
10	on	on	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	Body	Body	NNP	O	13	compound
13	Image	image	NN	O	9	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	5	5	CD	NUMBER	13	nmod
16	-	-	:	O	7	punct
17	to	to	TO	O	19	case
18	8-Year-Old	8-year-old	JJ	DURATION	19	amod
19	Girl	Girl	NNP	O	7	nmod
20	''	''	''	O	2	punct
21	created	create	VBN	O	2	acl
22	by	by	IN	O	25	case
23	Dr.	Dr.	NNP	O	25	compound
24	Helga	Helga	NNP	PERSON	25	compound
25	Dittmar	Dittmar	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	Dr.	Dr.	NNP	O	29	compound
28	Suzanne	Suzanne	NNP	PERSON	29	compound
29	Ive	Ive	NNP	PERSON	25	conj
30	from	from	IN	O	31	case
31	University	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	nmod
32	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	33	case
33	Sussex	Sussex	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	nmod
34	,	,	,	O	25	punct
35	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
36	Dr.	Dr.	NNP	O	38	compound
37	Emma	Emma	NNP	PERSON	38	compound
38	Halliwell	Halliwell	NNP	PERSON	25	conj
39	from	from	IN	O	40	case
40	University	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	nmod
41	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	42	case
42	West	West	NNP	ORGANIZATION	40	nmod
43	of	of	IN	O	45	case
44	England	England	NNP	LOCATION	45	compound
45	talks	talk	NNS	O	42	nmod
46	about	about	IN	O	48	case
47	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	48	compound
48	dolls	doll	NNS	O	21	nmod
49	affect	affect	VBP	O	0	ROOT
50	and	and	CC	O	49	cc
51	influence	influence	VBP	O	49	conj
52	on	on	IN	O	56	case
53	girls	girl	NNS	O	56	nmod:poss
54	'	'	POS	O	53	case
55	body	body	NN	O	56	compound
56	image	image	NN	O	49	nmod
57	.	.	.	O	49	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	facts	fact	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	that	that	WDT	O	6	nsubj
6	revealed	reveal	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	research	research	NN	O	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	``	``	``	O	9	punct
12	99	99	CD	PERCENT	13	nummod
13	%	%	NN	PERCENT	9	dep
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	3	3	LS	NUMBER	13	nmod
16	-	-	:	O	9	punct
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	10-year-olds	10-year-old	NNS	DURATION	6	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	22	compound
22	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	18	nmod
23	own	own	VB	O	6	ccomp
24	at	at	IN	O	25	case
25	least	least	JJS	O	26	nmod:npmod
26	one	one	CD	NUMBER	23	dobj
27	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	28	compound
28	Doll	Doll	NNP	O	26	dep
29	.	.	.	O	1	punct
30	''	''	''	O	1	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Dittmar	Dittmar	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	et.al	et.al	NNP	O	2	dep
4	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	283	283	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
2	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	1	punct
3	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Yet	yet	RB	O	7	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	4	compound
4	doll	doll	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	very	very	RB	O	7	advmod
7	thin	thin	JJ	O	0	ROOT
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	weight	weight	NN	O	16	nsubj
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	body	body	NN	O	10	conj
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	fact	fact	NN	O	10	nmod
15	are	be	VBP	O	16	cop
16	unobtainable	unobtainable	JJ	O	7	conj
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	also	also	RB	O	19	advmod
19	unhealthy	unhealthy	JJ	O	16	conj
20	!	!	.	O	7	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	study	study	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	11	cop
4	about	about	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	impact	impact	NN	O	11	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	exposure	exposure	NN	O	6	nmod
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	new	new	JJ	O	11	amod
11	doll	doll	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	shaped	shape	VBN	O	11	acl
13	manually	manually	RB	O	14	advmod
14	and	and	CC	O	12	advmod
15	accurately	accurately	RB	O	14	advmod
16	by	by	IN	O	20	case
17	the	the	DT	O	20	det
18	American	american	JJ	ORGANIZATION	20	amod
19	Dietetic	Dietetic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
20	Association	Association	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	nmod
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	enhance	enhance	VB	O	12	xcomp
23	a	a	DT	O	26	det
24	positive	positive	JJ	O	26	amod
25	body	body	NN	O	26	compound
26	image	image	NN	O	22	dobj
27	for	for	IN	O	28	case
28	girls	girl	NNS	O	22	nmod
29	,	,	,	O	28	punct
30	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
31	then	then	RB	O	34	advmod
32	exposure	exposure	NN	O	34	compound
33	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	34	compound
34	doll	doll	NN	O	28	conj
35	after	after	IN	O	36	case
36	that	that	DT	O	22	nmod
37	to	to	TO	O	39	case
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	girls	girl	NNS	O	36	nmod
40	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	recent	recent	JJ	O	3	amod
3	result	result	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
6	``	``	``	O	11	punct
7	The	the	DT	O	8	det
8	desire	desire	NN	O	11	nsubj
9	for	for	IN	O	10	case
10	thinness	thinness	NN	O	8	nmod
11	emerges	emerge	VBZ	O	4	ccomp
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	girls	girl	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	around	around	IN	O	16	case
16	age	age	NN	O	14	nmod
17	6	6	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
18	''	''	''	O	11	punct
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
20	Dittmar	Dittmar	NNP	PERSON	11	dep
21	et.al	et.al	JJ	O	22	amod
22	.283	.283	NN	NUMBER	20	dep
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	To	to	TO	O	2	mark
2	sum	sum	VB	O	7	advcl
3	up	up	RP	O	2	compound:prt
4	,	,	,	O	7	punct
5	young	young	JJ	O	6	amod
6	girls	girl	NNS	O	7	nsubj
7	show	show	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	body	body	NN	O	9	compound
9	dissatisfaction	dissatisfaction	NN	O	7	dobj
10	after	after	IN	O	11	case
11	exposure	exposure	NN	O	7	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	doll	doll	NN	O	11	nmod
15	but	but	CC	O	16	cc
16	not	not	RB	O	11	cc
17	after	after	IN	O	19	case
18	Emma	Emma	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	doll	doll	NN	O	11	conj
20	because	because	IN	O	23	mark
21	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	22	compound
22	doll	doll	NN	O	23	nsubj
23	represent	represent	VBP	O	7	advcl
24	a	a	DT	O	28	det
25	destructive	destructive	JJ	O	26	amod
26	thin	thin	JJ	O	28	amod
27	body	body	NN	O	28	compound
28	ideal	ideal	NN	O	23	dobj
29	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
4	can	can	MD	O	5	aux
5	lead	lead	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	8	case
7	tough	tough	JJ	O	8	amod
8	aftereffects	aftereffect	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	such	such	JJ	O	13	case
10	as	as	IN	O	9	mwe
11	``	``	``	O	13	punct
12	depressed	depressed	JJ	O	13	amod
13	effect	effect	NN	O	8	nmod
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	unhealthy	unhealthy	JJ	O	17	amod
16	eating	eating	NN	O	17	compound
17	behaviors	behavior	NNS	O	13	conj
18	,	,	,	O	13	punct
19	particularly	particularly	RB	O	13	advmod
20	dieting	dieting	NN	O	13	dep
21	,	,	,	O	8	punct
22	which	which	WDT	O	29	nsubj
23	,	,	,	O	29	punct
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	turn	turn	NN	O	29	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	29	punct
27	is	be	VBZ	O	29	cop
28	a	a	DT	O	29	det
29	precursor	precursor	NN	O	8	acl:relcl
30	of	of	IN	O	31	mark
31	eating	eat	VBG	O	29	acl
32	disorder	disorder	NN	O	31	dobj
33	.	.	.	O	5	punct
34	''	''	''	O	5	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Dittmar	Dittmar	NNP	PERSON	18	dep
3	et.al	et.al	JJ	O	4	amod
4	.290	.290	NN	NUMBER	2	dep
5	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
6	That	that	WDT	O	9	dobj
7	what	what	WP	O	9	nsubj
8	had	have	VBD	O	9	aux
9	happened	happen	VBN	O	18	advcl
10	exactly	exactly	RB	O	9	advmod
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	poem	poem	NN	O	9	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	18	punct
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	classmate	classmate	NN	O	18	nsubjpass
17	was	be	VBD	O	18	auxpass
18	annoyed	annoy	VBN	O	35	csubj
19	from	from	IN	O	22	case
20	her	she	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
21	fat	fat	JJ	O	22	amod
22	legs	leg	NNS	O	18	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	her	she	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
25	big	big	JJ	O	26	amod
26	nose	nose	NN	O	22	conj
27	,	,	,	O	18	punct
28	so	so	IN	O	18	dep
29	she	she	PRP	O	30	nsubj
30	ended	end	VBD	O	18	parataxis
31	up	up	RP	O	30	compound:prt
32	by	by	IN	O	34	case
33	``	``	``	O	34	punct
34	She	she	PRP	O	30	nmod
35	cut	cut	VBD	O	0	ROOT
36	off	off	RP	O	35	compound:prt
37	her	she	PRP$	O	38	nmod:poss
38	nose	nose	NN	O	35	dobj
39	and	and	CC	O	38	cc
40	her	she	PRP$	O	41	nmod:poss
41	legs	leg	NNS	O	38	conj
42	/	/	:	O	44	punct
43	and	and	CC	O	44	nsubj
44	offered	offer	VBD	O	41	dep
45	them	they	PRP	O	44	dobj
46	up	up	RP	O	44	compound:prt
47	.	.	.	O	35	punct
48	''	''	''	O	35	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Piercy	piercy	NN	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	194	194	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	To	to	TO	O	2	mark
2	go	go	VB	O	14	advcl
3	back	back	RB	O	2	advmod
4	for	for	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	previous	previous	JJ	O	7	amod
7	question	question	NN	O	2	nmod
8	about	about	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	title	title	NN	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	14	punct
12	we	we	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	can	can	MD	O	14	aux
14	understand	understand	VB	O	0	ROOT
15	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
16	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	doll	doll	NN	O	19	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	19	cop
19	unrealistic	unrealistic	JJ	O	14	ccomp
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	has	have	VBZ	O	19	conj
22	strange	strange	JJ	O	23	amod
23	perfection	perfection	NN	O	21	dobj
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	thinness	thinness	NN	O	23	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	hairstyle	hairstyle	NN	O	25	conj
28	,	,	,	O	25	punct
29	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
30	beauty	beauty	NN	O	25	conj
31	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	4	advmod
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	girls	girl	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	play	play	VBP	O	9	advcl
5	with	with	IN	O	7	case
6	this	this	DT	O	7	det
7	toy	toy	NN	O	4	nmod
8	they	they	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	want	want	VBP	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
11	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
12	like	like	IN	O	13	case
13	it	it	PRP	O	9	xcomp
14	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
2	it	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	infers	infer	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	society	society	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	want	want	VBP	O	3	ccomp
8	from	from	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	girls	girl	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
12	be	be	VB	O	14	cop
13	like	like	IN	O	14	case
14	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	PERSON	7	xcomp
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	3	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	3	punct
3	using	use	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Doll	Doll	NNP	O	3	dobj
6	corresponds	correspond	VBZ	O	3	dep
7	with	with	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	poem	poem	NN	O	10	compound
10	theme	theme	NN	O	6	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	conclusion	conclusion	NN	O	6	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	6	punct
4	it	it	PRP	O	6	nsubjpass
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	auxpass
6	seen	see	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
8	feminism	feminism	NN	O	9	compound
9	manifestations	manifestation	NNS	O	12	nsubj
10	did	do	VBD	O	12	aux
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	disappear	disappear	VB	O	6	ccomp
13	completely	completely	RB	O	12	advmod
14	;	;	:	O	6	punct
15	some	some	DT	O	19	nsubj
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	them	they	PRP	O	15	nmod
18	had	have	VBD	O	19	aux
19	gone	go	VBN	O	6	conj
20	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
21	some	some	DT	O	26	nsubj
22	of	of	IN	O	23	case
23	them	they	PRP	O	21	nmod
24	is	be	VBZ	O	26	cop
25	still	still	RB	O	26	advmod
26	present	present	JJ	DATE	6	conj
27	in	in	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	time	time	NN	O	26	nmod
30	of	of	IN	O	31	case
31	Piercy	Piercy	NNP	PERSON	29	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Moreover	moreover	RB	O	3	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	3	punct
3	looking	look	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	outside	outside	JJ	O	6	amod
6	sources	source	NNS	O	3	nmod
7	talk	talk	VBP	O	3	dep
8	about	about	IN	O	19	mark
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	historical	historical	JJ	O	11	amod
11	period	period	NN	O	19	nsubj
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	which	which	WDT	O	17	nmod
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	text	text	NN	O	17	nsubj
16	had	have	VBD	O	17	aux
17	written	write	VBN	O	11	acl:relcl
18	would	would	MD	O	19	aux
19	change	change	VB	O	7	advcl
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	shape	shape	VB	O	19	conj
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	way	way	NN	O	19	dobj
24	we	we	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	think	think	VBP	O	23	acl:relcl
26	of	of	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	text	text	NN	O	25	nmod
29	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
30	clearly	clearly	RB	O	31	advmod
31	enhance	enhance	VBP	O	25	conj
32	our	we	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	understanding	understanding	NN	O	31	dobj
34	to	to	TO	O	36	case
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	text	text	NN	O	31	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	external	external	JJ	O	3	amod
3	sources	source	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	help	help	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	us	we	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	imagine	imagine	VB	O	4	ccomp
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	visualize	visualize	VB	O	6	conj
9	images	image	NNS	O	6	dobj
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	themes	theme	NNS	O	9	conj
12	in	in	IN	O	15	case
13	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	15	compound
14	Doll	Doll	NNP	O	15	compound
15	poem	poem	NN	O	6	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Dittmar	Dittmar	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Helga	Helga	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	Emma	Emma	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Halliwell	Halliwell	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
7	,	,	,	O	3	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
9	Suzanne	Suzanne	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
10	Ive	Ive	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
11	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	Barbie	Barbie	NNP	O	6	compound
4	Make	Make	NNP	O	6	compound
5	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Want	Want	NNP	O	2	dobj
7	To	to	TO	O	9	mark
8	Be	be	VB	O	9	cop
9	Thin	Thin	NNP	O	2	xcomp
10	?	?	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	13	det
2	Effect	effect	NN	O	13	dep
3	Of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	Experimental	experimental	JJ	O	5	amod
5	Exposure	exposure	NN	O	2	nmod
6	To	to	TO	O	7	case
7	Images	image	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	Of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	Dolls	doll	NNS	O	2	nmod
10	On	on	IN	O	12	case
11	The	the	DT	O	12	det
12	Body	Body	NNP	O	2	nmod
13	Image	image	NN	O	0	ROOT
14	Of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	5	5	CD	NUMBER	13	nmod
16	-	-	:	O	15	punct
17	To	to	TO	O	19	case
18	8-Year-Old	8-year-old	JJ	DURATION	19	amod
19	Girls	girl	NNS	O	15	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	13	punct
21	''	''	''	O	13	punct

1	Developmental	developmental	JJ	O	2	amod
2	Psychology	psychology	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	42.2	42.2	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	5	punct
5	2006	2006	CD	DATE	2	appos
6	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	5	punct
7	:	:	:	O	2	punct
8	283-292	283-292	CD	NUMBER	2	dep
9	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Academic	Academic	NNP	O	2	nsubj
2	Search	search	VB	O	0	ROOT
3	Complete	complete	JJ	O	2	dobj
4	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Web	web	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	5	5	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	Nov.	Nov.	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2014	2014	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Pouba	Pouba	NNP	LOCATION	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Katherine	Katherine	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
6	Ashley	Ashley	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Tianen	Tianen	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
8	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Lunacy	lunacy	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	The19th	The19th	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Century	Century	NNP	DURATION	2	nmod
6	:	:	:	O	2	punct
7	Women	Women	NNP	O	9	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	Admission	admission	NN	O	2	dep
10	to	to	TO	O	11	case
11	Asylums	asylum	NNS	O	9	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	14	compound
14	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	LOCATION	16	case
16	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct
18	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	Rep.	Rep.	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Vol	Vol	NNP	O	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	1	1	LS	NUMBER	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Oshkosh	Oshkosh	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	:	:	:	O	1	punct
3	University	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	1	dep
4	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	6	case
5	Wisconsin	Wisconsin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Oshkosh	Oshkosh	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	May	May	NNP	DATE	6	appos
9	2006	2006	CD	DATE	8	nummod
10	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Pp.	Pp.	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	95-103	95-103	CD	NUMBER	1	dep
3	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Print	print	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

