1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	``	``	``	O	4	punct
3	The	the	DT	O	4	det
4	Cask	Cask	NNP	O	14	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	Amontillado	Amontillado	NNP	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	14	punct
8	''	''	''	O	14	punct
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	narrator	narrator	NN	O	14	nsubj
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	Montresor	Montresor	NNP	PERSON	10	appos
13	,	,	,	O	10	punct
14	tells	tell	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
15	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
16	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	uses	use	VBZ	O	14	ccomp
18	different	different	JJ	O	19	amod
19	tricks	trick	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	revenge	revenge	VB	O	17	advcl
22	on	on	IN	O	23	case
23	Fortunato	Fortunato	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod
24	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
25	shows	show	VBZ	O	17	conj
26	that	that	IN	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	inner	inner	JJ	O	29	amod
29	darkness	darkness	NN	O	25	nmod
30	of	of	IN	O	33	case
31	Montresor	Montresor	NNP	PERSON	33	nmod:poss
32	's	's	POS	O	31	case
33	mind	mind	NN	O	29	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	People	people	NNS	O	3	nsubj
2	usually	usually	RB	O	3	advmod
3	use	use	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	their	they	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	smartness	smartness	NN	O	3	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	overcome	overcome	VB	O	5	acl
8	dilemmas	dilemma	NNS	O	7	dobj
9	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
10	win	win	VB	O	7	conj
11	competition	competition	NN	O	10	dobj
12	out	out	IN	O	10	advmod
13	of	of	IN	O	17	case
14	the	the	DT	O	17	det
15	least	least	JJS	O	16	dep
16	possible	possible	JJ	O	17	amod
17	way	way	NN	O	12	nmod
18	;	;	:	O	3	punct
19	however	however	RB	O	26	advmod
20	,	,	,	O	26	punct
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	overuse	overuse	NN	O	26	nsubj
23	of	of	IN	O	24	case
24	smartness	smartness	NN	O	22	nmod
25	will	will	MD	O	26	aux
26	overthrow	overthrow	VB	O	3	parataxis
27	one	one	CD	NUMBER	26	dobj
28	's	's	POS	O	27	case
29	self-conscious	self-conscious	JJ	O	27	amod
30	about	about	IN	O	34	mark
31	what	what	WP	O	34	dobj
32	they	they	PRP	O	34	nsubj
33	really	really	RB	O	34	advmod
34	want	want	VBP	O	27	acl
35	,	,	,	O	27	punct
36	which	which	WDT	O	37	nsubj
37	promotes	promote	VBZ	O	27	acl:relcl
38	their	they	PRP$	O	39	nmod:poss
39	ambitions	ambition	NNS	O	37	dobj
40	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	``	``	``	O	4	punct
3	The	the	DT	O	4	det
4	Notorious	notorious	JJ	O	14	nmod
5	Jumping	jump	VBG	O	4	acl
6	Frog	frog	NN	O	5	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	Calaveras	Calaveras	NNP	LOCATION	9	compound
9	County	County	NNP	LOCATION	4	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	14	punct
11	''	''	''	O	14	punct
12	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Twain	Twain	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
14	writes	write	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	story	story	NN	O	14	dobj
17	about	about	IN	O	19	case
18	Jim	Jim	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	16	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	who	who	WP	O	22	nsubj
22	likes	like	VBZ	O	19	acl:relcl
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	bet	bet	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	on	on	IN	O	26	case
26	everything	everything	NN	O	24	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	22	punct
28	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
29	satirize	satirize	VB	O	22	xcomp
30	pugnacious	pugnacious	JJ	O	31	amod
31	people	people	NNS	O	29	dobj
32	in	in	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	DATE	34	det
34	1860s	1860	NNS	DATE	29	nmod
35	who	who	WP	O	36	nsubj
36	use	use	VBP	O	34	acl:relcl
37	tricks	trick	NNS	O	36	dobj
38	and	and	CC	O	37	cc
39	cunningness	cunningness	NN	O	37	conj
40	to	to	TO	O	41	mark
41	win	win	VB	O	36	advcl
42	over	over	IN	O	44	case
43	unfair	unfair	JJ	O	44	amod
44	acquisition	acquisition	NN	O	41	nmod
45	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	3	mark
2	people	people	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	plagiarize	plagiarize	VBP	O	20	advcl
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	cheat	cheat	VBP	O	3	conj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	obtain	obtain	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	good	good	JJ	O	9	amod
9	grades	grade	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	or	or	CC	O	9	cc
11	honor	honor	NN	O	9	conj
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	contest	contest	NN	O	7	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	20	punct
15	they	they	PRP	O	20	nsubj
16	are	be	VBP	O	20	cop
17	always	always	RB	O	20	advmod
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	risk	risk	NN	O	0	ROOT
21	of	of	IN	O	22	mark
22	getting	get	VBG	O	20	acl
23	caught	catch	VBN	O	22	xcomp
24	or	or	CC	O	23	cc
25	deceived	deceive	VBN	O	23	conj
26	by	by	IN	O	28	case
27	other	other	JJ	O	28	amod
28	people	people	NNS	O	25	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	Gambling	gambling	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	auxpass
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	supposed	suppose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
6	be	be	VB	O	9	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	main	main	JJ	O	9	amod
9	theme	theme	NN	O	4	xcomp
10	of	of	IN	O	14	case
11	one	one	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	person	person	NN	O	14	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	life	life	NN	O	9	nmod
15	;	;	:	O	4	punct
16	however	however	RB	O	20	advmod
17	,	,	,	O	20	punct
18	Jim	Jim	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	20	nsubj
20	uses	use	VBZ	O	4	parataxis
21	gambling	gamble	VBG	O	20	dobj
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	make	make	VB	O	20	xcomp
24	fun	fun	NN	O	23	dobj
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	others	other	NNS	O	24	nmod
27	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
28	show	show	VBP	O	20	conj
29	disrespect	disrespect	NN	O	28	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Simon	Simon	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Wheeler	Wheeler	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	describes	describe	VBZ	O	25	ccomp
4	Jim	Jim	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	3	dobj
6	as	as	IN	O	7	case
7	someone	someone	NN	O	5	nmod
8	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
9	always	always	RB	O	10	advmod
10	likes	like	VBZ	O	3	dep
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	bet	bet	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	on	on	IN	O	14	case
14	anything	anything	NN	O	12	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
16	whenever	whenever	WRB	O	19	advmod
17	``	``	``	O	19	punct
18	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	got	get	VBD	O	10	conj
20	a	a	DT	O	21	det
21	bet	bet	NN	O	19	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	25	punct
23	he	he	PRP	O	25	nsubj
24	was	be	VBD	O	25	cop
25	satisfied	satisfied	JJ	O	0	ROOT
26	''	''	''	O	25	punct
27	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	28	punct
28	2	2	LS	NUMBER	25	dep
29	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	28	punct
30	.	.	.	O	25	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	satisfying	satisfying	JJ	O	3	dep
3	feelings	feeling	NNS	O	8	dep
4	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	8	aux
6	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	pride	pride	NN	O	11	advcl
9	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	permanently	permanently	RB	O	11	advmod
11	receives	receive	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	but	but	CC	O	11	cc
14	some	some	DT	O	16	det
15	unreal	unreal	JJ	O	16	amod
16	honor	honor	NN	O	11	conj
17	that	that	WDT	O	18	nsubj
18	exists	exist	VBZ	O	16	acl:relcl
19	within	within	IN	O	21	case
20	his	he	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	mind	mind	NN	O	16	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	carries	carry	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	such	such	JJ	O	5	amod
4	artificial	artificial	JJ	O	5	amod
5	pride	pride	NN	O	2	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	which	which	WDT	O	8	nsubj
8	drives	drive	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
9	him	he	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	see	see	VB	O	8	ccomp
11	phenomenon	phenomenon	NN	O	10	dobj
12	without	without	IN	O	13	case
13	judgments	judgment	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	3	advmod
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	sees	see	VBZ	O	13	advcl
4	fighting	fight	VBG	O	3	xcomp
5	between	between	IN	O	6	case
6	dogs	dog	NNS	O	4	nmod
7	or	or	CC	O	6	cc
8	cats	cat	NNS	O	6	conj
9	,	,	,	O	13	punct
10	``	``	``	O	13	punct
11	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	'd	would	MD	O	13	aux
13	bet	bet	VB	O	0	ROOT
14	on	on	IN	O	15	case
15	it	it	PRP	O	13	nmod
16	''	''	''	O	15	punct
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	2	2	LS	NUMBER	13	dep
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
20	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	reason	reason	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	wants	want	VBZ	O	2	acl:relcl
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	bet	bet	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	events	event	NNS	O	6	dobj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
10	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
12	ambitious	ambitious	JJ	O	8	ccomp
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	likes	like	VBZ	O	12	conj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	show	show	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	off	off	RP	O	16	compound:prt
18	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	3	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	faces	face	VBZ	O	11	advcl
4	many	many	JJ	O	5	amod
5	competitions	competition	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	when	when	WRB	O	8	advmod
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	gambles	gamble	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
9	,	,	,	O	11	punct
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	becomes	become	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	little	little	JJ	O	14	nmod:npmod
14	rebellious	rebellious	JJ	O	11	xcomp
15	against	against	IN	O	16	case
16	others	other	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	11	punct
18	because	because	IN	O	20	mark
19	he	he	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	hates	hate	VBZ	O	11	advcl
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	lose	lose	VB	O	20	xcomp
23	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
2	disrespectful	disrespectful	JJ	O	3	amod
3	personality	personality	NN	O	12	nsubj
4	becomes	become	VBZ	O	3	dep
5	clear	clear	JJ	O	4	advmod
6	when	when	WRB	O	4	xcomp
7	''	''	''	O	4	punct
8	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	12	punct
9	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
10	'll	will	MD	O	12	aux
11	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	12	punct
12	resk	resk	NN	O	0	ROOT
13	two-and-a-half	two-and-a-half	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
14	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
15	Parson	Parson	NNP	PERSON	16	compound
16	Walker	Walker	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod:poss
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	wife	wife	NN	O	12	nmod
19	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	12	punct
20	do	do	VBP	O	12	dep
21	n't	not	RB	O	20	neg
22	anyway	anyway	RB	O	12	advmod
23	''	''	''	O	12	punct
24	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
25	2	2	LS	NUMBER	12	dep
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
27	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	Parson	Parson	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Walker	Walker	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	wife	wife	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	gets	get	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	sick	sick	JJ	O	5	xcomp
7	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	aux
9	getting	get	VBG	O	5	conj
10	better	better	RBR	O	9	advmod
11	,	,	,	O	5	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
13	everybody	everybody	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	thinks	think	VBZ	O	5	conj
15	she	she	PRP	O	23	nsubj
16	will	will	MD	O	23	aux
17	be	be	VB	O	23	cop
18	well	well	RB	O	23	advmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	but	but	CC	O	18	cc
21	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	18	conj
22	bets	bet	NNS	O	21	dep
23	money	money	NN	O	14	ccomp
24	that	that	IN	O	28	mark
25	she	she	PRP	O	28	nsubj
26	will	will	MD	O	28	aux
27	not	not	RB	O	28	neg
28	get	get	VB	O	23	ccomp
29	better	better	JJR	O	28	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	case	case	NN	O	9	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	5	mark
5	betting	bet	VBG	O	3	acl
6	,	,	,	O	9	punct
7	it	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
9	ordinary	ordinary	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	for	for	IN	O	11	case
11	people	people	NNS	O	9	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	bet	bet	VB	O	9	xcomp
14	on	on	IN	O	13	compound:prt
15	anything	anything	NN	O	13	dobj
16	but	but	CC	O	17	cc
17	not	not	RB	O	15	cc
18	other	other	JJ	O	21	nmod:poss
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	personal	personal	JJ	O	21	amod
21	issues	issue	NNS	O	15	conj
22	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	bet	bet	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	does	do	VBZ	O	2	acl:relcl
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
7	inconsiderate	inconsiderate	JJ	O	31	ccomp
8	because	because	IN	O	11	mark
9	people	people	NNS	O	11	nsubjpass
10	are	be	VBP	O	11	auxpass
11	worried	worry	VBN	O	7	advcl
12	about	about	IN	O	16	case
13	Parson	Parson	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Walker	Walker	NNP	PERSON	16	nmod:poss
15	's	's	POS	O	14	case
16	wife	wife	NN	O	11	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	7	punct
18	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
19	he	he	PRP	O	22	nsubj
20	does	do	VBZ	O	22	aux
21	not	not	RB	O	22	neg
22	take	take	VB	O	7	conj
23	serious	serious	JJ	O	22	xcomp
24	about	about	IN	O	25	case
25	it	it	PRP	O	22	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	22	punct
27	instead	instead	RB	O	22	advmod
28	,	,	,	O	31	punct
29	he	he	PRP	O	31	nsubj
30	is	be	VBZ	O	31	aux
31	scoffing	scoff	VBG	O	0	ROOT
32	at	at	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	people	people	NNS	O	31	nmod
35	who	who	WP	O	36	nsubj
36	care	care	VBP	O	34	acl:relcl
37	about	about	IN	O	38	case
38	her	she	PRP	O	36	nmod
39	.	.	.	O	31	punct

1	Wheeler	Wheeler	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	expresses	express	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	personality	personality	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod
7	through	through	IN	O	8	mark
8	betting	bet	VBG	O	2	advcl
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	telling	tell	VBG	O	2	advcl
11	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
12	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
14	rebellious	rebellious	JJ	O	10	ccomp
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	disrespectful	disrespectful	JJ	O	14	conj
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	part	part	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	whole	whole	JJ	O	6	amod
6	story	story	NN	O	2	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
8	an	a	DT	O	0	ROOT
9	imply	imply	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	later	later	JJ	O	12	amod
12	failure	failure	NN	O	9	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
4	way	way	NN	O	8	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Twain	Twain	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	writes	write	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	personality	personality	NN	O	8	dobj
12	in	in	IN	O	15	mark
13	order	order	NN	O	12	mwe
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	give	give	VB	O	8	advcl
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	foundation	foundation	NN	O	15	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	personality	personality	NN	O	17	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	people	people	NNS	O	20	nmod
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	DATE	25	det
25	1860s	1860	NNS	DATE	22	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Wheeler	Wheeler	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	later	later	RB	O	3	advmod
3	tells	tell	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	uses	use	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	smartness	smartness	NN	O	6	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	let	let	VB	O	8	acl
11	an	a	DT	O	13	det
12	ordinary	ordinary	JJ	O	13	amod
13	dog	dog	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	win	win	VB	O	10	ccomp
15	every	every	DT	O	16	det
16	contest	contest	NN	O	14	dobj
17	he	he	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	participates	participate	VBZ	O	16	acl:relcl
19	in	in	IN	O	22	mark
20	order	order	NN	O	19	mwe
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	show	show	VB	O	18	advcl
23	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
24	there	there	EX	O	25	expl
25	is	be	VBZ	O	22	ccomp
26	no	no	DT	O	28	neg
27	absolute	absolute	JJ	O	28	amod
28	equality	equality	NN	O	25	nsubj
29	in	in	IN	O	30	case
30	competitions	competition	NNS	O	28	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Wheeler	Wheeler	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	describes	describe	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	dog	dog	NN	O	13	nsubj
6	that	that	WDT	O	8	dobj
7	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	has	have	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
9	is	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
10	just	just	RB	O	13	advmod
11	an	a	DT	O	13	det
12	ordinary	ordinary	JJ	O	13	amod
13	dog	dog	NN	O	2	ccomp
14	that	that	WDT	O	15	nsubj
15	looks	look	VBZ	O	13	acl:relcl
16	like	like	IN	O	18	mark
17	there	there	EX	O	18	expl
18	is	be	VBZ	O	15	advcl
19	no	no	DT	O	20	neg
20	chance	chance	NN	O	18	nsubj
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	winning	win	VBG	O	20	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	15	punct
24	but	but	CC	O	15	cc
25	actually	actually	RB	O	26	advmod
26	wins	win	VBZ	O	15	conj
27	every	every	DT	O	28	det
28	contest	contest	NN	O	26	dobj
29	by	by	IN	O	31	case
30	''	''	''	O	31	punct
31	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	26	nmod
32	grabbing	grab	VBG	O	31	acl
33	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
34	that	that	IN	O	37	mark
35	other	other	JJ	O	37	amod
36	dog	dog	NN	O	37	compound
37	jest	jest	NN	O	32	dep
38	by	by	IN	O	41	case
39	the	the	DT	O	41	det
40	j'	j'	NN	O	41	compound
41	int	int	NN	O	37	dep
42	of	of	IN	O	45	case
43	his	he	PRP$	O	45	nmod:poss
44	hind	hind	JJ	O	45	amod
45	leg	leg	NN	O	41	nmod
46	and	and	CC	O	45	cc
47	freeze	freeze	NN	O	45	conj
48	to	to	TO	O	49	case
49	it	it	PRP	O	45	nmod
50	''	''	''	O	45	punct
51	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	52	punct
52	3	3	LS	NUMBER	45	dep
53	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	52	punct
54	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	dog	dog	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	names	name	NNS	O	2	appos
5	Andrew	Andrew	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	4	dep
7	,	,	,	O	2	punct
8	represents	represent	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	people	people	NNS	O	8	dobj
10	who	who	WP	O	11	nsubj
11	use	use	VBP	O	9	acl:relcl
12	their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	smartness	smartness	NN	O	11	dobj
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	overcome	overcome	VB	O	13	acl
16	different	different	JJ	O	17	amod
17	circumstances	circumstance	NNS	O	15	dobj
18	but	but	CC	O	22	cc
19	in	in	IN	O	22	case
20	a	a	DT	O	22	det
21	special	special	JJ	O	22	amod
22	way	way	NN	O	15	nmod
23	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
24	people	people	NNS	O	27	nsubj
25	do	do	VBP	O	27	aux
26	not	not	RB	O	27	neg
27	admit	admit	VB	O	15	ccomp
28	their	they	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	talents	talent	NNS	O	27	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Twain	Twain	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	satirizes	satirize	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	people	people	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
6	use	use	VBP	O	4	acl:relcl
7	tricks	trick	NNS	O	6	dobj
8	instead	instead	RB	O	12	case
9	of	of	IN	O	8	mwe
10	their	they	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
11	own	own	JJ	O	12	amod
12	ability	ability	NN	O	7	nmod
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	win	win	VB	O	6	xcomp
15	unfair	unfair	JJ	O	16	amod
16	contests	contest	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	,	,	,	O	3	punct
18	so	so	IN	O	3	dep
19	they	they	PRP	O	23	nsubjpass
20	are	be	VBP	O	23	auxpass
21	not	not	RB	O	23	neg
22	easily	easily	RB	O	23	advmod
23	recognized	recognize	VBN	O	3	parataxis
24	by	by	IN	O	25	case
25	criticisms	criticism	NNS	O	23	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Nevertheless	nevertheless	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	dog	dog	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	later	later	RB	O	6	advmod
6	meets	meet	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	``	``	``	O	6	punct
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	dog	dog	NN	O	10	nsubj
10	once	once	RB	DATE	6	xcomp
11	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
12	did	do	VBD	O	14	aux
13	n't	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	have	have	VB	O	10	ccomp
15	hind	hind	JJ	O	16	amod
16	legs	leg	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	''	''	''	O	6	punct
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	19	punct
19	3	3	LS	NUMBER	6	dep
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	19	punct
21	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	So	so	RB	O	3	advmod
2	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	loses	lose	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	fight	fight	NN	O	3	dobj
6	with	with	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	dog	dog	NN	O	5	nmod
9	without	without	IN	O	12	case
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	hind	hind	JJ	O	12	amod
12	leg	leg	NN	O	3	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	story	story	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
5	finding	find	VBG	O	14	csubj
6	other	other	JJ	O	7	amod
7	people	people	NNS	O	9	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	weakness	weakness	NN	O	5	dobj
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	combat	combat	NN	O	9	nmod
13	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
14	imperative	imperative	JJ	O	3	ccomp
15	,	,	,	O	3	punct
16	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
17	using	use	VBG	O	26	csubj
18	their	they	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	weakness	weakness	NN	O	17	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	dominate	dominate	VB	O	19	acl
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	fight	fight	NN	O	21	dobj
24	does	do	VBZ	O	26	aux
25	not	not	RB	O	26	neg
26	work	work	VB	O	3	conj
27	all	all	PDT	O	29	det:predet
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	time	time	NN	O	26	dobj
30	because	because	IN	O	33	mark
31	we	we	PRP	O	33	nsubj
32	never	never	RB	O	33	neg
33	know	know	VBP	O	26	advcl
34	that	that	IN	O	40	mark
35	their	they	PRP$	O	36	nmod:poss
36	weakness	weakness	NN	O	40	nsubj
37	could	could	MD	O	40	aux
38	be	be	VB	O	40	cop
39	our	we	PRP$	O	40	nmod:poss
40	vulnerability	vulnerability	NN	O	33	ccomp
41	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	3	advmod
2	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	loses	lose	VBZ	O	8	advcl
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	fight	fight	NN	O	3	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	chooses	choose	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	8	nmod
10	''	''	''	O	8	punct
11	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	12	punct
12	lay	lay	VBD	O	8	ccomp
13	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	12	punct
14	down	down	RB	O	12	advmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
17	die	die	VB	O	12	dep
18	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	17	dobj
19	''	''	''	O	17	punct
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	3	3	LS	NUMBER	17	dep
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
23	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	3	advmod
2	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	uses	use	VBZ	O	13	advcl
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	techniques	technique	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	win	win	VB	O	3	xcomp
8	over	over	IN	O	10	case
9	other	other	JJ	O	10	amod
10	dogs	dog	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	13	punct
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
14	ambition	ambition	NN	O	13	dobj
15	rather	rather	RB	O	14	cc
16	than	than	IN	O	15	mwe
17	shame	shame	NN	O	14	conj
18	,	,	,	O	13	punct
19	but	but	CC	O	13	cc
20	when	when	WRB	O	22	advmod
21	he	he	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	loses	lose	VBZ	O	27	advcl
23	this	this	DT	O	24	det
24	fight	fight	NN	O	22	dobj
25	,	,	,	O	27	punct
26	he	he	PRP	O	27	nsubj
27	chooses	choose	VBZ	O	13	conj
28	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
29	give	give	VB	O	27	xcomp
30	up	up	RP	O	29	compound:prt
31	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Twain	Twain	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	personalizes	personalize	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	3	dobj
5	as	as	IN	O	6	case
6	someone	someone	NN	O	4	nmod
7	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
8	does	do	VBZ	O	10	aux
9	not	not	RB	O	10	neg
10	use	use	VB	O	6	acl:relcl
11	his	he	PRP$	O	15	amod
12	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
13	her	she	PRP$	O	11	conj
14	own	own	JJ	O	15	amod
15	ability	ability	NN	O	10	dobj
16	,	,	,	O	6	punct
17	but	but	CC	O	18	cc
18	rather	rather	RB	O	6	cc
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	find	find	VB	O	6	acl
21	tricks	trick	NNS	O	20	dobj
22	in	in	IN	O	25	mark
23	order	order	NN	O	22	mwe
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	accomplish	accomplish	VB	O	20	advcl
26	achievement	achievement	NN	O	25	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	tricks	trick	NNS	O	6	nsubj
3	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	uses	use	VBZ	O	2	acl:relcl
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
6	acceptable	acceptable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	by	by	IN	O	8	case
8	rules	rule	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
10	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubjpass
11	can	can	MD	O	15	aux
12	not	not	RB	O	15	neg
13	be	be	VB	O	15	auxpass
14	fully	fully	RB	O	15	advmod
15	respected	respect	VBN	O	6	conj
16	by	by	IN	O	19	case
17	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	own	own	JJ	O	19	amod
19	potentiality	potentiality	NN	O	15	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	little	little	JJ	O	3	amod
3	smartness	smartness	NN	O	9	nsubj
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	competition	competition	NN	O	3	nmod
7	does	do	VBZ	O	9	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	seem	seem	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
11	be	be	VB	O	12	cop
12	overwhelming	overwhelming	JJ	O	9	xcomp
13	,	,	,	O	9	punct
14	but	but	CC	O	9	cc
15	when	when	WRB	O	17	advmod
16	someone	someone	NN	O	17	nsubj
17	uses	use	VBZ	O	24	advcl
18	smartness	smartness	NN	O	17	dobj
19	too	too	RB	O	20	advmod
20	much	much	RB	O	17	advmod
21	,	,	,	O	24	punct
22	then	then	RB	O	23	advmod
23	it	it	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	becomes	become	VBZ	O	9	conj
25	cunningness	cunningness	NN	O	24	xcomp
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	which	which	WDT	O	28	nsubj
28	means	mean	VBZ	O	25	acl:relcl
29	to	to	TO	O	30	mark
30	take	take	VB	O	28	xcomp
31	unfair	unfair	JJ	O	32	amod
32	advantage	advantage	NN	O	30	dobj
33	of	of	IN	O	34	case
34	someone	someone	NN	O	32	nmod
35	else	else	RB	O	34	advmod
36	in	in	IN	O	39	mark
37	order	order	NN	O	36	mwe
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	achieve	achieve	VB	O	30	advcl
40	the	the	DT	O	41	det
41	goal	goal	NN	O	39	dobj
42	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	main	main	JJ	O	4	amod
3	focal	focal	JJ	O	4	amod
4	point	point	NN	O	11	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	story	story	NN	O	4	nmod
8	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
9	about	about	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	frog	frog	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	that	that	WDT	O	16	dobj
13	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
14	uses	use	VBZ	O	11	acl:relcl
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	deceive	deceive	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	other	other	JJ	O	18	amod
18	people	people	NNS	O	16	dobj
19	but	but	CC	O	14	cc
20	is	be	VBZ	O	21	auxpass
21	deluded	delude	VBN	O	14	conj
22	by	by	IN	O	25	case
23	an	a	DT	O	25	det
24	ordinary	ordinary	JJ	O	25	amod
25	stranger	stranger	NN	O	21	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	frog	frog	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	names	name	NNS	O	2	appos
5	Dan	Dan	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	'	'	POS	O	5	case
7	l	l	NN	O	4	dep
8	Webster	Webster	NNP	O	4	appos
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	can	can	MD	O	11	aux
11	jump	jump	VB	O	0	ROOT
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	highest	highest	JJS	O	11	dobj
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	Calaveras	Calaveras	NNP	LOCATION	16	compound
16	County	County	NNP	LOCATION	13	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Webster	Webster	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	``	``	``	O	5	punct
4	so	so	RB	O	5	advmod
5	modest	modest	JJ	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	straightfor	straightfor	JJ	O	5	conj
8	`	`	``	O	5	punct
9	ard	ard	NN	O	5	xcomp
10	as	as	IN	O	12	mark
11	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	5	advcl
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	for	for	IN	O	15	case
15	all	all	DT	O	5	nmod
16	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
18	so	so	RB	O	19	advmod
19	gifted	gifted	JJ	O	15	acl:relcl
20	''	''	''	O	19	punct
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	22	punct
22	4	4	LS	NUMBER	19	dep
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	22	punct
24	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	description	description	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	Webster	Webster	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	displays	display	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	9	mark
7	he	he	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
9	talented	talented	JJ	O	5	ccomp
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	capable	capable	JJ	O	9	conj
12	of	of	IN	O	13	mark
13	beating	beat	VBG	O	9	advcl
14	any	any	DT	O	15	det
15	frog	frog	NN	O	13	dobj
16	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	4	advmod
2	a	a	DT	O	3	det
3	stranger	stranger	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	comes	come	VBZ	O	10	advcl
5	to	to	TO	O	7	case
6	Calaveras	Calaveras	NNP	LOCATION	7	compound
7	County	County	NNP	LOCATION	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	10	punct
9	he	he	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	disagrees	disagree	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
11	with	with	IN	O	12	case
12	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
13	that	that	WDT	O	18	dobj
14	Webster	Webster	NNP	PERSON	18	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	highest	highest	JJS	O	18	amod
18	jumper	jumper	NN	O	12	acl:relcl
19	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	stranger	stranger	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	tricks	trick	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	such	such	JJ	O	16	case
6	as	as	IN	O	5	mwe
7	``	``	``	O	16	punct
8	taking	take	VBG	O	16	dep
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	teaspoon	teaspoon	NN	O	8	dobj
11	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
12	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	13	advmod
13	filling	fill	VBG	O	8	conj
14	Webster	Webster	NNP	PERSON	13	dobj
15	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	16	punct
16	full	full	JJ	O	4	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	quail-shot	quail-shot	NN	O	16	nmod
19	''	''	''	O	16	punct
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	5	5	CD	NUMBER	16	appos
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
23	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	stranger	stranger	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	so	so	RB	O	5	advmod
5	cunning	cunning	JJ	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	takes	take	VBZ	O	5	ccomp
9	advantage	advantage	NN	O	8	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	11	case
11	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	9	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	8	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
14	wins	win	VBZ	O	8	conj
15	forty	forty	CD	MONEY	16	nummod
16	dollars	dollar	NNS	MONEY	14	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	5	advmod
2	though	though	IN	O	5	mark
3	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
5	smart	smart	JJ	O	20	advcl
6	at	at	IN	O	7	case
7	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	5	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
9	uses	use	VBZ	O	5	conj
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	smartness	smartness	NN	O	9	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	win	win	VB	O	11	acl
14	over	over	IN	O	16	case
15	many	many	JJ	O	16	amod
16	competitions	competition	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	20	punct
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	stranger	stranger	NN	O	20	nsubj
20	seems	seem	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
21	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
22	be	be	VB	O	23	cop
23	insidious	insidious	JJ	O	20	xcomp
24	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
25	takes	take	VBZ	O	20	conj
26	inequitable	inequitable	JJ	O	27	amod
27	advantages	advantage	NNS	O	25	dobj
28	of	of	IN	O	29	case
29	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	27	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	story	story	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	indispensable	indispensable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	in	in	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	entire	entire	JJ	O	8	amod
8	story	story	NN	O	4	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	Jim	Jim	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
12	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
13	Simon	Simon	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Wheeler	Wheeler	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
15	tells	tell	VBZ	O	4	ccomp
16	about	about	RB	O	15	advmod
17	,	,	,	O	15	punct
18	because	because	IN	O	20	mark
19	it	it	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	shows	show	VBZ	O	15	advcl
21	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
22	smartness	smartness	NN	O	25	nsubjpass
23	can	can	MD	O	25	aux
24	be	be	VB	O	25	auxpass
25	overthrown	overthrow	VBN	O	20	ccomp
26	by	by	IN	O	27	case
27	insidiousness	insidiousness	NN	O	25	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Twain	Twain	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	correlates	correlate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	two	two	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	people	people	NNS	O	3	dobj
7	:	:	:	O	6	punct
8	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	6	dep
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	stranger	stranger	NN	O	8	conj
12	,	,	,	O	3	punct
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	satirize	satirize	VB	O	3	advcl
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	people	people	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	who	who	WP	O	18	nsubj
18	use	use	VBP	O	16	acl:relcl
19	their	they	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
20	``	``	``	O	21	punct
21	smartness	smartness	NN	O	18	dobj
22	''	''	''	O	21	punct
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	deceive	deceive	VB	O	18	xcomp
25	people	people	NNS	O	24	dobj
26	in	in	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	DATE	28	det
28	1860s	1860	NNS	DATE	24	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	someone	someone	NN	O	27	ccomp
4	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
6	pugnacious	pugnacious	JJ	O	3	acl:relcl
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	likes	like	VBZ	O	6	conj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	gamble	gamble	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
12	uses	use	VBZ	O	8	conj
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	smartness	smartness	NN	O	8	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	achieve	achieve	VB	O	14	acl
17	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	personal	personal	JJ	O	19	amod
19	goals	goal	NNS	O	16	dobj
20	,	,	,	O	3	punct
21	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	stranger	stranger	NN	O	25	nsubj
24	is	be	VBZ	O	25	cop
25	charlatan	charlatan	NN	O	3	conj
26	,	,	,	O	27	punct
27	deceives	deceive	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
28	people	people	NNS	O	27	nsubj
29	by	by	IN	O	30	mark
30	using	use	VBG	O	28	acl
31	unjustifiable	unjustifiable	JJ	O	32	amod
32	convenience	convenience	NN	O	30	dobj
33	and	and	CC	O	32	cc
34	trickery	trickery	NN	O	32	conj
35	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	two	two	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
3	analogous	analogous	JJ	O	4	amod
4	sides	side	NNS	O	16	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	story	story	NN	O	4	nmod
8	:	:	:	O	4	punct
9	smartness	smartness	NN	O	4	dep
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	cunning	cunning	JJ	O	9	conj
12	,	,	,	O	4	punct
13	are	be	VBP	O	16	cop
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	main	main	JJ	O	16	amod
16	theme	theme	NN	O	0	ROOT
17	in	in	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	stories	story	NNS	O	16	nmod
20	Wheeler	Wheeler	NNP	PERSON	21	nsubj
21	tells	tell	VBZ	O	19	acl:relcl
22	about	about	IN	O	23	case
23	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	4	advmod
2	cunning	cunning	JJ	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	aux
4	dominating	dominate	VBG	O	15	advcl
5	one	one	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	person	person	NN	O	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	ambition	ambition	NN	O	4	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	15	punct
10	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubjpass
11	or	or	CC	O	10	cc
12	she	she	PRP	O	10	conj
13	will	will	MD	O	15	aux
14	be	be	VB	O	15	auxpass
15	corrupted	corrupt	VBN	O	0	ROOT
16	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	nowadays	nowadays	RB	O	6	advcl
3	,	,	,	O	6	punct
4	people	people	NNS	O	6	nsubjpass
5	are	be	VBP	O	6	auxpass
6	judged	judge	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	by	by	IN	O	8	mark
8	taking	take	VBG	O	6	advcl
9	advantages	advantage	NNS	O	8	dobj
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	contest	contest	NN	O	8	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	6	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
15	they	they	PRP	O	18	nsubjpass
16	will	will	MD	O	18	aux
17	get	get	VB	O	18	auxpass
18	caught	catch	VBN	O	6	conj
19	eventually	eventually	RB	O	18	advmod
20	or	or	CC	O	18	cc
21	will	will	MD	O	23	aux
22	be	be	VB	O	23	auxpass
23	defeated	defeat	VBN	O	18	conj
24	by	by	IN	O	25	case
25	someone	someone	NN	O	23	nmod
26	who	who	WP	O	27	nsubj
27	does	do	VBZ	O	25	acl:relcl
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	same	same	JJ	O	27	dobj
30	to	to	TO	O	31	case
31	them	they	PRP	O	27	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Smartness	smartness	NN	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	marvelous	marvelous	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	in	in	IN	O	5	case
5	success	success	NN	O	3	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	3	punct
7	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
8	cunning	cunning	JJ	O	12	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
10	definitely	definitely	RB	O	12	advmod
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	acceptable	acceptable	JJ	O	3	conj
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	society	society	NN	O	12	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Twain	Twain	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	irony	irony	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	lively	lively	JJ	O	7	amod
7	humor	humor	NN	O	4	conj
8	are	be	VBP	O	4	dep
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	mainstreams	mainstream	NNS	O	4	dep
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	story	story	NN	O	10	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	4	punct
15	both	both	CC	O	16	dep
16	criticizing	criticize	VBG	O	4	acl
17	Jim	Jim	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
18	Smiley	Smiley	NNP	PERSON	16	dobj
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	story	story	NN	O	18	nmod
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	general	general	JJ	O	24	amod
24	people	people	NNS	O	21	conj
25	in	in	IN	O	27	case
26	the	the	DT	DATE	27	det
27	1860s	1860	NNS	DATE	4	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	4	punct

