1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Catcher	catcher	NN	O	16	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	Rye	Rye	NNP	O	2	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	2	punct
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	famous	famous	JJ	O	9	amod
9	book	book	NN	O	2	appos
10	written	write	VBN	O	9	acl
11	by	by	IN	O	13	case
12	J.D.	J.D.	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	2	punct
15	has	have	VBZ	O	16	aux
16	impacted	impact	VBN	O	0	ROOT
17	several	several	JJ	O	18	amod
18	generations	generation	NNS	O	16	dobj
19	since	since	IN	O	20	case
20	1950s	1950s	CD	DATE	16	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	protagonist	protagonist	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	story	story	NN	O	2	nmod
6	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	11	det
8	sixty	sixty	CD	DURATION	9	nummod
9	years	year	NNS	DURATION	10	nmod:npmod
10	old	old	JJ	DURATION	11	amod
11	boy	boy	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	who	who	WP	O	13	nsubj
13	dislikes	dislikes	NN	O	11	acl:relcl
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	world	world	NN	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	adults	adult	NNS	O	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	boy	boy	NN	O	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	name	name	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Caulfield	Caulfield	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	story	story	NN	O	12	nsubj
12	begins	begin	VBZ	O	7	conj
13	with	with	IN	O	15	case
14	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	departure	departure	NN	O	12	nmod
16	from	from	IN	O	18	case
17	Pencey	Pencey	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	prep	prep	NN	O	12	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	12	punct
20	a	a	DT	O	22	det
21	famous	famous	JJ	O	22	amod
22	school	school	NN	O	12	dobj
23	he	he	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	attended	attend	VBD	O	22	acl:relcl
25	in	in	IN	O	26	case
26	Agerstown	Agerstown	NNP	LOCATION	24	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	gets	get	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	expelled	expel	VBN	O	2	dep
4	,	,	,	O	2	punct
5	because	because	IN	O	7	mark
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	failed	fail	VBD	O	2	advcl
8	four	four	CD	NUMBER	7	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
11	five	five	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	classes	class	NNS	O	8	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	First	first	RB	ORDINAL	8	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	8	punct
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	chapter	chapter	NN	O	8	nmod
5	one	one	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	mentions	mention	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	has	have	VBZ	O	8	ccomp
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	brother	brother	NN	O	11	dobj
14	who	who	WP	O	15	nsubj
15	works	work	VBZ	O	13	acl:relcl
16	for	for	IN	O	17	case
17	Hollywood	Hollywood	NNP	LOCATION	15	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	15	punct
19	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
20	gives	give	VBZ	O	15	conj
21	up	up	RP	O	20	compound:prt
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	career	career	NN	O	20	dobj
24	in	in	IN	O	26	case
25	serious	serious	JJ	O	26	amod
26	literature	literature	NN	O	23	nmod
27	for	for	IN	O	28	case
28	money	money	NN	O	26	nmod
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	fame	fame	NN	O	28	conj
31	of	of	IN	O	33	case
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	movies	movie	NNS	O	23	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	3	aux
3	know	know	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	personality	personality	NN	O	3	dobj
7	from	from	IN	O	9	case
8	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	9	amod
9	chapters	chapter	NNS	O	3	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	visit	visit	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Spencer	Spencer	NNP	PERSON	4	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	8	case
8	politeness	politeness	NNP	O	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	even	even	RB	O	12	advmod
11	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	failed	fail	VBD	O	2	ccomp
13	in	in	IN	O	16	case
14	his	he	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	history	history	NN	O	16	compound
16	class	class	NN	O	12	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	cynicism	cynicism	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	gets	get	VBZ	O	4	auxpass
4	showed	show	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	from	from	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	conversation	conversation	NN	O	4	nmod
8	with	with	IN	O	10	case
9	Mrs	Mrs	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
10	Spencer	Spencer	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	4	advmod
2	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Spencer	Spencer	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	asks	ask	VBZ	O	21	advcl
5	him	he	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	reason	reason	NN	O	9	compound
9	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
10	left	leave	VBD	O	4	ccomp
11	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	last	last	JJ	O	13	amod
13	school	school	NN	O	10	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	21	punct
15	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	17	nmod:poss
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	answer	answer	NN	O	21	nsubj
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	mind	mind	NN	O	17	nmod
21	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
22	that	that	IN	O	24	mark
23	there	there	EX	O	24	expl
24	were	be	VBD	O	21	ccomp
25	so	so	RB	O	24	advmod
26	many	many	JJ	O	27	amod
27	hypocrite	hypocrite	NN	O	24	nsubj
28	,	,	,	O	27	punct
29	especially	especially	RB	O	27	advmod
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	27	dep
32	Roxas	Roxas	NNP	PERSON	31	dep
33	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
34	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	32	appos
35	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
36	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	says	say	VBZ	O	25	ccomp
3	that	that	IN	O	4	case
4	every	every	DT	SET	2	advmod
5	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	2	nmod:tmod
6	,	,	,	O	2	punct
7	when	when	WRB	O	9	advmod
8	parents	parent	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	come	come	VBP	O	2	advcl
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	school	school	NN	O	9	xcomp
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	pick	pick	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	their	they	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	kids	kid	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	up	up	RB	O	13	advmod
17	,	,	,	O	25	punct
18	Roxas	Roxas	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
19	would	would	MD	O	25	aux
20	be	be	VB	O	25	cop
21	super	super	JJ	O	25	amod
22	nice	nice	JJ	O	25	amod
23	to	to	TO	O	24	case
24	those	those	DT	O	22	nmod
25	parents	parent	NNS	O	0	ROOT
26	who	who	WP	O	27	nsubj
27	drive	drive	VBP	O	25	acl:relcl
28	cars	car	NNS	O	27	dobj
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	dress	dress	NN	O	28	conj
31	nicely	nicely	RB	O	27	advmod
32	.	.	.	O	25	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	3	advmod
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	sees	see	VBZ	O	13	advcl
4	some	some	DT	O	5	det
5	parents	parent	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	who	who	WP	O	7	nsubj
7	dress	dress	VBP	O	5	acl:relcl
8	bad	bad	JJ	O	7	xcomp
9	,	,	,	O	13	punct
10	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
11	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	say	say	VB	O	0	ROOT
14	anything	anything	NN	O	13	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	but	but	CC	O	17	cc
17	just	just	RB	O	14	cc
18	smile	smile	NN	O	14	conj
19	at	at	IN	O	20	case
20	them	they	PRP	O	18	nmod
21	for	for	IN	O	23	case
22	a	a	DT	DURATION	23	det
23	second	second	JJ	DURATION	13	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
4	did	do	VBD	O	6	aux
5	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
6	tell	tell	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Spencer	Spencer	NNP	PERSON	6	dobj
9	what	what	WP	O	12	dobj
10	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	really	really	RB	O	12	advmod
12	think	think	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
13	about	about	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	reason	reason	NN	O	12	nmod
16	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	left	leave	VBD	O	15	acl:relcl
18	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
19	last	last	JJ	O	20	amod
20	school	school	NN	O	17	dobj
21	,	,	,	O	17	punct
22	because	because	IN	O	24	mark
23	he	he	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	knew	know	VBD	O	17	advcl
25	that	that	IN	O	30	mark
26	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	27	compound
27	Spencer	Spencer	NNP	PERSON	30	nsubj
28	could	could	MD	O	30	aux
29	not	not	RB	O	30	neg
30	understand	understand	VB	O	24	ccomp
31	him	he	PRP	O	30	dobj
32	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	3	advmod
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	ran	run	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	away	away	RB	O	3	advmod
5	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Second	second	RB	ORDINAL	12	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	12	punct
3	after	after	IN	O	5	mark
4	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	fought	fight	VBD	O	12	advcl
6	with	with	IN	O	9	case
7	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	9	compound
8	Rudd	Rudd	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	letta	letta	NNP	O	5	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	12	punct
11	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	left	leave	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	school	school	NN	O	12	dobj
14	immediately	immediately	RB	O	12	advmod
15	because	because	IN	O	19	mark
16	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
18	so	so	RB	O	19	advmod
19	angry	angry	JJ	O	12	advcl
20	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	5	case
4	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
5	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	2	nmod
6	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
7	decide	decide	VB	O	2	conj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	live	live	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	hotel	hotel	NN	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	9	punct
14	because	because	IN	O	19	mark
15	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
16	did	do	VBD	O	19	aux
17	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
18	really	really	RB	O	19	advmod
19	want	want	VB	O	9	advcl
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	see	see	VB	O	19	xcomp
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	parents	parent	NNS	O	21	dobj
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	During	during	IN	O	3	case
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	time	time	NN	O	7	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	7	punct
5	many	many	JJ	O	6	amod
6	things	thing	NNS	O	7	nsubj
7	happened	happen	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	around	around	IN	O	9	case
9	him	he	PRP	O	7	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	case
4	Ernie	Ernie	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	really	really	RB	O	2	advcl
5	like	like	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	pianoforte	pianoforte	NN	O	4	nmod
8	Ernie	Ernie	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
9	played	play	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
10	after	after	IN	O	11	case
11	he	he	PRP	O	9	nmod
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	feel	feel	VB	O	9	ccomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	environment	environment	NN	O	13	dobj
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	Ernie	Ernie	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	People	people	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	applaud	applaud	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	no	no	DT	O	4	neg
4	matter	matter	NN	O	2	dobj
5	they	they	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	like	like	VBP	O	4	acl:relcl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	pianoforte	pianoforte	NN	O	6	dobj
9	or	or	CC	O	8	cc
10	not	not	RB	O	8	conj
11	,	,	,	O	2	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
13	Ernie	Ernie	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
14	will	will	MD	O	15	aux
15	bow	bow	VB	O	2	conj
16	phonily	phonily	RB	O	15	advmod
17	after	after	IN	O	19	mark
18	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	plays	play	VBZ	O	15	advcl
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	19	dep
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	thinks	think	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
4	Ernie	Ernie	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
5	does	do	VBZ	O	8	aux
6	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
7	even	even	RB	O	8	advmod
8	think	think	VB	O	2	ccomp
9	about	about	IN	O	10	case
10	weather	weather	NN	O	8	nmod
11	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	does	do	VBZ	O	10	acl:relcl
13	well	well	RB	O	12	advmod
14	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
15	not	not	RB	O	13	conj
16	,	,	,	O	10	punct
17	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	fickleness	fickleness	NN	O	10	conj
20	of	of	IN	O	23	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	crowed	crow	VBN	O	23	amod
23	changes	change	NNS	O	19	nmod
24	Ernie	Ernie	NNP	PERSON	23	appos
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	takes	take	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	table	table	NN	O	4	dobj
7	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
8	listens	listen	VBZ	O	4	conj
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	conversations	conversation	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	around	around	IN	O	12	case
12	him	he	PRP	O	8	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	gets	get	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	disgusting	disgusting	JJ	O	2	xcomp
4	by	by	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	phony	phony	JJ	O	7	amod
7	talk	talk	NN	O	3	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	couple	couple	NN	O	7	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	boy	boy	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	aux
4	talking	talk	VBG	O	0	ROOT
5	about	about	IN	O	9	case
6	a	a	DT	O	9	det
7	professional	professional	JJ	O	9	amod
8	football	football	NN	O	9	compound
9	game	game	NN	O	4	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	12	case
11	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	girlfriend	girlfriend	NN	O	4	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	girl	girl	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	no	no	DT	O	5	neg
5	interest	interest	NN	O	3	dobj
6	on	on	IN	O	7	case
7	football	football	NN	O	5	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	3	punct
9	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
10	she	she	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	was	be	VBD	O	12	aux
12	listening	listen	VBG	O	3	conj
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	even	even	RB	O	19	advmod
15	she	she	PRP	O	19	nsubj
16	did	do	VBD	O	19	aux
17	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
18	really	really	RB	O	19	advmod
19	pay	pay	VB	O	12	ccomp
20	attention	attention	NN	O	19	dobj
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	another	another	DT	O	5	det
4	couple	couple	JJ	O	5	amod
5	seat	seat	NN	O	2	nsubj
6	near	near	IN	O	7	case
7	Holden	Holden	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	man	man	NN	O	3	compound
3	dresses	dress	NNS	O	0	ROOT
4	like	like	IN	O	7	case
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	Yale	Yale	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	student	student	NN	O	3	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	aux
3	stroking	stroke	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	girl	girl	NN	O	8	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	private	private	JJ	O	8	amod
8	part	part	NN	O	3	dobj
9	while	while	IN	O	12	mark
10	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	was	be	VBD	O	12	aux
12	telling	tell	VBG	O	3	advcl
13	her	she	PRP$	O	12	dep
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	story	story	NN	O	12	dobj
16	about	about	IN	O	18	case
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	person	person	NN	O	15	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	his	he	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	dorm	dorm	NN	O	18	nmod
22	who	who	WP	O	23	nsubj
23	ate	eat	VBD	O	15	acl:relcl
24	aspirin	aspirin	NN	O	23	dobj
25	for	for	IN	O	26	case
26	suicide	suicide	NN	O	23	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	14	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	dep
3	dresses	dress	NNS	O	14	nsubj
4	like	like	IN	O	7	case
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	successful	successful	JJ	O	7	amod
7	man	man	NN	O	3	nmod
8	which	which	WDT	O	11	dobj
9	most	most	JJS	O	10	amod
10	people	people	NNS	O	11	nsubj
11	think	think	VBP	O	7	acl:relcl
12	you	you	PRP	O	11	dobj
13	are	be	VBP	O	14	cop
14	successful	successful	JJ	O	28	advcl
15	if	if	IN	O	17	mark
16	you	you	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	go	go	VBP	O	14	ccomp
18	to	to	TO	O	21	case
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	nice	nice	JJ	O	21	amod
21	school	school	NN	O	17	nmod
22	such	such	JJ	O	24	case
23	as	as	IN	O	22	mwe
24	Yale	Yale	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	28	punct
26	he	he	PRP	O	28	nsubj
27	was	be	VBD	O	28	aux
28	doing	do	VBG	O	0	ROOT
29	the	the	DT	O	31	det
30	dirty	dirty	JJ	O	31	amod
31	things	thing	NNS	O	28	dobj
32	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	2	case
2	that	that	DT	O	5	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	encounters	encounter	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	an	a	DT	O	8	det
7	obnoxious	obnoxious	JJ	O	8	amod
8	girl	girl	NN	O	5	dobj
9	named	name	VBN	O	8	acl
10	Lillian	Lillian	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Simmons	Simmons	NNP	PERSON	9	dobj
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	whom	whom	WP	O	15	dobj
14	D.B.	D.B.	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
15	dated	date	VBN	O	11	acl:relcl
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	DATE	18	det
18	past	past	NN	DATE	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	respect	respect	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	people	people	NNS	O	4	dobj
6	by	by	IN	O	7	mark
7	blocking	block	VBG	O	4	advcl
8	everyone	everyone	NN	O	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	way	way	NN	O	7	dobj
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	showed	show	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	big	big	JJ	O	5	amod
5	passion	passion	NN	O	2	dobj
6	after	after	IN	O	8	mark
7	she	she	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	knew	know	VBD	O	2	advcl
9	D.B.	D.B.	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
10	was	be	VBD	O	11	aux
11	working	work	VBG	O	8	ccomp
12	for	for	IN	O	13	case
13	Hollywood	Hollywood	NNP	LOCATION	11	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	2	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
16	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
17	thinks	think	VBZ	O	2	conj
18	that	that	IN	O	28	mark
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	reason	reason	NN	O	28	nsubj
21	she	she	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	invites	invite	VBZ	O	20	acl:relcl
23	him	he	PRP	O	22	dobj
24	to	to	TO	O	25	case
25	seat	seat	NN	O	22	nmod
26	with	with	IN	O	27	case
27	them	they	PRP	O	25	nmod
28	is	be	VBZ	O	17	ccomp
29	that	that	IN	O	31	mark
30	she	she	PRP	O	31	nsubj
31	wants	want	VBZ	O	28	ccomp
32	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	31	dobj
33	to	to	TO	O	34	mark
34	tell	tell	VB	O	31	xcomp
35	D.B.	D.B.	NNP	PERSON	34	dobj
36	how	how	WRB	O	39	advmod
37	nice	nice	JJ	O	39	nsubj
38	is	be	VBZ	O	39	cop
39	she	she	PRP	O	35	dep
40	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Last	last	JJ	O	17	nsubj
2	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
3	not	not	RB	O	1	cc
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	least	least	JJS	O	1	conj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	the	the	DT	O	10	det
8	most	most	RBS	O	9	advmod
9	famous	famous	JJ	O	10	amod
10	part	part	NN	O	5	appos
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	book	book	NN	O	10	nmod
14	should	should	MD	O	17	aux
15	be	be	VB	O	17	cop
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	conversation	conversation	NN	O	0	ROOT
18	between	between	IN	O	19	case
19	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	17	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
22	sister	sister	NN	O	23	compound
23	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	19	conj
24	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	time	time	NN	DATE	5	nmod
4	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	went	go	VBD	O	11	ccomp
6	back	back	RB	O	5	advmod
7	home	home	NN	O	6	dep
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
10	was	be	VBD	O	11	aux
11	sleeping	sleep	VBG	O	0	ROOT
12	in	in	IN	O	15	case
13	D.B.	D.B.	NNP	O	15	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	O	13	case
15	room	room	NN	O	11	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	overjoyed	overjoy	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	see	see	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	him	he	PRP	O	5	dobj
7	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	started	start	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	telling	tell	VBG	O	2	xcomp
4	him	he	PRP	O	3	iobj
5	things	thing	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	her	she	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	life	life	NN	O	5	nmod
9	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	enjoyed	enjoy	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	listening	listen	VBG	O	3	xcomp
5	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	talking	talking	NN	O	4	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	3	punct
9	because	because	IN	O	13	mark
10	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubj
11	was	be	VBD	O	13	cop
12	still	still	RB	O	13	advmod
13	innocent	innocent	JJ	O	3	advcl
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
16	what	what	WP	O	18	dobj
17	she	she	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	told	tell	VBD	O	13	conj
19	were	be	VBD	O	21	cop
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	things	thing	NNS	O	18	ccomp
22	she	she	PRP	O	24	nsubj
23	truthfully	truthfully	RB	O	24	advmod
24	wanted	want	VBD	O	21	acl:relcl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	share	share	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	with	with	IN	O	28	case
28	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	26	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	got	get	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	angry	angry	JJ	O	4	xcomp
6	after	after	IN	O	8	mark
7	she	she	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	noticed	notice	VBD	O	4	advcl
9	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
10	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
11	was	be	VBD	O	8	ccomp
12	home	home	RB	O	11	advmod
13	two	two	CD	DURATION	14	nummod
14	days	day	NNS	DURATION	11	nmod:tmod
15	early	early	RB	O	14	advmod
16	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
17	he	he	PRP	O	20	nsubjpass
18	must	must	MD	O	20	aux
19	be	be	VB	O	20	auxpass
20	kicked	kick	VBN	O	4	conj
21	out	out	RP	O	20	compound:prt
22	by	by	IN	O	23	case
23	school	school	NN	O	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	all	all	DT	O	3	advmod
3	know	know	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	people	people	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	get	get	VBP	O	3	ccomp
7	mad	mad	JJ	O	6	xcomp
8	about	about	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	things	thing	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	you	you	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	do	do	VBP	O	10	acl:relcl
13	because	because	IN	O	15	mark
14	they	they	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	care	care	VBP	O	12	advcl
16	about	about	IN	O	17	case
17	you	you	PRP	O	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	what	what	WP	O	5	dobj
4	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	felt	feel	VBD	O	2	ccomp
6	from	from	IN	O	7	case
7	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	explained	explain	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	case
4	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	why	why	WRB	O	9	advmod
6	he	he	PRP	O	9	nsubj
7	did	do	VBD	O	9	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	like	like	VB	O	2	advcl
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	school	school	NN	O	9	dobj
12	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	says	say	VBZ	O	6	advcl
4	,	,	,	O	6	punct
5	adults	adult	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	look	look	VBP	O	14	ccomp
7	lousy	lousy	JJ	O	6	dobj
8	when	when	WRB	O	11	advmod
9	they	they	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	are	be	VBP	O	11	aux
11	sleeping	sleep	VBG	O	7	acl:relcl
12	,	,	,	O	14	punct
13	children	child	NNS	O	14	nsubj
14	look	look	VBP	O	0	ROOT
15	all	all	RB	O	16	advmod
16	right	right	JJ	O	14	advmod
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	16	dep
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
20	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Afterwards	afterwards	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	Phoebe	Phoebe	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	asked	ask	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	him	he	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	what	what	WP	O	8	dobj
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	wanted	want	VBD	O	4	dep
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	do	do	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	with	with	IN	O	13	case
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	life	life	NN	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	``	``	``	O	6	punct
4	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
5	'm	be	VBP	O	6	aux
6	standing	stand	VBG	O	2	ccomp
7	on	on	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	edge	edge	NN	O	6	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	some	some	DT	O	13	det
12	crazy	crazy	JJ	O	13	amod
13	cliff	cliff	NN	O	9	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	What	what	WP	O	3	dobj
2	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	have	have	VBP	O	8	advcl
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	do	do	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	catch	catch	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	everybody	everybody	NN	O	10	dobj
12	if	if	IN	O	14	mark
13	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	start	start	VBP	O	10	advcl
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	go	go	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	over	over	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	cliff	cliff	NN	O	16	nmod
20	--	--	:	O	8	punct
21	I	I	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	mean	mean	VBP	O	8	parataxis
23	if	if	IN	O	26	mark
24	they	they	PRP	O	26	nsubj
25	're	be	VBP	O	26	aux
26	running	run	VBG	O	22	advcl
27	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
28	they	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
29	do	do	VBP	O	31	aux
30	n't	not	RB	O	31	neg
31	look	look	VB	O	26	conj
32	where	where	WRB	O	35	advmod
33	they	they	PRP	O	35	nsubj
34	're	be	VBP	O	35	aux
35	going	go	VBG	O	31	advcl
36	I	I	PRP	O	37	nsubj
37	have	have	VBP	O	35	ccomp
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	come	come	VB	O	37	xcomp
40	out	out	RP	O	39	compound:prt
41	from	from	IN	O	42	case
42	somewhere	somewhere	RB	O	39	nmod
43	and	and	CC	O	39	cc
44	catch	catch	VB	O	39	conj
45	them	they	PRP	O	44	dobj
46	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	's	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	all	all	DT	O	0	ROOT
4	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
5	'd	would	MD	O	6	aux
6	do	do	VB	O	3	acl:relcl
7	all	all	DT	O	8	det
8	day	day	NN	DURATION	6	nmod:tmod
9	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
2	'd	would	MD	O	6	aux
3	just	just	RB	O	6	advmod
4	be	be	VB	O	6	cop
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	catcher	catcher	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	rye	rye	NN	O	6	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	all	all	DT	O	9	conj
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
13	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	11	appos
14	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
15	.	.	.	O	6	punct
16	''	''	''	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	reveals	reveal	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	yearn	yearn	VB	O	2	ccomp
6	for	for	IN	O	8	case
7	idealistic	idealistic	JJ	O	8	amod
8	childhood	childhood	NN	O	5	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	role	role	NN	O	8	conj
12	as	as	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	catcher	catcher	NN	O	5	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	innocence	innocence	NN	O	14	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Why	why	WRB	O	4	advmod
2	does	do	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	use	use	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	``	``	``	O	6	punct
6	catcher	catcher	NN	O	4	dobj
7	''	''	''	O	6	punct
8	here	here	RB	O	6	advmod
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	but	but	CC	O	11	cc
11	not	not	RB	O	6	cc
12	``	``	``	O	13	punct
13	savior	savior	NN	O	6	conj
14	''	''	''	O	13	punct
15	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
16	``	``	``	O	17	punct
17	protector	protector	NN	O	13	conj
18	''	''	''	O	17	punct
19	?	?	.	O	4	punct

1	Imagine	imagine	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	a	a	DT	O	3	det
3	graph	graph	NN	O	1	dobj
4	which	which	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	having	have	VBG	O	3	acl:relcl
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	cliff	cliff	NN	O	5	dobj
8	at	at	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	end	end	NN	O	5	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	rye	rye	NN	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	knows	know	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	DT	O	4	det
4	children	child	NNS	O	6	nsubj
5	will	will	MD	O	6	aux
6	fall	fall	VB	O	2	ccomp
7	off	off	RP	O	6	compound:prt
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	cliff	cliff	NN	O	6	dobj
10	if	if	IN	O	12	mark
11	there	there	EX	O	12	expl
12	is	be	VBZ	O	6	advcl
13	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	catcher	catcher	NN	O	12	nsubj
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	4	mark
2	we	we	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	all	all	DT	O	4	advmod
4	know	know	VBP	O	8	advcl
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	rye	rye	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
8	pure	pure	JJ	O	0	ROOT
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	which	which	WDT	O	12	dobj
11	there	there	EX	O	12	expl
12	is	be	VBZ	O	8	acl:relcl
13	only	only	RB	O	12	advmod
14	wheat	wheat	NN	O	12	nsubj
15	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	rye	rye	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	describe	describe	VBP	O	2	ccomp
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	purely	purely	RB	O	7	advmod
7	innocence	innocence	NN	O	4	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	children	child	NNS	O	7	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	use	use	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	``	``	``	O	6	punct
6	protect	protect	VB	O	4	ccomp
7	''	''	''	O	6	punct
8	here	here	RB	O	6	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	because	because	IN	O	12	mark
11	there	there	EX	O	12	expl
12	is	be	VBZ	O	6	advcl
13	no	no	DT	O	14	neg
14	need	need	NN	O	12	nsubj
15	for	for	IN	O	16	mark
16	protecting	protect	VBG	O	14	acl
17	if	if	IN	O	20	case
18	a	a	DT	O	20	det
19	child	child	NN	O	20	compound
20	fall	fall	NN	DATE	16	nmod
21	off	off	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	cliff	cliff	NN	O	16	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	All	all	DT	O	7	nsubj
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	wants	want	VBZ	O	1	acl:relcl
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	do	do	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	aux
7	catching	catch	VBG	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	children	child	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	who	who	WP	O	12	nsubj
11	will	will	MD	O	12	aux
12	fall	fall	VB	O	9	acl:relcl
13	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	use	use	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	``	``	``	O	4	punct
6	savior	savior	NN	O	4	dobj
7	''	''	''	O	6	punct
8	,	,	,	O	4	punct
9	either	either	RB	O	4	advmod
10	,	,	,	O	4	punct
11	because	because	IN	O	15	mark
12	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
13	does	do	VBZ	O	15	aux
14	not	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	think	think	VB	O	4	advcl
16	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	saves	save	VBZ	O	15	ccomp
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	children	child	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	think	think	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	himself	himself	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	as	as	IN	O	7	case
7	great	great	JJ	O	4	advcl
8	as	as	IN	O	11	mark
9	other	other	JJ	O	10	amod
10	readers	reader	NNS	O	11	nsubj
11	do	do	VBP	O	4	advcl
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	2	case
2	him	he	PRP	O	15	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	15	punct
4	catching	catch	VBG	O	15	csubj
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	kid	kid	NN	O	4	dobj
7	who	who	WP	O	9	nsubj
8	will	will	MD	O	9	aux
9	fall	fall	VB	O	6	acl:relcl
10	off	off	RP	O	9	compound:prt
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	cliff	cliff	NN	O	9	dobj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	15	cop
14	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	responsible	responsible	JJ	O	0	ROOT
16	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	3	mark
2	Salinger	Salinger	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	uses	use	VBZ	O	15	advcl
4	``	``	``	O	5	punct
5	savior	savior	JJ	O	3	xcomp
6	''	''	''	O	5	punct
7	instead	instead	RB	O	10	case
8	of	of	IN	O	7	mwe
9	``	``	``	O	10	punct
10	catcher	catcher	NN	O	5	nmod
11	''	''	''	O	10	punct
12	,	,	,	O	15	punct
13	it	it	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	will	will	MD	O	15	aux
15	show	show	VB	O	0	ROOT
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	glorification	glorification	NN	O	15	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	19	case
19	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	4	compound
4	dose	dose	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
6	think	think	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	about	about	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	honor	honor	NN	O	6	nmod
10	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
12	get	get	VB	O	9	acl:relcl
13	by	by	IN	O	16	mark
14	being	be	VBG	O	16	cop
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	catcher	catcher	NN	O	12	advcl
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	point	point	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	wanting	want	VBG	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	let	let	VB	O	6	xcomp
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	innocence	innocence	NN	O	13	nsubj
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	children	child	NNS	O	10	nmod
13	stay	stay	VBP	O	8	ccomp
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	another	another	DT	O	18	det
18	word	word	NN	O	20	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	20	punct
20	retain	retain	VBP	O	13	conj
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	innocence	innocence	NN	O	20	dobj
23	without	without	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	alienation	alienation	NN	O	20	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Unfortunately	unfortunately	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	we	we	PRP	O	6	nsubj
4	can	can	MD	O	6	aux
5	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
6	get	get	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	result	result	NN	O	6	dobj
9	from	from	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	ending	ending	NN	O	6	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	book	book	NN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	always	always	RB	O	4	advmod
4	trying	try	VBG	O	0	ROOT
5	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
6	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
7	be	be	VB	O	8	cop
8	alone	alone	RB	O	4	xcomp
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
11	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubj
12	just	just	RB	O	15	advmod
13	can	can	MD	O	15	aux
14	not	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	step	step	VB	O	4	conj
16	into	into	IN	O	19	case
17	people	people	NNS	O	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	world	world	NN	O	15	nmod
20	which	which	WDT	O	24	nsubjpass
21	have	have	VBP	O	24	aux
22	already	already	RB	O	24	advmod
23	been	be	VBN	O	24	auxpass
24	alienated	alienate	VBN	O	19	acl:relcl
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	wants	want	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
6	be	be	VB	O	8	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	catcher	catcher	NN	O	4	xcomp
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	rye	rye	NN	O	8	nmod
12	;	;	:	O	4	punct
13	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	wants	want	VBZ	O	4	parataxis
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	let	let	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	more	more	JJR	O	18	amod
18	children	child	NNS	O	19	nsubj
19	keep	keep	VBP	O	16	ccomp
20	their	they	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	innocence	innocence	NN	O	19	dobj
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Nevertheless	nevertheless	RB	O	12	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	12	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	power	power	NN	O	12	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	alienation	alienation	NN	O	4	nmod
7	by	by	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	society	society	NN	O	6	nmod
10	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
11	so	so	RB	O	12	advmod
12	strong	strong	JJ	O	0	ROOT
13	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
14	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
16	impossible	impossible	JJ	O	12	ccomp
17	for	for	IN	O	18	case
18	him	he	PRP	O	16	nmod
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	catch	catch	VB	O	16	xcomp
21	others	other	NNS	O	23	nmod:poss
22	'	'	POS	O	21	case
23	innocence	innocence	NN	O	20	dobj
24	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	know	know	VB	O	15	dep
5	what	what	WP	O	9	dobj
6	kind	kind	NN	O	9	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	life	life	NN	O	6	nmod
9	will	will	MD	O	4	ccomp
10	Holden	Holden	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
11	have	have	VBP	O	15	aux
12	with	with	IN	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	incessant	incessant	JJ	O	15	amod
15	disappoints	disappoint	NNS	O	0	ROOT
16	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Maybe	maybe	RB	O	5	advmod
2	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	5	cop
5	alone	alone	RB	O	0	ROOT
6	forever	forever	RB	O	5	advmod
7	,	,	,	O	5	punct
8	or	or	CC	O	5	cc
9	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubjpass
10	may	may	MD	O	12	aux
11	be	be	VB	O	12	auxpass
12	alienated	alienate	VBN	O	5	conj
13	by	by	IN	O	15	case
14	this	this	DT	O	15	det
15	society	society	NN	O	12	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	5	punct

