1	During	during	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	DATE	4	det
3	19th	19th	JJ	DATE	4	amod
4	century	century	NN	DATE	8	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	had	have	VBD	O	8	aux
8	become	become	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	a	a	DT	O	12	det
10	popular	popular	JJ	O	12	amod
11	medical	medical	JJ	O	12	amod
12	treatment	treatment	NN	O	8	xcomp
13	for	for	IN	O	15	case
14	numerous	numerous	JJ	O	15	amod
15	aliments	aliment	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
17	also	also	RB	O	19	advmod
18	a	a	DT	O	19	det
19	form	form	NN	O	12	conj
20	of	of	IN	O	21	case
21	anesthesia	anesthesia	NN	O	19	nmod
22	for	for	IN	O	23	case
23	surgery	surgery	NN	O	8	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	5	mark
2	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubjpass
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	auxpass
4	generally	generally	RB	O	5	advmod
5	seen	see	VBN	O	22	advcl
6	as	as	IN	O	9	case
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	parlor	parlor	NN	O	9	compound
9	trick	trick	NN	O	5	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	22	punct
11	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	22	nsubj
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	which	which	WDT	O	16	nsubjpass
14	is	be	VBZ	O	16	auxpass
15	now	now	RB	DATE	16	advmod
16	referred	refer	VBN	O	11	acl:relcl
17	to	to	TO	O	16	xcomp
18	as	as	IN	O	19	case
19	hypnosis	hypnosis	NN	O	16	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	11	punct
21	is	be	VBZ	O	22	aux
22	beginning	begin	VBG	O	0	ROOT
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	reappear	reappear	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	as	as	IN	O	28	case
26	a	a	DT	O	28	det
27	legitimate	legitimate	JJ	O	28	amod
28	form	form	NN	O	24	nmod
29	of	of	IN	O	30	case
30	treatment	treatment	NN	O	28	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	Mesmerism	Mesmerism	NNP	O	5	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	5	cop
3	at	at	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	height	height	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	its	its	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	popularity	popularity	NN	O	5	nmod
9	during	during	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	1840	1840	CD	DATE	5	nmod
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	,	,	,	O	11	punct
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	time	time	NN	O	22	dobj
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	which	which	WDT	O	15	nmod
18	Edgar	Edgar	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
19	Allan	Allan	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
20	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
21	was	be	VBD	O	22	aux
22	writing	write	VBG	O	11	acl:relcl
23	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	popular	popular	JJ	O	5	amod
5	writer	writer	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	thus	thus	RB	O	29	advmod
8	``	``	``	O	29	punct
9	it	it	PRP	O	29	dep
10	was	be	VBD	O	11	cop
11	logical	logical	JJ	O	9	dep
12	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
13	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
14	,	,	,	O	25	punct
15	as	as	IN	O	18	mark
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	journalist	journalist	NN	O	18	dep
18	sensitive	sensitive	JJ	O	25	dep
19	to	to	TO	O	21	case
20	popular	popular	JJ	O	21	amod
21	interest	interest	NN	O	18	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	25	punct
23	should	should	MD	O	25	aux
24	have	have	VB	O	25	aux
25	exploited	exploit	VBN	O	11	ccomp
26	it	it	PRP	O	25	dobj
27	''	''	''	O	29	punct
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	Lind	Lind	NNP	PERSON	5	conj
30	1078	1078	CD	DATE	29	nummod
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
32	,	,	,	O	5	punct
33	according	accord	VBG	O	36	case
34	to	to	TO	O	33	mwe
35	Sidney	Sidney	NNP	PERSON	36	compound
36	Lind	Lind	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
37	in	in	IN	O	40	case
38	her	she	PRP$	O	40	nmod:poss
39	1947	1947	CD	DATE	40	nummod
40	article	article	NN	O	36	nmod
41	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	40	dep
42	and	and	CC	O	41	cc
43	Mesmerism	Mesmerism	NNP	O	41	conj
44	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	did	do	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	explore	explore	VB	O	2	ccomp
4	it	it	PRP	O	3	dobj
5	,	,	,	O	2	punct
6	by	by	IN	O	7	mark
7	writing	write	VBG	O	2	advcl
8	three	three	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
9	stories	story	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	all	all	DT	O	9	appos
12	mostly	mostly	RB	O	13	advmod
13	based	base	VBN	O	11	acl
14	on	on	IN	O	15	case
15	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	13	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	stories	story	NNS	O	10	nsubj
3	that	that	WDT	O	4	nsubj
4	feature	feature	VBP	O	2	acl:relcl
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	practice	practice	NN	O	4	dobj
7	are	be	VBP	O	10	cop
8	``	``	``	O	10	punct
9	A	a	DT	O	10	det
10	Tale	tale	NN	O	0	ROOT
11	of	of	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	Ragged	ragged	JJ	O	14	amod
14	Mountains	mountain	NNS	O	10	nmod
15	''	''	''	O	14	punct
16	,	,	,	O	14	punct
17	``	``	``	O	14	punct
18	Mesmeric	mesmeric	JJ	O	19	amod
19	Revelation	revelation	NN	O	14	conj
20	''	''	''	O	14	punct
21	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
22	``	``	``	O	14	punct
23	The	the	DT	O	24	det
24	Facts	fact	NNS	O	14	conj
25	in	in	IN	O	27	case
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	Case	case	NN	O	24	nmod
28	of	of	IN	O	30	case
29	M.	M.	NNP	PERSON	30	compound
30	Valdemar	Valdemar	NNP	PERSON	27	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	``	``	``	O	4	punct
3	The	the	DT	O	4	det
4	Facts	fact	NNS	O	20	nmod
5	in	in	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	Case	case	NN	MISC	4	nmod
8	of	of	IN	MISC	10	case
9	M.	M.	NNP	MISC	10	compound
10	Valdemar	Valdemar	NNP	MISC	7	nmod
11	''	''	''	MISC	4	punct
12	,	,	,	O	4	punct
13	which	which	WDT	O	15	nsubjpass
14	was	be	VBD	O	15	auxpass
15	written	write	VBN	O	4	acl:relcl
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	1845	1845	CD	DATE	15	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	20	punct
19	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	20	nsubj
20	seemed	seem	VBD	O	0	ROOT
21	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
22	be	be	VB	O	23	auxpass
23	influenced	influence	VBN	O	20	xcomp
24	by	by	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	popularity	popularity	NN	O	23	nmod
27	of	of	IN	O	28	case
28	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	26	nmod
29	,	,	,	O	20	punct
30	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	35	dep
31	's	's	POS	O	30	case
32	low	low	JJ	O	35	amod
33	life	life	NN	O	35	compound
34	expectancy	expectancy	NN	O	35	compound
35	rates	rate	NNS	O	20	ccomp
36	,	,	,	O	20	punct
37	the	the	DT	O	39	det
38	overall	overall	JJ	O	39	amod
39	way	way	NN	O	44	nsubjpass
40	the	the	DT	O	42	det
41	medical	medical	JJ	O	42	amod
42	community	community	NN	O	39	dep
43	was	be	VBD	O	44	auxpass
44	regarded	regard	VBN	O	20	conj
45	at	at	IN	O	47	case
46	the	the	DT	O	47	det
47	time	time	NN	DATE	44	nmod
48	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
49	by	by	IN	O	50	mark
50	examining	examine	VBG	O	61	advcl
51	these	these	DT	O	53	det
52	different	different	JJ	O	53	amod
53	influential	influential	JJ	O	50	xcomp
54	and	and	CC	O	50	cc
55	motivating	motivate	VBG	O	50	conj
56	factors	factor	NNS	O	55	dobj
57	,	,	,	O	61	punct
58	we	we	PRP	O	61	nsubj
59	can	can	MD	O	61	aux
60	better	better	RBR	O	61	advmod
61	understand	understand	VB	O	20	conj
62	the	the	DT	O	63	det
63	information	information	NN	O	61	dobj
64	in	in	IN	O	66	case
65	the	the	DT	O	66	det
66	story	story	NN	O	63	nmod
67	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	Mesmerism	Mesmerism	NNP	O	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	proposed	propose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	1770	1770	CD	DATE	3	nmod
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	by	by	IN	O	12	case
9	German	german	JJ	MISC	12	amod
10	physician	physician	NN	O	12	compound
11	Franz	Franz	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Mesmer	Mesmer	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	practice	practice	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	2	nmod
5	was	be	VBD	O	7	cop
6	very	very	RB	O	7	advmod
7	popular	popular	JJ	O	0	ROOT
8	from	from	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	1780	1780	CD	DATE	7	nmod
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	until	until	IN	O	10	dep
13	about	about	IN	DATE	14	case
14	1850	1850	CD	DATE	12	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	around	around	IN	O	4	case
4	1850	1850	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
5	when	when	WRB	O	9	advmod
6	actual	actual	JJ	O	7	amod
7	medicine	medicine	NN	O	9	nsubjpass
8	was	be	VBD	O	9	auxpass
9	discovered	discover	VBN	O	4	advcl
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	starting	start	VBG	O	9	conj
12	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
13	be	be	VB	O	15	auxpass
14	widely	widely	RB	O	15	advmod
15	used	use	VBN	O	11	xcomp
16	as	as	IN	O	18	case
17	an	a	DT	O	18	det
18	alternative	alternative	NN	O	15	nmod
19	to	to	TO	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	popular	popular	JJ	O	22	amod
22	practice	practice	NN	O	18	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	introduction	introduction	NN	O	18	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	chloroform	chloroform	NN	O	2	nmod
5	in	in	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	DATE	7	det
7	1830s	1830s	CD	DATE	4	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
9	ether	ether	NN	O	4	conj
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	1840s	1840	NNS	DATE	9	nmod
12	for	for	IN	O	13	case
13	use	use	NN	O	11	nmod
14	as	as	IN	O	15	case
15	anesthesia	anesthesia	NN	O	13	nmod
16	may	may	MD	O	18	aux
17	have	have	VB	O	18	aux
18	contributed	contribute	VBN	O	0	ROOT
19	to	to	TO	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	decline	decline	NN	O	18	nmod
22	of	of	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	use	use	NN	O	21	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	24	nmod
27	by	by	IN	O	29	case
28	healthcare	healthcare	NN	O	29	compound
29	professionals	professional	NNS	O	18	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	8	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	8	punct
3	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	8	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	8	auxpass
5	still	still	RB	O	8	advmod
6	very	very	RB	O	7	advmod
7	much	much	JJ	O	8	advmod
8	debated	debate	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	discussed	discuss	VBN	O	8	conj
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	medical	medical	JJ	O	13	amod
13	journals	journal	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	1840	1840	CD	DATE	13	nmod
17	's	's	POS	O	10	xcomp
18	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	easy	easy	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	see	see	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	why	why	WRB	O	8	advmod
7	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	took	take	VBD	O	5	advcl
9	such	such	PDT	O	11	det:predet
10	an	a	DT	O	11	det
11	interest	interest	NN	O	8	dobj
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	mesmerizing	mesmerizing	JJ	O	8	advcl
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
2	himself	himself	PRP	O	1	nmod:npmod
3	might	might	MD	O	6	aux
4	have	have	VB	O	6	aux
5	been	be	VBN	O	6	aux
6	trying	try	VBG	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	become	become	VB	O	6	xcomp
9	involved	involve	VBN	O	8	xcomp
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	discussions	discussion	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Mendenhall	Mendenhall	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	did	do	VBD	O	2	ccomp
6	this	this	DT	O	5	dobj
7	by	by	IN	O	9	case
8	``	``	``	O	9	punct
9	dissertating	dissertate	VBG	O	5	nmod
10	with	with	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	hopes	hope	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
14	,	,	,	O	20	punct
15	one	one	CD	DURATION	16	nummod
16	day	day	NN	DURATION	20	nsubj
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	scientists	scientist	NNS	O	16	appos
19	would	would	MD	O	20	aux
20	look	look	VB	O	9	dep
21	on	on	IN	O	23	case
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	fiction	fiction	NN	O	20	nmod
24	as	as	IN	O	26	case
25	a	a	DT	O	26	det
26	catalyst	catalyst	NN	O	20	nmod
27	for	for	IN	O	31	case
28	new	new	JJ	O	31	amod
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	innovative	innovative	JJ	O	28	conj
31	practices	practice	NNS	O	26	nmod
32	''	''	''	O	9	punct
33	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
34	Mendenhall	Mendenhall	NNP	PERSON	9	appos
35	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
36	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	time	time	NN	DATE	10	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	10	punct
5	new	new	JJ	O	6	amod
6	inventions	invention	NNS	O	10	nsubj
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	discoveries	discovery	NNS	O	6	conj
9	were	be	VBD	O	10	aux
10	advancing	advance	VBG	O	0	ROOT
11	modern	modern	JJ	O	12	amod
12	medicine	medicine	NN	O	10	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	may	may	MD	O	5	aux
3	have	have	VB	O	5	aux
4	been	be	VBN	O	5	aux
5	writing	write	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	on	on	IN	O	25	case
7	the	the	DT	O	25	det
8	subject	subject	JJ	O	25	amod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	encourage	encourage	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	future	future	JJ	DATE	12	amod
12	scientists	scientist	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	doctors	doctor	NNS	O	12	conj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	move	move	VB	O	10	xcomp
17	back	back	RB	O	16	advmod
18	towards	towards	IN	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	metaphysical	metaphysical	JJ	O	21	amod
21	way	way	NN	O	16	nmod
22	of	of	IN	O	23	mark
23	looking	look	VBG	O	21	acl
24	at	at	IN	O	23	nmod
25	medicine	medicine	NN	O	5	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	influence	influence	NN	O	9	nsubj
3	that	that	WDT	O	4	nsubj
4	mesmerizing	mesmerize	VBG	O	2	acl:relcl
5	had	have	VBD	O	4	dep
6	on	on	IN	O	7	case
7	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
8	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
9	astounding	astounding	JJ	O	16	ccomp
10	,	,	,	O	16	punct
11	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	16	cop
13	such	such	JJ	O	16	case
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	popular	popular	JJ	O	16	amod
16	practice	practice	NN	O	0	ROOT
17	at	at	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	time	time	NN	DATE	16	nmod
20	that	that	WDT	O	22	dobj
21	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
22	wrote	write	VBD	O	19	acl:relcl
23	three	three	CD	NUMBER	24	nummod
24	stories	story	NNS	O	22	dobj
25	about	about	IN	O	26	case
26	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	22	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	36	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	36	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	36	neg
4	a	a	DT	O	36	det
5	far	far	RB	O	36	advmod
6	stretch	stretch	NN	O	5	nmod:npmod
7	for	for	IN	O	8	case
8	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	case
10	transition	transition	NN	O	5	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	topic	topic	NN	O	5	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	13	nmod
16	from	from	IN	O	19	case
17	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	other	other	JJ	O	19	amod
19	writings	writings	NNS	O	15	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	5	punct
21	as	as	IN	O	22	case
22	attested	attested	NN	O	5	nmod
23	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
24	by	by	IN	O	26	case
25	Matthew	Matthew	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
26	Taylor	Taylor	NNP	PERSON	28	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	28	punct
28	author	author	NN	O	22	acl
29	of	of	IN	O	31	case
30	Allen	Allen	NNP	PERSON	31	compound
31	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	28	nmod
32	's	's	POS	O	31	case
33	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
34	Meta	meta	NN	ORGANIZATION	22	appos
35	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
36	physics	physics	NN	O	0	ROOT
37	.	.	.	O	36	punct

1	Taylor	Taylor	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	wrote	write	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	``	``	``	O	7	punct
5	So	so	RB	O	6	advmod
6	well	well	RB	O	7	advmod
7	suited	suit	VBN	O	2	dep
8	to	to	TO	O	11	case
9	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	principles	principle	NNS	O	7	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	literary	literary	JJ	O	14	amod
14	composition	composition	NN	O	11	nmod
15	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
16	it	it	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	18	cop
18	natural	natural	JJ	O	7	ccomp
19	for	for	IN	O	20	case
20	him	he	PRP	O	18	nmod
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	work	work	VB	O	2	xcomp
23	this	this	DT	O	25	det
24	new	new	JJ	O	25	amod
25	field	field	NN	O	22	dobj
26	,	,	,	O	22	punct
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	attempt	attempt	VB	O	22	advcl
29	to	to	TO	O	30	mark
30	achieve	achieve	VB	O	28	xcomp
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	sensational	sensational	JJ	O	30	dobj
33	without	without	IN	O	35	mark
34	deliberately	deliberately	RB	O	35	advmod
35	attempting	attempt	VBG	O	30	advcl
36	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
37	mislead	mislead	VB	O	35	xcomp
38	''	''	''	O	37	punct
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	Taylor	Taylor	NNP	PERSON	30	dep
41	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct
42	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	writing	write	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	widely	widely	RB	O	5	advmod
5	focused	focus	VBN	O	3	xcomp
6	on	on	IN	O	7	case
7	death	death	NN	O	5	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	3	punct
9	which	which	WDT	O	12	dobj
10	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	also	also	RB	O	12	advmod
12	seemed	seem	VBD	O	3	dep
13	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
14	be	be	VB	O	16	cop
15	very	very	RB	O	16	advmod
16	interested	interested	JJ	O	12	xcomp
17	in	in	IN	O	16	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	``	``	``	O	4	punct
3	The	the	DT	O	4	det
4	Facts	fact	NNS	O	13	nmod
5	in	in	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	Case	case	NN	O	4	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	12	case
9	M.	M.	NNP	O	12	compound
10	Valdemar	Valdemar	NNP	O	12	compound
11	''	''	''	O	12	punct
12	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod
13	combines	combine	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	two	two	CD	NUMBER	13	nsubj
16	with	with	IN	O	18	case
17	an	a	DT	O	18	det
18	interest	interest	NN	O	15	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	prolonging	prolong	VBG	O	21	amod
21	life	life	NN	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	fascination	fascination	NN	O	10	nsubj
4	with	with	IN	O	5	case
5	life	life	NN	O	3	nmod
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	death	death	NN	O	5	conj
8	could	could	MD	O	10	aux
9	have	have	VB	O	10	aux
10	been	be	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	two-fold	two-fold	RB	O	10	advmod
12	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	During	during	IN	O	4	case
2	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	life	life	NN	O	15	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	15	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	life	life	NN	O	8	compound
8	expectancy	expectancy	NN	O	15	nsubj
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	average	average	JJ	O	12	amod
12	individual	individual	NN	O	8	nmod
13	was	be	VBD	O	15	cop
14	much	much	RB	O	15	advmod
15	less	less	JJR	O	0	ROOT
16	than	than	IN	O	19	mark
17	it	it	PRP	O	19	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	19	cop
19	present	present	JJ	DATE	15	ccomp
20	day	day	NN	DURATION	19	nmod:tmod
21	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Today	today	NN	DATE	7	nmod:tmod
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	modern	modern	JJ	O	4	amod
4	medicine	medicine	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	greatly	greatly	RB	O	7	advmod
7	increased	increase	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	11	det
9	average	average	JJ	O	11	amod
10	life	life	NN	O	11	compound
11	expectancy	expectancy	NN	O	7	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	15	case
13	approximately	approximately	RB	O	14	advmod
14	78	78	CD	DURATION	15	nummod
15	years	year	NNS	DURATION	7	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	20	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	20	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	average	average	JJ	O	6	amod
5	life	life	NN	O	6	compound
6	expectancy	expectancy	NN	O	20	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	individuals	individual	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	living	live	VBG	O	8	acl
10	in	in	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
13	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	9	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	DATE	16	det
16	mid-1800s	mid-1800s	CD	DATE	9	nmod
17	was	be	VBD	O	20	cop
18	under	under	IN	O	20	case
19	40	40	CD	DURATION	20	nummod
20	years	year	NNS	DURATION	0	ROOT
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	age	age	NN	O	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	story	story	NN	O	20	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	``	``	``	O	8	punct
7	The	the	DT	O	8	det
8	Facts	fact	NNS	O	4	appos
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	Case	case	NN	O	8	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	M.	M.	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Valdemar	Valdemar	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod
15	''	''	''	O	8	punct
16	,	,	,	O	20	punct
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	main	main	JJ	O	19	amod
19	character	character	NN	O	20	nsubj
20	attempted	attempt	VBN	O	0	ROOT
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	extend	extend	VB	O	20	xcomp
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	life	life	NN	O	22	dobj
25	of	of	IN	O	28	case
26	a	a	DT	O	28	det
27	dying	die	VBG	O	28	amod
28	man	man	NN	O	24	nmod
29	by	by	IN	O	30	mark
30	mesmerizing	mesmerize	VBG	O	22	advcl
31	him	he	PRP	O	30	dobj
32	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	patient	patient	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	continued	continue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
5	be	be	VB	O	6	cop
6	responsive	responsive	JJ	O	3	xcomp
7	even	even	RB	O	10	advmod
8	after	after	IN	O	10	mark
9	death	death	NN	O	10	dep
10	due	due	JJ	O	6	advcl
11	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
12	being	be	VBG	O	15	cop
13	under	under	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	spell	spell	NN	O	10	advcl
16	,	,	,	O	6	punct
17	thereby	thereby	RB	O	18	advmod
18	extending	extend	VBG	O	6	xcomp
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	period	period	NN	O	18	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	time	time	NN	O	20	nmod
23	that	that	IN	O	26	mark
24	he	he	PRP	O	26	nsubj
25	was	be	VBD	O	26	cop
26	alive	alive	JJ	O	3	ccomp
27	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	reason	reason	NN	O	21	nsubj
3	that	that	WDT	O	13	dobj
4	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubjpass
5	might	might	MD	O	8	aux
6	have	have	VB	O	8	aux
7	been	be	VBN	O	8	auxpass
8	preoccupied	preoccupy	VBN	O	2	acl:relcl
9	with	with	IN	O	10	case
10	death	death	NN	O	8	nmod
11	enough	enough	RB	O	10	advmod
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	influence	influence	VB	O	8	xcomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	writing	writing	NN	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	this	this	DT	O	18	det
18	story	story	NN	O	15	nmod
19	is	be	VBZ	O	21	cop
20	more	more	RBR	O	21	advmod
21	personal	personal	JJ	O	0	ROOT
22	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	During	during	IN	O	4	case
2	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	life	life	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	lost	lose	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	many	many	JJ	O	7	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
11	loved	love	VBN	O	12	amod
12	ones	one	NNS	O	8	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	young	young	JJ	O	4	amod
4	age	age	NN	O	9	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	three	three	CD	NUMBER	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	9	punct
8	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
9	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	orphaned	orphan	VBN	O	9	xcomp
11	when	when	WRB	O	14	advmod
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	father	father	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	deserted	desert	VBD	O	10	acl:relcl
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	family	family	NN	O	20	nsubj
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	mother	mother	NN	O	16	conj
20	died	die	VBD	O	14	ccomp
21	soon	soon	RB	O	20	advmod
22	after	after	IN	O	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	young	young	JJ	O	4	amod
4	brother	brother	NN	O	15	nsubj
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	woman	woman	NN	O	4	conj
8	who	who	WP	O	9	nsubj
9	raised	raise	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
10	him	he	PRP	O	9	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	4	punct
12	Mrs.	Mrs.	NNP	O	13	compound
13	Allan	Allan	NNP	PERSON	4	appos
14	also	also	RB	O	15	advmod
15	perished	perish	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Virginia	Virginia	NNP	LOCATION	8	nsubjpass
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
4	's	's	POS	O	3	case
5	wife	wife	NN	O	1	appos
6	,	,	,	O	1	punct
7	was	be	VBD	O	8	auxpass
8	diagnosed	diagnose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	with	with	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	same	same	JJ	O	12	amod
12	disease	disease	NN	O	8	nmod
13	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
14	brother	brother	NN	O	16	compound
15	,	,	,	O	16	punct
16	mother	mother	NN	O	19	compound
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	foster	foster	JJ	O	16	conj
19	mother	mother	NN	O	21	nsubj
20	had	have	VBD	O	21	aux
21	died	die	VBN	O	12	acl:relcl
22	of	of	IN	O	21	nmod
23	;	;	:	O	12	punct
24	tuberculosis	tuberculosis	NN	O	12	dep
25	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	person	person	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	being	be	VBG	O	4	auxpass
4	mesmerized	mesmerize	VBN	O	2	acl
5	,	,	,	O	2	punct
6	M.	M.	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Valdemar	Valdemar	NNP	PERSON	2	appos
8	,	,	,	O	2	punct
9	was	be	VBD	O	11	aux
10	also	also	RB	O	11	advmod
11	dying	die	VBG	O	0	ROOT
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	this	this	DT	O	14	det
14	disease	disease	NN	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	``	``	``	O	31	punct
17	his	he	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	physicians	physician	NNS	O	31	dep
19	had	have	VBD	O	20	aux
20	declared	declare	VBN	O	18	acl:relcl
21	him	he	PRP	O	20	dobj
22	in	in	IN	O	25	case
23	a	a	DT	O	25	det
24	confirmed	confirm	VBN	O	25	amod
25	phthisis	phthisis	NN	O	20	nmod
26	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	27	punct
27	tuberculosis	tuberculosis	NN	O	25	nmod
28	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
29	''	''	''	O	31	punct
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Poe	Poe	NNP	O	14	appos
32	14	14	CD	NUMBER	31	nummod
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
34	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	very	very	RB	O	4	advmod
4	ill	ill	RB	O	11	dep
5	at	at	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	time	time	NN	DATE	4	nmod
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	story	story	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
10	was	be	VBD	O	11	auxpass
11	written	write	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	passed	pass	VBN	O	11	conj
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	1847	1847	CD	DATE	11	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	11	punct
17	just	just	RB	O	19	advmod
18	two	two	CD	DURATION	19	nummod
19	years	year	NNS	DURATION	11	nmod
20	after	after	IN	O	19	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	story	story	NN	O	24	nmod:poss
23	's	's	POS	O	22	case
24	completion	completion	NN	O	19	dep
25	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	tragedies	tragedy	NNS	O	5	nsubj
3	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
4	have	have	VB	O	5	aux
5	shaped	shape	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	5	dobj
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	writing	writing	NN	O	6	conj
10	;	;	:	O	5	punct
11	influencing	influence	VBG	O	5	parataxis
12	him	he	PRP	O	11	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	write	write	VB	O	11	xcomp
15	about	about	IN	O	17	case
16	this	this	DT	O	17	det
17	topic	topic	NN	O	14	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
19	reflecting	reflect	VBG	O	11	conj
20	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
21	hidden	hidden	JJ	O	22	amod
22	desire	desire	NN	O	19	dobj
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	lengthen	lengthen	VB	O	19	advcl
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	lives	life	NNS	O	24	dobj
27	of	of	IN	O	30	case
28	his	he	PRP$	O	30	nmod:poss
29	loved	love	VBN	O	30	amod
30	ones	one	NNS	O	26	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	5	advmod
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	story	story	NN	O	5	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	written	write	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	shed	shed	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	light	light	JJ	O	9	amod
9	one	one	CD	NUMBER	7	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	major	major	JJ	O	13	amod
13	issues	issue	NNS	O	9	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	time	time	NN	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	medical	medical	JJ	O	19	amod
19	care	care	NN	O	16	appos
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	According	accord	VBG	O	5	case
2	to	to	TO	O	1	mwe
3	their	they	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
4	research	research	NN	O	5	compound
5	students	student	NNS	O	21	nmod
6	that	that	WDT	O	9	dobj
7	UNC	UNC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	Pembroke	Pembroke	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nsubj
9	discovered	discover	VBD	O	5	acl:relcl
10	that	that	IN	O	9	advmod
11	,	,	,	O	9	punct
12	during	during	IN	O	14	case
13	this	this	DT	O	14	det
14	time	time	NN	O	9	nmod
15	medical	medical	JJ	O	16	amod
16	care	care	NN	O	21	nsubj
17	``	``	``	O	21	punct
18	was	be	VBD	O	21	cop
19	most	most	RBS	O	20	advmod
20	often	often	RB	O	21	advmod
21	inadequate	inadequate	JJ	O	0	ROOT
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	insufficient	insufficient	JJ	O	21	conj
24	in	in	IN	O	28	case
25	meeting	meeting	NN	O	26	compound
26	patients	patient	NNS	O	28	nmod:poss
27	'	'	POS	O	26	case
28	needs	need	NNS	O	21	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	Diseases	disease	NNS	O	5	nsubj
2	were	be	VBD	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	major	major	JJ	O	5	amod
5	problem	problem	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	led	lead	VBD	O	5	conj
8	to	to	TO	O	10	case
9	many	many	JJ	O	10	amod
10	deaths	death	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	''	''	''	O	10	punct
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
13	Collins	Collins	NNP	PERSON	10	appos
14	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Tuberculosis	tuberculosis	NN	O	7	nsubj
2	along	along	IN	O	7	advmod
3	with	with	IN	O	6	case
4	many	many	JJ	O	6	amod
5	other	other	JJ	O	6	amod
6	culprits	culprit	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	claimed	claim	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	lives	life	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	many	many	JJ	O	13	amod
12	American	american	JJ	MISC	13	amod
13	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	9	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	inability	inability	NN	O	13	nsubj
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	medical	medical	JJ	O	5	amod
5	field	field	NN	O	7	nsubj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	prevent	prevent	VB	O	2	acl
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	treat	treat	VB	O	7	conj
10	disease	disease	NN	O	7	dobj
11	may	may	MD	O	13	aux
12	have	have	VB	O	13	aux
13	influenced	influence	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	13	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	write	write	VB	O	13	xcomp
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	story	story	NN	O	16	dobj
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	form	form	NN	O	16	nmod
22	of	of	IN	O	25	case
23	a	a	DT	O	25	det
24	medical	medical	JJ	O	25	amod
25	record	record	NN	O	21	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	may	may	MD	O	5	aux
3	have	have	VB	O	5	aux
4	been	be	VBN	O	5	aux
5	trying	try	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	illustrate	illustrate	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	an	a	DT	O	9	det
9	individual	individual	NN	O	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	need	need	NN	O	7	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	seek	seek	VB	O	11	acl
14	any	any	DT	O	15	det
15	care	care	NN	O	16	nsubj
16	available	available	JJ	O	13	xcomp
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	theory	theory	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	rejected	reject	VBD	O	3	ccomp
7	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	6	dobj
8	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
9	did	do	VBD	O	11	aux
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	want	want	VB	O	6	conj
12	people	people	NNS	O	11	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	use	use	VB	O	11	xcomp
15	it	it	PRP	O	14	dobj
16	because	because	IN	O	21	mark
17	it	it	PRP	O	21	nsubj
18	did	do	VBD	O	21	aux
19	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
20	``	``	``	O	21	punct
21	lead	lead	VB	O	14	advcl
22	down	down	RP	O	21	compound:prt
23	a	a	DT	O	24	det
24	road	road	NN	O	21	dobj
25	to	to	TO	O	27	case
26	human	human	JJ	O	27	amod
27	improvement	improvement	NN	O	21	nmod
28	''	''	''	O	27	punct
29	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	30	punct
30	Mendenhall	Mendenhall	NNP	PERSON	27	appos
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	30	punct
32	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	could	could	MD	O	4	aux
3	have	have	VB	O	4	aux
4	written	write	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	this	this	DT	O	6	det
6	story	story	NN	O	4	dobj
7	like	like	IN	O	11	case
8	an	a	DT	O	11	det
9	legitimate	legitimate	JJ	O	11	amod
10	medical	medical	JJ	O	11	amod
11	report	report	NN	O	4	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	discourage	discourage	VB	O	4	advcl
14	people	people	NNS	O	13	dobj
15	from	from	IN	O	16	mark
16	using	use	VBG	O	13	advcl
17	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	16	dobj
18	as	as	IN	O	21	case
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	medical	medical	JJ	O	21	amod
21	treatment	treatment	NN	O	16	nmod
22	because	because	IN	O	26	mark
23	he	he	PRP	O	26	nsubj
24	did	do	VBD	O	26	aux
25	not	not	RB	O	26	neg
26	think	think	VB	O	13	advcl
27	it	it	PRP	O	30	nsubjpass
28	should	should	MD	O	30	aux
29	be	be	VB	O	30	auxpass
30	used	use	VBN	O	26	ccomp
31	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	reason	reason	NN	O	22	nsubj
3	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
4	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
5	might	might	MD	O	7	aux
6	have	have	VB	O	7	aux
7	written	write	VBN	O	2	dep
8	``	``	``	O	10	punct
9	The	the	DT	O	10	det
10	Facts	fact	NNS	O	7	dobj
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Case	case	NN	O	10	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	M.	M.	NNP	PERSON	16	compound
16	Valdemar	Valdemar	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod
17	''	''	''	O	10	punct
18	like	like	IN	O	21	case
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	factual	factual	JJ	O	21	amod
21	case	case	NN	O	7	nmod
22	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	highlight	highlight	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	lack	lack	NN	O	24	dobj
27	of	of	IN	O	28	case
28	treatment	treatment	NN	O	26	nmod
29	of	of	IN	O	30	case
30	diseases	disease	NNS	O	28	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	story	story	NN	O	6	nmod
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	doctors	doctor	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	did	do	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	very	very	RB	O	8	advmod
8	little	little	JJ	O	6	xcomp
9	except	except	IN	O	10	mark
10	observe	observe	VBP	O	6	advcl
11	what	what	WP	O	13	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	13	aux
13	going	go	VBG	O	10	ccomp
14	on	on	IN	O	13	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	are	be	VBP	O	3	cop
3	examples	example	NNS	O	0	ROOT
4	of	of	IN	O	7	mark
5	what	what	WP	O	7	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	7	aux
7	happening	happen	VBG	O	3	acl
8	socially	socially	RB	O	7	xcomp
9	during	during	IN	O	11	case
10	that	that	DT	O	11	det
11	time	time	NN	O	8	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	history	history	NN	O	11	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	3	case
2	an	a	DT	O	3	det
3	understanding	understanding	NN	O	12	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	these	these	DT	O	7	det
6	historical	historical	JJ	O	7	amod
7	information	information	NN	O	3	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	12	punct
9	it	it	PRP	O	12	nsubj
10	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
11	better	better	RB	O	12	advmod
12	help	help	VB	O	0	ROOT
13	shape	shape	VB	O	12	xcomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	understanding	understanding	NN	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	story	story	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	An	a	DT	O	2	det
2	understanding	understanding	NN	O	12	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	all	all	DT	O	2	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	10	case
6	these	these	DT	O	10	det
7	historical	historical	JJ	O	10	amod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	cultural	cultural	JJ	O	7	conj
10	events	event	NNS	O	4	nmod
11	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
12	help	help	VB	O	0	ROOT
13	shape	shape	VB	O	12	xcomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	meaning	meaning	NN	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	story	story	NN	O	15	nmod
19	``	``	``	O	18	punct
20	The	the	DT	O	21	det
21	Facts	fact	NNS	O	18	dep
22	in	in	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	Case	case	NN	O	21	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	M.	M.	NNP	O	27	compound
27	Valdemar	Valdemar	NNP	O	24	nmod
28	''	''	''	O	18	punct
29	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	fact	fact	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
4	mesmerism	mesmerism	NN	O	8	nsubj
5	was	be	VBD	O	8	cop
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	widespread	widespread	JJ	O	8	amod
8	idea	idea	NN	O	2	dep
9	combined	combine	VBN	O	2	acl
10	with	with	IN	O	14	case
11	the	the	DT	O	14	det
12	low	low	JJ	O	14	amod
13	life	life	NN	O	14	compound
14	expectancy	expectancy	NN	O	9	nmod
15	because	because	IN	O	26	mark
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	both	both	DT	O	18	cc:preconj
18	diseases	disease	NNS	O	26	nmod
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	poor	poor	JJ	O	22	amod
21	health	health	NN	O	22	compound
22	care	care	NN	O	18	conj
23	,	,	,	O	26	punct
24	it	it	PRP	O	26	nsubj
25	is	be	VBZ	O	26	cop
26	easy	easy	JJ	O	9	advcl
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	see	see	VB	O	26	xcomp
29	why	why	WRB	O	31	advmod
30	Poe	Poe	NNP	PERSON	31	nsubj
31	chose	choose	VBD	O	28	advcl
32	to	to	TO	O	33	mark
33	write	write	VB	O	31	xcomp
34	a	a	DT	O	35	det
35	story	story	NN	O	33	dobj
36	about	about	IN	O	38	case
37	these	these	DT	O	38	det
38	subjects	subject	NNS	O	35	nmod
39	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	knowledge	knowledge	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	can	can	MD	O	5	aux
4	completely	completely	RB	O	5	advmod
5	change	change	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	how	how	WRB	O	10	advmod
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	story	story	NN	O	10	nsubjpass
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	auxpass
10	read	read	VBN	O	5	ccomp
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	understood	understand	VBN	O	10	conj
13	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Instead	instead	RB	O	6	advmod
2	of	of	IN	O	6	case
3	a	a	DT	O	6	det
4	creepy	creepy	JJ	O	6	amod
5	fictional	fictional	JJ	O	6	amod
6	story	story	NN	O	16	advcl
7	with	with	IN	O	11	case
8	a	a	DT	O	11	det
9	weird	weird	JJ	O	10	amod
10	disgusting	disgusting	JJ	O	11	amod
11	ending	ending	NN	O	6	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	16	punct
13	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubjpass
14	can	can	MD	O	16	aux
15	be	be	VB	O	16	auxpass
16	read	read	VBN	O	0	ROOT
17	as	as	IN	O	20	case
18	an	a	DT	O	20	det
19	informative	informative	JJ	O	20	amod
20	piece	piece	NN	O	16	nmod
21	about	about	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	subjects	subject	NNS	O	20	nmod
24	popular	popular	JJ	O	23	amod
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	important	important	JJ	O	24	conj
27	to	to	TO	O	28	case
28	people	people	NNS	O	16	nmod
29	in	in	IN	O	32	case
30	the	the	DT	DATE	32	det
31	mid-19th	mid-19th	JJ	DATE	32	amod
32	century	century	NN	DATE	28	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Collins	Collins	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Timmy	Timmy	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	William	William	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Harris	Harris	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
7	,	,	,	O	3	punct
8	Mary	Mary	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
9	K.	K.	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
10	Inman	Inman	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
11	,	,	,	O	3	punct
12	Ronnie	Ronnie	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Locklear	Locklear	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
14	,	,	,	O	3	punct
15	Malaika	Malaika	NNP	PERSON	16	compound
16	Ratley	Ratley	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
17	,	,	,	O	3	punct
18	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
19	Veronica	Veronica	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
20	Revels	Revels	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
21	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Health	Health	NNP	O	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct
4	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	04	04	NN	DATE	0	ROOT
2	Nov.	Nov.	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2014	2014	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

