1	``	``	``	O	4	punct
2	YOU	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	'RE	be	VBP	O	4	cop
4	PATHETIC	pathetic	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	!	!	.	O	4	punct
6	''	''	''	O	4	punct

1	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	yelled	yell	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	``	``	``	O	26	punct
2	JUST	just	RB	O	26	advmod
3	BECAUSE	because	IN	O	7	case
4	THEY	THEY	NNP	O	7	compound
5	MADE	MADE	NNP	O	7	compound
6	A	A	NNP	O	7	compound
7	FOOL	FOOL	NNP	O	2	nmod
8	OF	of	IN	O	9	case
9	YOU	you	PRP	O	7	nmod
10	AT	at	IN	O	11	case
11	SCHOOL	SCHOOL	NNP	O	9	nmod
12	YOU	you	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	WO	wo	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
14	N'T	not	RB	O	13	neg
15	EVEN	even	JJ	O	16	amod
16	LISTEN	listen	NN	O	13	dobj
17	-	-	:	O	9	punct
18	''	''	''	O	9	punct
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
20	Pg	pg	NN	O	7	appos
21	.361	.361	CD	NUMBER	20	nummod
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
23	,	,	,	O	26	punct
24	those	those	DT	O	26	nsubj
25	are	be	VBP	O	26	cop
26	words	word	NNS	O	0	ROOT
27	that	that	WDT	O	31	nsubjpass
28	must	must	MD	O	31	aux
29	not	not	RB	O	31	neg
30	be	be	VB	O	31	auxpass
31	told	tell	VBN	O	26	acl:relcl
32	to	to	TO	O	34	case
33	a	a	DT	O	34	det
34	teacher	teacher	NN	O	31	nmod
35	,	,	,	O	34	punct
36	an	a	DT	O	37	det
37	authority	authority	NN	O	34	conj
38	,	,	,	O	34	punct
39	and	and	CC	O	34	cc
40	an	a	DT	O	41	det
41	adult	adult	NN	O	34	conj
42	.	.	.	O	26	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	6	advmod
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	law	law	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	does	do	VBZ	O	6	aux
5	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
6	apply	apply	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	10	case
8	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	nmod:poss
9	'	'	POS	O	8	case
10	students	student	NNS	O	6	nmod
11	who	who	WP	O	12	nsubj
12	lack	lack	VBP	O	10	ccomp
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	respect	respect	NN	O	12	nmod
15	toward	toward	IN	O	16	case
16	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Is	be	VBZ	O	3	auxpass
2	clearly	clearly	RB	O	3	advmod
3	showed	show	VBN	O	23	dep
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	this	this	DT	O	6	det
6	passage	passage	NN	O	3	nmod
7	I	I	PRP	O	10	nsubj
8	have	have	VBP	O	10	aux
9	close	close	RB	O	10	advmod
10	read	read	VBN	O	6	acl:relcl
11	on	on	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Prisoner	prisoner	NN	MISC	10	nmod
14	of	of	IN	MISC	15	case
15	Azkaban	Azkaban	NNP	MISC	13	nmod
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	word	word	NN	O	19	compound
18	``	``	``	O	19	punct
19	respect	respect	NN	O	23	nsubj
20	''	''	''	O	19	punct
21	do	do	VBP	O	23	aux
22	not	not	RB	O	23	neg
23	exist	exist	VB	O	0	ROOT
24	in	in	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	vocabulary	vocabulary	NN	O	23	nmod
27	of	of	IN	O	31	case
28	most	most	JJS	O	29	amod
29	Hogwarts	hogwart	NNS	ORGANIZATION	31	nmod:poss
30	'	'	POS	O	29	case
31	students	student	NNS	O	26	nmod
32	upon	upon	IN	O	34	case
33	their	they	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
34	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	23	nmod
35	,	,	,	O	34	punct
36	which	which	WDT	O	41	dobj
37	most	most	RBS	O	38	advmod
38	readers	reader	NNS	O	41	nsubj
39	do	do	VBP	O	41	aux
40	not	not	RB	O	41	neg
41	notice	notice	VB	O	34	acl:relcl
42	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	students	student	NNS	O	12	nsubj
3	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	4	punct
4	children	child	NNS	O	2	appos
5	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	at	at	IN	O	7	case
7	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
8	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
9	on	on	IN	O	12	case
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	higher	higher	JJR	O	12	amod
12	position	position	NN	O	0	ROOT
13	than	than	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	17	punct
17	adults	adult	NNS	O	15	appos
18	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	17	punct
19	with	with	IN	O	21	case
20	more	more	JJR	O	21	amod
21	liberty	liberty	NN	O	15	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	commit	commit	VB	O	12	ccomp
24	errors	error	NNS	O	23	dobj
25	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
26	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
27	be	be	VB	O	28	auxpass
28	forgiven	forgive	VBN	O	23	conj
29	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	3	advmod
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	11	nsubjpass
4	whom	whom	WP	O	8	nsubj
5	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	continuing	continue	VBG	O	8	amod
8	observation	observation	NN	O	3	acl:relcl
9	,	,	,	O	11	punct
10	are	be	VBP	O	11	auxpass
11	treated	treat	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	differently	differently	RB	O	11	advmod
13	by	by	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	11	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
17	are	be	VBP	O	19	auxpass
18	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
19	listened	listen	VBN	O	11	conj
20	by	by	IN	O	21	case
21	him	he	PRP	O	19	nmod
22	as	as	RB	O	23	advmod
23	much	much	RB	O	19	advmod
24	as	as	IN	O	27	mark
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	students	student	NNS	O	27	nsubj
27	are	be	VBP	O	23	advcl
28	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	2	case
2	example	example	NN	O	13	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	13	punct
4	when	when	WRB	O	6	advmod
5	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	told	tell	VBD	O	13	advcl
7	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	6	dobj
8	about	about	IN	O	9	case
9	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod
10	``	``	``	O	13	punct
11	I	I	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	've	have	VBP	O	13	aux
13	told	tell	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	13	dobj
16	again	again	RB	O	13	advmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	again	again	RB	O	16	conj
19	that	that	IN	O	22	mark
20	you	you	PRP	O	22	nsubj
21	're	be	VBP	O	22	aux
22	helping	help	VBG	O	13	ccomp
23	your	you	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	old	old	JJ	O	25	amod
25	friend	friend	NN	O	22	dobj
26	Black	black	JJ	PERSON	25	amod
27	into	into	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	castle	castle	NN	O	22	nmod
30	,	,	,	O	29	punct
31	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	O	29	appos
32	,	,	,	O	29	punct
33	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
34	here	here	RB	O	37	advmod
35	's	be	VBZ	O	37	cop
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	proof	proof	NN	O	13	conj
38	.	.	.	O	13	punct
39	''	''	''	O	13	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	pg	pg	NN	O	6	appos
3	.358	.358	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Potter	Potter	NNP	PERSON	13	nsubj
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	6	conj
9	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
10	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	6	conj
11	do	do	VBP	O	13	aux
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	have	have	VB	O	0	ROOT
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	``	``	``	O	16	punct
16	fear	fear	NN	O	13	dobj
17	''	''	''	O	16	punct
18	most	most	RBS	O	19	advmod
19	students	student	NNS	O	22	nsubj
20	have	have	VBP	O	22	aux
21	upon	upon	IN	O	22	case
22	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	16	acl:relcl
23	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	capitalization	capitalization	NN	O	14	nmod
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	words	word	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	in	in	IN	O	2	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	book	book	NN	O	2	dep
10	-	-	:	O	14	punct
11	``	``	``	O	14	punct
12	YOU	you	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	'RE	be	VBP	O	14	cop
14	PATHETIC	pathetic	JJ	O	0	ROOT
15	!	!	.	O	14	punct
16	''	''	''	O	14	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	pg	pg	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	361	361	CD	NUMBER	29	nsubj
2	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	1	punct
3	,	,	,	O	1	punct
4	shows	show	VBZ	O	1	dep
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	raise	raise	NN	O	4	dobj
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	voice	voice	NN	O	6	nmod
10	when	when	WRB	O	11	advmod
11	talking	talk	VBG	O	4	dep
12	to	to	TO	O	13	case
13	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	1	punct
15	one	one	CD	NUMBER	1	appos
16	of	of	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	most	most	RBS	O	19	advmod
19	feared	fear	VBN	O	15	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	``	``	``	O	24	punct
22	respected	respect	VBN	O	24	amod
23	''	''	''	O	24	punct
24	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	19	conj
25	at	at	IN	O	26	case
26	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	1	punct
28	clearly	clearly	RB	O	29	advmod
29	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
30	how	how	WRB	O	33	advmod
31	confident	confident	JJ	O	30	dep
32	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	33	nsubj
33	is	be	VBZ	O	29	ccomp
34	just	just	RB	O	40	advmod
35	because	because	IN	O	40	mark
36	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	40	nsubj
37	is	be	VBZ	O	40	cop
38	on	on	IN	O	40	case
39	their	they	PRP$	O	40	nmod:poss
40	side	side	NN	O	33	advcl
41	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
42	is	be	VBZ	O	43	auxpass
43	fooled	fool	VBN	O	29	conj
44	by	by	IN	O	45	case
45	them	they	PRP	O	43	nmod
46	.	.	.	O	29	punct

1	Meaning	mean	VBG	O	0	ROOT
2	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
3	they	they	PRP	O	8	nsubjpass
4	wo	will	MD	O	8	aux
5	n't	not	RB	O	8	neg
6	ever	ever	RB	O	8	advmod
7	be	be	VB	O	8	auxpass
8	punished	punish	VBN	O	1	ccomp
9	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
10	they	they	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
12	do	do	VB	O	1	conj
13	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	15	dobj
14	they	they	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	feel	feel	VBP	O	12	ccomp
16	like	like	IN	O	17	mark
17	doing	do	VBG	O	15	advcl
18	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	8	advmod
2	others	other	NNS	O	3	compound
3	students	student	NNS	O	8	nsubj
4	at	at	IN	O	5	case
5	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nmod
6	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	confront	confront	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	raise	raise	VB	O	8	conj
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	voices	voice	NNS	O	8	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	15	case
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	teacher	teacher	NN	O	8	nmod
16	like	like	IN	O	22	mark
17	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	17	conj
20	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
21	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	17	conj
22	do	do	VBP	O	8	advcl
23	;	;	:	O	22	punct
24	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
25	not	not	RB	O	29	neg
26	all	all	DT	O	27	det
27	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	29	nsubj
28	will	will	MD	O	29	aux
29	let	let	VB	O	22	conj
30	them	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
31	confront	confront	VB	O	29	ccomp
32	them	they	PRP	O	31	dobj
33	either	either	RB	O	31	advmod
34	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	all	all	DT	O	0	ROOT
4	because	because	IN	O	7	mark
5	they	they	PRP	O	7	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	7	cop
7	privileged	privileged	JJ	O	3	dep
8	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
3	no	no	RB	O	4	neg
4	longer	longer	RB	O	7	advmod
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	only	only	JJ	O	7	amod
7	one	one	NN	NUMBER	24	ccomp
8	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
9	can	can	MD	O	10	aux
10	do	do	VB	O	7	acl:relcl
11	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	13	dobj
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	please	please	VB	O	10	ccomp
14	,	,	,	O	24	punct
15	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	24	nsubj
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	15	conj
18	,	,	,	O	15	punct
19	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
20	two	two	CD	NUMBER	22	nummod
21	best	best	JJS	O	22	amod
22	friends	friend	NNS	O	15	appos
23	,	,	,	O	15	punct
24	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
25	just	just	RB	O	24	advmod
26	starting	start	VBG	O	24	xcomp
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	feel	feel	VB	O	26	xcomp
29	privileged	privileged	JJ	O	28	dobj
30	,	,	,	O	28	punct
31	just	just	RB	O	38	advmod
32	because	because	IN	O	38	mark
33	they	they	PRP	O	38	nsubj
34	are	be	VBP	O	38	cop
35	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	38	nmod:poss
36	's	's	POS	O	35	case
37	best	best	JJS	O	38	amod
38	friends	friend	NNS	O	28	advcl
39	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	An	a	DT	O	2	det
2	example	example	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	it	it	PRP	O	2	nmod
5	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	when	when	WRB	O	8	advmod
7	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	convince	convince	VB	O	5	advcl
9	professor	professor	NN	O	10	compound
10	McGonagall	McGonagall	NNP	PERSON	8	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	allow	allow	VB	O	8	xcomp
13	her	she	PRP	O	12	dobj
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	use	use	VB	O	12	xcomp
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	``	``	``	O	19	punct
18	time	time	NN	O	19	compound
19	turner	turner	NN	O	15	dobj
20	''	''	''	O	19	punct
21	when	when	WRB	O	24	advmod
22	it	it	PRP	O	24	nsubj
23	was	be	VBD	O	24	cop
24	something	something	NN	O	19	acl:relcl
25	that	that	IN	O	29	mark
26	no	no	DT	O	27	neg
27	student	student	NN	O	29	nsubj
28	could	could	MD	O	29	aux
29	use	use	VB	O	24	ccomp
30	,	,	,	O	34	punct
31	however	however	RB	O	34	advmod
32	professor	professor	NN	O	33	compound
33	McGonagall	McGonagall	NNP	PERSON	34	nsubj
34	did	do	VBD	O	29	parataxis
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	impossible	impossible	JJ	O	34	dep
37	to	to	TO	O	38	mark
38	help	help	VB	O	34	xcomp
39	her	she	PRP	O	38	dobj
40	,	,	,	O	34	punct
41	just	just	RB	O	48	advmod
42	because	because	IN	O	48	mark
43	she	she	PRP	O	48	nsubj
44	is	be	VBZ	O	48	cop
45	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	48	nmod:poss
46	's	's	POS	O	45	case
47	best	best	JJS	O	48	amod
48	friend	friend	NN	O	29	advcl
49	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	On	on	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
4	hand	hand	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	9	appos
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	PERSON	11	conj
14	,	,	,	O	9	punct
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	unprotected	unprotected	JJ	O	9	appos
17	,	,	,	O	9	punct
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	non-favorites	non-favorite	NNS	O	9	appos
20	,	,	,	O	9	punct
21	like	like	IN	O	23	mark
22	I	I	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	stated	state	VBD	O	9	dep
24	before	before	RB	O	28	advmod
25	is	be	VBZ	O	28	cop
26	one	one	CD	NUMBER	28	advmod
27	of	of	IN	O	26	case
28	the	the	DT	O	23	ccomp
29	most	most	RBS	O	28	advmod
30	``	``	``	O	31	punct
31	respected	respect	VBN	O	28	xcomp
32	''	''	''	O	31	punct
33	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
34	feared	fear	VBD	O	23	conj
35	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	34	dobj
36	at	at	IN	O	37	case
37	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	34	nmod
38	but	but	CC	O	7	cc
39	for	for	IN	O	40	case
40	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	49	nmod
41	,	,	,	O	40	punct
42	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	40	conj
43	and	and	CC	O	40	cc
44	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	40	conj
45	,	,	,	O	49	punct
46	he	he	PRP	O	49	nsubj
47	is	be	VBZ	O	49	cop
48	just	just	RB	O	49	advmod
49	one	one	CD	NUMBER	7	conj
50	of	of	IN	O	52	case
51	a	a	DT	O	52	advmod
52	million	million	CD	NUMBER	49	nmod
53	,	,	,	NUMBER	52	punct
54	one	one	CD	NUMBER	52	appos
55	among	among	IN	O	57	case
56	the	the	DT	O	57	det
57	others	other	NNS	O	54	nmod
58	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
59	what	what	WP	O	61	dobj
60	he	he	PRP	O	61	nsubj
61	says	say	VBZ	O	68	csubj
62	or	or	CC	O	61	cc
63	instruct	instruct	VB	O	61	conj
64	them	they	PRP	O	63	dobj
65	to	to	TO	O	66	mark
66	do	do	VB	O	63	xcomp
67	is	be	VBZ	O	68	cop
68	something	something	NN	O	7	conj
69	they	they	PRP	O	72	nsubj
70	do	do	VBP	O	72	aux
71	n't	not	RB	O	72	neg
72	take	take	VB	O	68	acl:relcl
73	in	in	RP	O	72	compound:prt
74	consideration	consideration	NN	O	72	dobj
75	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	4	neg
2	even	even	RB	O	4	advmod
3	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	listens	listen	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	8	case
6	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	words	word	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
3	since	since	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	beginning	beginning	NN	O	6	nmod
6	did	do	VBD	O	1	acl:relcl
7	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
8	trust	trust	NN	O	9	compound
9	Lupin	lupin	NN	O	6	dobj
10	-	-	:	O	1	punct
11	``	``	``	O	14	punct
12	I	I	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	've	have	VBP	O	14	aux
14	told	tell	VBN	O	1	parataxis
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	14	dobj
17	again	again	RB	O	14	advmod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	again	again	RB	O	17	conj
20	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
21	you	you	PRP	O	23	nsubj
22	're	be	VBP	O	23	aux
23	helping	help	VBG	O	14	ccomp
24	your	you	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
25	old	old	JJ	O	26	amod
26	friend	friend	NN	O	23	dobj
27	Black	black	JJ	PERSON	26	amod
28	into	into	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	castle	castle	NN	O	23	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	30	punct
32	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	O	30	appos
33	,	,	,	O	30	punct
34	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
35	here	here	RB	O	38	advmod
36	's	be	VBZ	O	38	cop
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	proof	proof	NN	O	14	conj
39	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	-	-	:	O	41	punct
2	``	``	``	O	41	punct
3	thinking	think	VBG	O	41	dep
4	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
5	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
6	will	will	MD	O	8	aux
7	probably	probably	RB	O	8	advmod
8	listen	listen	VB	O	3	ccomp
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	words	word	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	8	punct
13	but	but	CC	O	8	cc
14	once	once	RB	DATE	17	advmod
15	again	again	RB	O	17	advmod
16	this	this	DT	O	17	det
17	show	show	NN	O	8	conj
18	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
19	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	20	nsubj
20	does	do	VBZ	O	17	ccomp
21	n't	not	RB	O	20	neg
22	trust	trust	NN	O	20	dobj
23	or	or	CC	O	8	cc
24	listen	listen	VB	O	8	conj
25	to	to	TO	O	28	case
26	his	he	PRP$	O	28	nmod:poss
27	own	own	JJ	O	28	amod
28	staff	staff	NN	O	24	nmod
29	or	or	CC	O	8	cc
30	does	do	VBZ	O	32	aux
31	n't	not	RB	O	32	neg
32	believe	believe	VB	O	8	conj
33	at	at	IN	O	35	case
34	all	all	DT	O	35	det
35	everything	everything	NN	O	32	nmod
36	they	they	PRP	O	37	nsubj
37	have	have	VBP	O	35	acl:relcl
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	say	say	VB	O	37	xcomp
40	,	,	,	O	41	punct
41	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
42	like	like	IN	O	51	mark
43	if	if	IN	O	51	mark
44	what	what	WP	O	46	dobj
45	they	they	PRP	O	46	nsubj
46	think	think	VBP	O	51	csubj
47	or	or	CC	O	46	cc
48	say	say	VBP	O	46	conj
49	do	do	VBP	O	51	aux
50	not	not	RB	O	51	neg
51	count	count	VB	O	41	advcl
52	at	at	IN	O	53	case
53	all	all	DT	O	51	nmod
54	,	,	,	O	51	punct
55	but	but	CC	O	51	cc
56	if	if	IN	O	62	mark
57	instead	instead	RB	O	59	case
58	of	of	IN	O	57	mwe
59	Snape	Snape	NNP	LOCATION	62	nmod
60	,	,	,	O	62	punct
61	were	be	VBD	O	62	cop
62	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	80	advcl
63	,	,	,	O	62	punct
64	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	62	conj
65	or	or	CC	O	62	cc
66	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	62	conj
67	the	the	DT	O	68	det
68	one	one	CD	NUMBER	62	nmod
69	from	from	IN	O	68	mark
70	whom	whom	WP	O	72	dobj
71	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	72	nsubj
72	heard	hear	VBD	O	68	dep
73	about	about	IN	O	74	case
74	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	O	72	nmod
75	the	the	DT	O	76	det
76	situation	situation	NN	O	80	nsubj
77	would	would	MD	O	80	aux
78	have	have	VB	O	80	aux
79	been	be	VBN	O	80	cop
80	different	different	JJ	O	51	conj
81	.	.	.	O	41	punct

1	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
3	have	have	VB	O	5	aux
4	either	either	CC	O	5	advmod
5	done	do	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	something	something	NN	O	5	dobj
7	or	or	CC	O	5	cc
8	tell	tell	VB	O	5	conj
9	them	they	PRP	O	8	iobj
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	reason	reason	NN	O	8	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	16	mark
13	why	why	WRB	O	16	advmod
14	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	O	16	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
16	trustable	trustable	JJ	O	11	acl
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	4	advmod
2	that	that	DT	O	4	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
4	not	not	RB	O	0	ROOT
5	what	what	WP	O	6	nsubj
6	happened	happen	VBD	O	4	ccomp
7	because	because	IN	O	15	mark
8	instead	instead	RB	O	13	advmod
9	of	of	IN	O	13	case
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	student	student	NN	O	13	nmod:poss
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	word	word	NN	O	15	advcl
14	it	it	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	was	be	VBD	O	6	advcl
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	teacher	teacher	NN	O	15	xcomp
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Most	most	JJS	O	2	amod
2	readers	reader	NNS	O	5	nsubj
3	do	do	VBP	O	5	aux
4	n't	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	notice	notice	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	how	how	WRB	O	7	advmod
7	students	student	NNS	O	17	dobj
8	at	at	IN	O	9	case
9	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
10	most	most	JJS	O	17	nsubjpass
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	time	time	NN	O	10	nmod
14	do	do	VBP	O	17	aux
15	n't	not	RB	O	17	neg
16	get	get	VB	O	17	auxpass
17	punished	punish	VBN	O	5	dep
18	when	when	WRB	O	20	advmod
19	they	they	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	do	do	VBP	O	17	advcl
21	something	something	NN	O	20	dobj
22	they	they	PRP	O	26	nsubjpass
23	should	should	MD	O	26	aux
24	clearly	clearly	RB	O	26	advmod
25	be	be	VB	O	26	auxpass
26	punished	punish	VBN	O	21	acl:relcl
27	from	from	IN	O	26	nmod
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	break	break	VB	O	20	parataxis
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	rules	rule	NNS	O	29	dobj
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
33	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
34	how	how	WRB	O	36	advmod
35	they	they	PRP	O	36	nsubj
36	influence	influence	VBP	O	17	conj
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	36	dobj
39	,	,	,	O	38	punct
40	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	38	appos
41	,	,	,	O	38	punct
42	most	most	JJS	O	38	appos
43	of	of	IN	O	45	case
44	the	the	DT	O	45	det
45	time	time	NN	O	42	nmod
46	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	On	on	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
4	hand	hand	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	7	punct
11	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
12	does	do	VBZ	O	14	aux
13	n't	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	matter	matter	VB	O	7	conj
15	how	how	WRB	O	18	advmod
16	right	right	JJ	O	15	dep
17	they	they	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	are	be	VBP	O	14	ccomp
19	,	,	,	O	14	punct
20	or	or	CC	O	14	cc
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	proofs	proof	NNS	O	14	conj
23	they	they	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	have	have	VBP	O	22	acl:relcl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	accuse	accuse	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	someone	someone	NN	O	26	dobj
28	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	5	nsubjpass
2	definitely	definitely	RB	O	5	advmod
3	are	be	VBP	O	5	auxpass
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	taken	take	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	as	as	IN	O	7	case
7	serious	serious	JJ	O	5	advcl
8	as	as	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	students	student	NNS	O	5	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
12	that	that	DT	O	14	nsubj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
14	something	something	NN	O	5	conj
15	unusual	unusual	JJ	O	14	amod
16	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	no	no	DT	O	5	neg
4	such	such	JJ	O	5	amod
5	school	school	NN	O	2	nsubj
6	like	like	IN	O	7	case
7	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	world	world	NN	O	7	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	school	school	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	in	in	IN	O	6	mark
4	where	where	WRB	O	6	advmod
5	students	student	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	raise	raise	VBP	O	2	acl
7	their	they	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	voices	voice	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	6	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	respecting	respect	VBG	O	11	conj
15	them	they	PRP	O	14	dobj
16	,	,	,	O	6	punct
17	without	without	IN	O	19	mark
18	being	be	VBG	O	19	auxpass
19	punished	punish	VBN	O	6	advcl
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	school	school	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	in	in	IN	O	6	mark
4	where	where	WRB	O	6	advmod
5	students	student	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	hit	hit	VBP	O	2	acl
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	this	this	DT	O	10	det
10	case	case	NN	O	6	nmod
11	with	with	IN	O	13	case
12	their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	wands	wand	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	6	punct
15	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	6	dobj
16	without	without	IN	O	18	mark
17	being	be	VBG	O	18	auxpass
18	punished	punish	VBN	O	15	acl
19	either	either	RB	O	18	advmod
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	school	school	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	in	in	IN	O	8	mark
4	where	where	WRB	O	8	advmod
5	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	8	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	ones	one	NNS	O	2	acl
9	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
10	control	control	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
11	what	what	WP	O	13	dobj
12	they	they	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	say	say	VBP	O	10	ccomp
14	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
15	do	do	VBP	O	13	conj
16	to	to	TO	O	17	case
17	students	student	NNS	O	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	3	aux
3	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	by	by	IN	O	5	mark
5	looking	look	VBG	O	3	advcl
6	at	at	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	passage	passage	NN	O	5	nmod
9	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	students	student	NNS	O	20	nsubj
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
13	young	young	JJ	O	11	dep
14	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
15	at	at	IN	O	16	case
16	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	nmod
17	are	be	VBP	O	20	cop
18	above	above	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	5	ccomp
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	22	punct
22	adults	adult	NNS	O	20	appos
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	22	punct
24	,	,	,	O	3	punct
25	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
26	that	that	DT	O	29	nsubj
27	is	be	VBZ	O	29	cop
28	something	something	NN	O	29	nmod:npmod
29	unusual	unusual	JJ	O	3	conj
30	that	that	IN	O	35	mark
31	most	most	JJS	O	32	amod
32	readers	reader	NNS	O	35	nsubj
33	do	do	VBP	O	35	aux
34	n't	not	RB	O	35	neg
35	see	see	VB	O	29	ccomp
36	,	,	,	O	3	punct
37	this	this	DT	O	39	nsubj
38	is	be	VBZ	O	39	cop
39	important	important	JJ	O	3	conj
40	because	because	IN	O	42	mark
41	it	it	PRP	O	42	nsubj
42	explain	explain	VB	O	39	advcl
43	the	the	DT	O	44	det
44	decisions	decision	NNS	O	42	dobj
45	and	and	CC	O	44	cc
46	actions	action	NNS	O	44	conj
47	of	of	IN	O	48	case
48	most	most	JJS	O	44	nmod
49	of	of	IN	O	51	case
50	the	the	DT	O	51	det
51	students	student	NNS	O	48	nmod
52	at	at	IN	O	53	case
53	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	51	nmod
54	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
55	most	most	RBS	O	56	advmod
56	importantly	importantly	RB	O	58	advmod
57	it	it	PRP	O	58	nsubj
58	explains	explain	VBZ	O	3	conj
59	why	why	WRB	O	66	advmod
60	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	66	nsubj
61	,	,	,	O	60	punct
62	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	60	conj
63	and	and	CC	O	60	cc
64	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	60	conj
65	``	``	``	O	66	punct
66	keep	keep	VB	O	58	advcl
67	getting	get	VBG	O	66	xcomp
68	into	into	IN	O	69	case
69	trouble	trouble	NN	O	67	nmod
70	''	''	''	O	58	punct
71	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	All	all	DT	O	10	nsubj
2	because	because	IN	O	4	mark
3	they	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	know	know	VBP	O	1	dep
5	that	that	IN	O	9	mark
6	they	they	PRP	O	9	nsubj
7	will	will	MD	O	9	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	get	get	VB	O	4	ccomp
10	punished	punish	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	because	because	IN	O	14	mark
12	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubjpass
13	are	be	VBP	O	14	auxpass
14	overprotected	overprotect	VBN	O	10	advcl
15	by	by	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	14	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	17	appos
20	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	something	something	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	WDT	O	8	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	8	aux
7	just	just	RB	O	8	advmod
8	starting	start	VBG	O	4	acl:relcl
9	at	at	IN	O	10	case
10	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	10	advmod
2	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
3	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
6	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
7	Sirius	Sirius	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	conj
8	were	be	VBD	O	10	cop
9	at	at	IN	O	10	case
10	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	advcl
11	,	,	,	O	14	punct
12	students	student	NNS	O	14	nsubj
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	cop
14	privileged	privileged	JJ	O	0	ROOT
15	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
16	some	some	DT	O	18	det
17	always	always	RB	O	18	advmod
18	more	more	JJR	O	14	dep
19	than	than	IN	O	20	case
20	others	other	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
22	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	3	case
2	example	example	NN	O	3	compound
3	Lupin	lupin	NN	O	8	nmod
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	Sirius	Sirius	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	conj
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	almost	almost	RB	O	8	advmod
8	killed	kill	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	8	dobj
10	when	when	WRB	O	14	advmod
11	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	all	all	DT	O	14	advmod
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	cop
14	students	student	NNS	O	28	advcl
15	at	at	IN	O	16	case
16	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	28	punct
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	two	two	CD	NUMBER	28	nsubjpass
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	including	include	VBG	O	24	case
22	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	24	nmod:poss
23	's	's	POS	O	22	case
24	dad	dad	NN	O	19	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	19	punct
26	were	be	VBD	O	28	auxpass
27	not	not	RB	O	28	neg
28	punished	punish	VBN	O	9	acl:relcl
29	for	for	IN	O	32	mark
30	what	what	WP	O	32	dobj
31	they	they	PRP	O	32	nsubj
32	did	do	VBD	O	28	advcl
33	instead	instead	RB	O	32	advmod
34	they	they	PRP	O	36	nsubjpass
35	were	be	VBD	O	36	auxpass
36	forgiven	forgive	VBN	O	32	ccomp
37	for	for	IN	O	39	case
38	their	they	PRP$	O	39	nmod:poss
39	actions	action	NNS	O	36	nmod
40	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	history	history	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	would	would	MD	O	6	aux
4	have	have	VB	O	6	aux
5	been	be	VBN	O	6	cop
6	different	different	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	if	if	IN	O	14	mark
8	the	the	DT	O	11	det
9	word	word	NN	O	11	compound
10	``	``	``	O	11	punct
11	expelliarmus	expelliarmus	NN	O	14	nsubj
12	''	''	''	O	11	punct
13	had	have	VBD	O	14	aux
14	gotten	get	VBN	O	6	advcl
15	out	out	IN	O	14	compound:prt
16	of	of	IN	O	19	case
17	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	mouth	mouth	NN	O	14	nmod
20	toward	toward	IN	O	21	case
21	Harry	Harry	NNP	O	19	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	21	conj
24	or	or	CC	O	21	cc
25	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	21	conj
26	instead	instead	RB	O	14	advmod
27	of	of	IN	O	29	mark
28	them	they	PRP	O	29	nsubj
29	hurting	hurt	VBG	O	14	advcl
30	him	he	PRP	O	29	dobj
31	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	definitely	definitely	RB	O	5	advmod
3	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
4	have	have	VB	O	5	aux
5	been	be	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	kick	kick	NN	O	5	ccomp
7	out	out	IN	O	6	advmod
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	school	school	NN	O	7	nmod
11	even	even	RB	O	15	advmod
12	though	though	IN	O	15	mark
13	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	had	have	VBD	O	15	aux
15	told	tell	VBN	O	6	advcl
16	them	they	PRP	O	15	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	get	get	VB	O	15	xcomp
19	out	out	IN	O	18	compound:prt
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	way	way	NN	O	18	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	6	cc
2	it	it	PRP	O	6	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
4	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	case	case	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
6	,	,	,	O	1	punct
7	were	be	VBD	O	9	cop
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	ones	one	NNS	O	0	ROOT
10	who	who	WP	O	11	nsubj
11	used	use	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	wands	wand	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	against	against	IN	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	teacher	teacher	NN	O	11	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	who	who	WP	O	20	nsubjpass
19	is	be	VBZ	O	20	auxpass
20	supposed	suppose	VBN	O	16	acl:relcl
21	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
22	be	be	VB	O	23	cop
23	superior	superior	JJ	O	20	xcomp
24	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
25	respected	respect	VBN	O	20	conj
26	by	by	IN	O	27	case
27	them	they	PRP	O	25	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	19	cc
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	three	three	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
4	friends	friend	NNS	O	19	nsubj
5	,	,	,	O	19	punct
6	knowing	know	VBG	O	19	advcl
7	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
8	they	they	PRP	O	10	nsubj
9	can	can	MD	O	10	aux
10	do	do	VB	O	6	ccomp
11	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	13	dobj
12	they	they	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	want	want	VBP	O	10	ccomp
14	without	without	IN	O	15	case
15	consequences	consequence	NNS	O	13	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	19	punct
17	did	do	VBD	O	19	aux
18	n't	not	RB	O	19	neg
19	care	care	VB	O	0	ROOT
20	about	about	IN	O	23	mark
21	what	what	WP	O	23	dobj
22	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	23	nsubj
23	had	have	VBD	O	19	advcl
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	say	say	VB	O	23	xcomp
26	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	4	aux
3	n't	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	listen	listen	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	case
6	anybody	anybody	NN	O	4	nmod
7	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
8	themselves	themselves	PRP	O	13	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	that	that	DT	O	8	conj
11	's	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
12	something	something	NN	O	13	nmod:npmod
13	unusual	unusual	JJ	O	4	conj
14	when	when	WRB	O	15	advmod
15	talking	talk	VBG	O	13	advcl
16	about	about	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	relation	relation	NN	O	15	nmod
19	between	between	IN	O	20	case
20	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	students	student	NNS	O	20	conj
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	children	child	NNS	O	20	dep
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	adults	adult	NNS	O	24	conj
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
28	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	see	see	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	2	dobj
4	as	as	IN	O	9	case
5	our	we	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
6	``	``	``	O	9	punct
7	parents	parent	NNS	O	9	compound
8	''	''	''	O	9	punct
9	adults	adult	NNS	O	3	nmod
10	from	from	IN	O	13	mark
11	who	who	WP	O	13	dobj
12	we	we	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	take	take	VBP	O	2	advcl
14	advices	advice	NNS	O	13	dobj
15	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
16	listen	listen	VB	O	13	conj
17	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
18	what	what	WP	O	20	dobj
19	they	they	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	have	have	VBP	O	16	advcl
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	say	say	VB	O	20	xcomp
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	People	people	NNS	O	19	nsubj
2	from	from	IN	O	5	mark
3	whom	whom	WP	O	5	dobj
4	we	we	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	learn	learn	VBP	O	1	acl
6	about	about	IN	O	7	case
7	life	life	NN	O	5	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	case	case	NN	O	7	conj
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	wizards	wizard	NNS	O	11	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	13	appos
16	are	be	VBP	O	19	cop
17	their	they	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	``	``	``	O	19	punct
19	masters	master	NNS	O	0	ROOT
20	''	''	''	O	19	punct
21	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	5	advmod
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	case	case	NN	O	20	ccomp
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	8	conj
11	,	,	,	O	20	punct
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	only	only	JJ	O	14	amod
14	teacher	teacher	NN	O	20	nsubj
15	they	they	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	respect	respect	VBP	O	14	acl:relcl
17	so	so	RB	O	18	advmod
18	far	far	RB	O	16	advmod
19	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
20	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
21	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	3	case
2	close	close	JJ	O	3	amod
3	reading	reading	NN	O	22	nmod
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	passage	passage	NN	O	3	dep
6	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	7	punct
7	Chapter	chapter	NN	O	5	appos
8	19	19	CD	NUMBER	7	nummod
9	,	,	,	O	7	punct
10	358-361	358-361	CD	NUMBER	7	dep
11	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	7	punct
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Potter	Potter	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	Prisoner	prisoner	NN	MISC	3	conj
18	of	of	IN	MISC	19	case
19	Azkaban	Azkaban	NNP	MISC	17	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	22	punct
21	we	we	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	notice	notice	VBP	O	0	ROOT
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	relation	relation	NN	O	22	dobj
25	between	between	IN	O	28	case
26	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	28	nmod:poss
27	'	'	POS	O	26	case
28	students	student	NNS	O	24	nmod
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	28	conj
31	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	No	no	DT	O	5	neg
2	a	a	DT	O	5	det
3	good	good	JJ	O	5	amod
4	teacher-student	teacher-student	JJ	O	5	amod
5	relation	relation	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
6	because	because	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	are	be	VBP	O	11	auxpass
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	trusted	trust	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
13	respected	respect	VBN	O	11	conj
14	by	by	IN	O	19	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	students	student	NNS	O	19	nmod:npmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	vice	vice	NN	O	16	conj
19	versa	versa	RB	O	11	advcl
20	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Keep	keep	VB	O	0	ROOT
3	Quiet	Quiet	NNP	O	2	dobj
4	,	,	,	O	2	punct
5	you	you	PRP	O	7	dep
6	stupid	stupid	JJ	O	7	amod
7	girl	girl	NN	O	2	dobj
8	''	''	''	O	2	punct
9	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
10	pg	pg	NN	O	2	dep
11	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	360	360	CD	NUMBER	6	dep
2	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	6	punct
3	are	be	VBP	O	6	cop
4	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	kind	kind	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	things	thing	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	teacher	teacher	NN	O	12	nsubj
11	will	will	MD	O	12	aux
12	tell	tell	VB	O	8	acl:relcl
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	student	student	NN	O	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Just	just	RB	O	3	advmod
2	like	like	IN	O	3	case
3	words	word	NNS	O	0	ROOT
4	such	such	JJ	O	12	case
5	as	as	IN	O	4	mwe
6	``	``	``	O	9	punct
7	you	you	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	're	be	VBP	O	9	cop
9	pathetic	pathetic	JJ	O	12	dep
10	''	''	''	O	9	punct
11	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	12	punct
12	pg	pg	NN	O	3	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	360	360	CD	NUMBER	5	dep
2	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	5	punct
3	should	should	MD	O	5	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	5	auxpass
5	told	tell	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	8	case
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	teacher	teacher	NN	O	5	nmod
9	.	.	.	O	5	punct

