1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	addressed	address	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	nation	nation	NN	O	3	dobj
6	on	on	IN	O	7	case
7	September	September	NNP	DATE	3	nmod
8	10	10	CD	DATE	7	nummod
9	,	,	,	DATE	7	punct
10	2013	2013	CD	DATE	7	nummod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	discuss	discuss	VB	O	3	advcl
13	an	a	DT	O	14	det
14	attack	attack	NN	O	12	dobj
15	on	on	IN	O	16	case
16	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	for	for	IN	O	19	case
18	its	its	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	use	use	NN	O	12	nmod
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	chemical	chemical	NN	O	22	compound
22	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	19	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	situation	situation	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	2	nmod
5	has	have	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	been	be	VBN	O	7	aux
7	brewing	brew	VBG	O	0	ROOT
8	for	for	IN	O	10	case
9	several	several	JJ	DURATION	10	amod
10	years	year	NNS	DURATION	7	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
12	now	now	RB	DATE	14	advmod
13	has	have	VBZ	O	14	aux
14	come	come	VBN	O	7	conj
15	to	to	TO	O	17	case
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	crisis	crisis	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	goal	goal	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	36	ccomp
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	persuade	persuade	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	American	american	JJ	MISC	10	amod
10	public	public	NN	O	7	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	agree	agree	VB	O	7	xcomp
13	with	with	IN	O	15	case
14	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	decision	decision	NN	O	12	nmod
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	act	act	VB	O	15	acl
18	on	on	IN	O	21	case
19	this	this	DT	O	21	det
20	critical	critical	JJ	O	21	amod
21	situation	situation	NN	O	17	nmod
22	through	through	IN	O	25	case
23	his	he	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	strategic	strategic	JJ	O	25	amod
25	layout	layout	NN	O	17	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	27	case
27	information	information	NN	O	25	nmod
28	;	;	:	O	5	punct
29	He	he	PRP	O	30	nsubj
30	explains	explain	VBZ	O	5	parataxis
31	why	why	WRB	O	34	advmod
32	we	we	PRP	O	34	nsubj
33	must	must	MD	O	34	aux
34	act	act	VB	O	30	advcl
35	,	,	,	O	36	punct
36	lists	list	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
37	what	what	WP	O	40	dobj
38	his	he	PRP$	O	39	nmod:poss
39	possibilities	possibility	NNS	O	40	nsubj
40	are	be	VBP	O	36	ccomp
41	,	,	,	O	40	punct
42	and	and	CC	O	40	cc
43	refutes	refute	VBZ	O	40	conj
44	arguments	argument	NNS	O	36	nsubj
45	made	make	VBN	O	44	acl
46	against	against	IN	O	47	mark
47	acting	act	VBG	O	45	advcl
48	.	.	.	O	36	punct

1	Through	through	IN	O	3	case
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	structure	structure	NN	O	5	nmod
4	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	tries	try	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	persuade	persuade	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	Democrats	Democrats	NNPS	MISC	7	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	Republicans	Republicans	NNPS	MISC	8	conj
11	,	,	,	O	8	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
13	international	international	JJ	O	14	amod
14	audiences	audience	NNS	O	8	conj
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	4	mark
2	President	President	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	explains	explain	VBZ	O	18	advcl
5	why	why	WRB	O	11	advmod
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
8	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	11	nsubjpass
9	must	must	MD	O	11	aux
10	be	be	VB	O	11	auxpass
11	involved	involve	VBN	O	4	advcl
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	this	this	DT	O	14	det
14	situation	situation	NN	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	18	punct
16	he	he	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	strategically	strategically	RB	O	18	advmod
18	places	place	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
19	sentences	sentence	NNS	O	18	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	convince	convince	VB	O	18	xcomp
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	American	american	JJ	MISC	24	amod
24	public	public	NN	O	21	dobj
25	that	that	IN	O	28	mark
26	we	we	PRP	O	28	nsubj
27	must	must	MD	O	28	aux
28	act	act	VB	O	21	ccomp
29	in	in	IN	O	30	case
30	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	28	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	3	advmod
3	explains	explain	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	what	what	WP	O	6	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	happened	happen	VBN	O	17	dep
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
10	uses	use	VBZ	O	8	acl
11	heart	heart	NN	O	10	dobj
12	rendering	render	VBG	O	11	acl
13	imagery	imagery	NN	O	12	dobj
14	:	:	:	O	8	punct
15	''	''	''	O	8	punct
16	...	...	:	O	17	punct
17	men	man	NNS	O	3	dobj
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	woman	woman	NN	O	17	conj
20	,	,	,	O	17	punct
21	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
22	children	child	NNS	O	17	conj
23	lying	lie	VBG	O	22	dep
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	rows	row	NNS	O	23	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	killed	kill	VBN	O	25	acl
28	by	by	IN	O	30	case
29	poison	poison	NN	O	30	compound
30	gas	gas	NN	O	27	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	30	punct
32	others	other	NNS	O	30	appos
33	foaming	foam	VBG	O	32	amod
34	at	at	IN	O	36	case
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	mouth	mouth	NN	O	32	nmod
37	,	,	,	O	23	punct
38	gasping	gasp	VBG	O	23	dep
39	for	for	IN	O	40	case
40	breath	breath	NN	O	38	nmod
41	,	,	,	O	40	punct
42	a	a	DT	O	43	det
43	father	father	NN	O	40	appos
44	clutching	clutch	VBG	O	43	acl
45	his	he	PRP$	O	47	nmod:poss
46	dead	dead	JJ	O	47	amod
47	children	child	NNS	O	44	dobj
48	,	,	,	O	23	punct
49	imploring	implore	VBG	O	23	dep
50	them	they	PRP	O	49	dobj
51	to	to	TO	O	52	mark
52	get	get	VB	O	49	xcomp
53	up	up	RB	O	52	advmod
54	and	and	CC	O	52	cc
55	walk	walk	VB	O	52	conj
56	.	.	.	O	3	punct
57	''	''	''	O	3	punct

1	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	imagery	imagery	NN	O	2	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	6	case
6	tug	tug	NN	O	2	nmod
7	at	at	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	emotions	emotion	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	audience	audience	NN	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	especially	especially	RB	O	16	advmod
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	emotions	emotion	NNS	O	12	appos
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	mothers	mother	NNS	O	16	nmod
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	fathers	father	NNS	O	18	conj
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	emotion	emotion	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	implores	implore	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	audience	audience	NN	O	3	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	feel	feel	VB	O	5	acl
8	sympathy	sympathy	NN	O	7	dobj
9	for	for	IN	O	10	case
10	those	those	DT	O	7	nmod
11	who	who	WP	O	13	nsubjpass
12	were	be	VBD	O	13	auxpass
13	affected	affect	VBN	O	10	acl:relcl
14	by	by	IN	O	16	case
15	this	this	DT	O	16	det
16	attack	attack	NN	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	13	punct
18	thus	thus	RB	O	19	advmod
19	giving	give	VBG	O	13	xcomp
20	them	they	PRP	O	19	iobj
21	a	a	DT	O	22	det
22	motive	motive	NN	O	19	dobj
23	for	for	IN	O	24	case
24	action	action	NN	O	22	nmod
25	against	against	IN	O	28	case
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	28	compound
28	regime	regime	NN	O	24	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	3	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	7	case
6	his	he	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	advantage	advantage	NN	O	3	nmod
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	the	the	DT	O	7	nmod
10	beginning	begin	VBG	O	9	acl
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	grab	grab	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	attention	attention	NN	O	12	dobj
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	audience	audience	NN	O	14	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
19	keep	keep	VB	O	12	conj
20	them	they	PRP	O	19	dobj
21	in	in	IN	O	24	case
22	an	a	DT	O	24	det
23	anticipatory	anticipatory	JJ	O	24	amod
24	state	state	NN	O	19	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	mind	mind	NN	O	24	nmod
27	for	for	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	rest	rest	NN	O	19	nmod
30	of	of	IN	O	32	case
31	his	he	PRP$	O	32	nmod:poss
32	speech	speech	NN	O	29	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	starts	start	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	with	with	IN	O	4	case
4	emotion	emotion	NN	O	2	nmod
5	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
6	only	only	RB	O	8	advmod
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	appeal	appeal	VB	O	2	ccomp
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	audience	audience	NN	O	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	8	punct
13	but	but	CC	O	8	cc
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	prepare	prepare	VB	O	8	conj
16	them	they	PRP	O	15	dobj
17	for	for	IN	O	20	case
18	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	20	nmod:poss
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	plan	plan	NN	O	15	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	action	action	NN	O	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	later	later	RB	O	3	advmod
3	states	state	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	fact	fact	NN	O	3	dobj
6	for	for	IN	O	7	case
7	those	those	DT	O	5	nmod
8	who	who	WP	O	11	nsubj
9	are	be	VBP	O	11	cop
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	sympathetic	sympathetic	JJ	O	7	acl:relcl
12	towards	towards	IN	O	15	case
13	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	15	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	O	13	case
15	people	people	NNS	O	11	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	3	punct
17	``	``	``	O	3	punct
18	And	and	CC	O	27	cc
19	in	in	IN	O	20	case
20	1997	1997	CD	DATE	27	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	27	punct
22	the	the	DT	O	25	det
23	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	25	compound
24	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	25	compound
25	Senate	Senate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	nsubj
26	overwhelmingly	overwhelmingly	RB	O	27	advmod
27	approved	approve	VBD	O	3	parataxis
28	an	a	DT	O	30	det
29	international	international	JJ	O	30	amod
30	agreement	agreement	NN	O	27	dobj
31	prohibiting	prohibit	VBG	O	27	xcomp
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	use	use	NN	O	31	dobj
34	of	of	IN	O	36	case
35	chemical	chemical	NN	O	36	compound
36	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	33	nmod
37	,	,	,	O	36	punct
38	now	now	RB	DATE	39	advmod
39	joined	join	VBN	O	36	acl
40	by	by	IN	O	42	case
41	189	189	CD	NUMBER	42	nummod
42	governments	government	NNS	O	39	nmod
43	that	that	WDT	O	44	nsubj
44	represent	represent	VBP	O	42	acl:relcl
45	98	98	CD	PERCENT	46	nummod
46	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	44	dobj
47	of	of	IN	O	48	case
48	humanity	humanity	NN	O	46	nmod
49	.	.	.	O	3	punct
50	''	''	''	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	4	det
4	statement	statement	NN	O	2	dobj
5	after	after	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	imagery	imagery	NN	O	2	nmod
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	appeal	appeal	VB	O	7	acl
10	to	to	TO	O	11	case
11	those	those	DT	O	9	nmod
12	who	who	WP	O	13	nsubj
13	think	think	VBP	O	11	acl:relcl
14	logically	logically	RB	O	13	advmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	not	not	RB	O	14	conj
17	emotionally	emotionally	RB	O	13	advmod
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	puts	put	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	4	det
4	statement	statement	NN	O	2	dobj
5	after	after	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	emotional	emotional	JJ	O	8	amod
8	one	one	NN	NUMBER	2	nmod
9	because	because	IN	O	17	mark
10	those	those	DT	O	17	nsubj
11	who	who	WP	O	14	nsubj
12	do	do	VBP	O	14	aux
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	trust	trust	VB	O	10	acl:relcl
15	government	government	NN	O	14	dobj
16	will	will	MD	O	17	aux
17	need	need	VB	O	2	advcl
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	facts	fact	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	agree	agree	VB	O	17	xcomp
22	on	on	IN	O	24	case
23	an	a	DT	O	24	det
24	issue	issue	NN	O	21	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Here	here	RB	O	6	advmod
2	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	only	only	RB	O	6	advmod
6	talking	talk	VBG	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	American	american	JJ	MISC	10	amod
10	public	public	NN	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	6	punct
12	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
13	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	is	be	VBZ	O	15	aux
15	calling	call	VBG	O	6	conj
16	out	out	RP	O	15	compound:prt
17	other	other	JJ	O	18	amod
18	governments	government	NNS	O	15	dobj
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	nations	nation	NNS	O	18	conj
21	that	that	WDT	O	22	nsubj
22	agreed	agree	VBD	O	18	acl:relcl
23	with	with	IN	O	24	mark
24	prohibiting	prohibit	VBG	O	22	advcl
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	use	use	NN	O	24	dobj
27	of	of	IN	O	29	case
28	chemical	chemical	NN	O	29	compound
29	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	26	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	3	case
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	point	point	NN	O	11	nmod
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	speech	speech	NN	O	3	nmod
7	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	11	aux
9	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
10	only	only	RB	O	11	advmod
11	talking	talk	VBG	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	15	compound
15	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	11	nmod
16	;	;	:	O	11	punct
17	he	he	PRP	O	20	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	20	aux
19	also	also	RB	O	20	advmod
20	addressing	address	VBG	O	11	parataxis
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	international	international	JJ	O	23	amod
23	community	community	NN	O	20	dobj
24	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	2	dobj
4	before	before	IN	O	6	mark
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	introduces	introduce	VBZ	O	2	advcl
7	what	what	WP	O	14	dobj
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	10	compound
10	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	12	nsubj
11	is	be	VBZ	O	12	aux
12	going	go	VBG	O	6	ccomp
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	do	do	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	because	because	IN	O	17	mark
16	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	wants	want	VBZ	O	14	advcl
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	other	other	JJ	O	20	amod
20	nations	nation	NNS	O	17	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	know	know	VB	O	17	xcomp
23	what	what	WP	O	22	dobj
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	26	compound
26	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	22	nmod
27	in	in	IN	O	26	case
28	capable	capable	JJ	O	26	dep
29	of	of	IN	O	26	case
30	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
31	use	use	VB	O	22	conj
32	this	this	DT	O	33	det
33	situation	situation	NN	O	31	dobj
34	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
35	be	be	VB	O	37	cop
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	example	example	NN	O	33	acl
38	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	then	then	RB	O	4	advmod
4	announces	announce	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	plans	plan	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	8	mark
8	addressing	address	VBG	O	4	advcl
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	situation	situation	NN	O	8	dobj
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
13	:	:	:	O	10	punct
14	a	a	DT	O	17	det
15	targeted	target	VBN	O	17	amod
16	military	military	JJ	O	17	amod
17	strike	strike	NN	O	10	dep
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	According	accord	VBG	O	3	case
2	to	to	TO	O	1	mwe
3	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	''	''	''	O	3	punct
6	...	...	:	O	7	punct
7	it	it	PRP	O	3	dep
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	dep
9	in	in	IN	O	7	nmod
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	national	national	JJ	O	13	amod
12	security	security	NN	O	13	compound
13	interests	interest	NNS	O	7	dep
14	of	of	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
17	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	13	nmod
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	respond	respond	VB	O	13	dep
20	to	to	TO	O	25	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	23	compound
23	regime	regime	NN	O	25	nmod:poss
24	's	's	POS	O	23	case
25	use	use	NN	O	19	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	28	case
27	chemical	chemical	NN	O	28	compound
28	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	25	nmod
29	through	through	IN	O	33	case
30	a	a	DT	O	33	det
31	targeted	target	VBN	O	33	amod
32	military	military	JJ	O	33	amod
33	strike	strike	NN	O	19	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	19	punct
35	''	''	''	O	19	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	dives	dive	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	right	right	RB	O	2	advmod
4	into	into	IN	O	9	mark
5	what	what	WP	O	9	dobj
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	military	military	NN	O	9	nsubj
8	will	will	MD	O	9	aux
9	do	do	VB	O	3	advcl
10	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	interesting	interesting	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	because	because	IN	O	8	mark
5	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
6	does	do	VBZ	O	8	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	state	state	VB	O	3	advcl
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	peaceful	peaceful	JJ	O	11	amod
11	route	route	NN	O	8	dobj
12	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	8	advmod
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	strategy	strategy	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	auxpass
4	used	use	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	show	show	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	strength	strength	NN	O	6	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
12	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	8	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	severity	severity	NN	O	8	conj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	issue	issue	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Part	part	NN	O	6	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	his	he	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	audience	audience	NN	O	1	nmod
5	will	will	MD	O	6	aux
6	like	like	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	10	compound
10	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	13	nsubj
11	is	be	VBZ	O	13	aux
12	finally	finally	RB	O	13	advmod
13	acting	act	VBG	O	6	ccomp
14	like	like	IN	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	leader	leader	NN	O	13	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
18	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
19	tolerating	tolerate	VBG	O	13	conj
20	this	this	DT	O	21	det
21	behavior	behavior	NN	O	19	dobj
22	,	,	,	O	6	punct
23	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
24	others	other	NNS	O	26	nsubj
25	will	will	MD	O	26	aux
26	disagree	disagree	VB	O	6	conj
27	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	military	military	JJ	O	3	amod
3	families	family	NNS	O	13	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	which	which	WDT	O	7	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	7	cop
7	part	part	NN	O	3	acl:relcl
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	audience	audience	NN	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	3	punct
12	will	will	MD	O	13	aux
13	disagree	disagree	VB	O	0	ROOT
14	with	with	IN	O	15	case
15	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	his	he	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	plan	plan	NN	O	15	conj
19	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	2	case
2	that	that	DT	O	6	nmod
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	mind	mind	NN	O	2	nmod
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	wants	want	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	military	military	JJ	O	9	amod
9	families	family	NNS	O	6	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	focus	focus	VB	O	6	xcomp
12	on	on	IN	O	15	mark
13	what	what	WP	O	15	dobj
14	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	talks	talk	VBZ	O	11	advcl
16	about	about	IN	O	17	case
17	next	next	JJ	O	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	peaceful	peaceful	JJ	O	3	amod
3	route	route	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	aux
5	encouraging	encourage	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	9	compound
9	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	5	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	international	international	JJ	O	13	amod
13	audience	audience	NN	O	9	conj
14	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	describes	describe	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	route	route	NN	O	3	dobj
6	as	as	IN	O	7	mark
7	having	have	VBG	O	3	advcl
8	``	``	``	O	10	punct
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	potential	potential	NN	O	7	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	remove	remove	VB	O	10	acl
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	threat	threat	NN	O	12	dobj
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	chemical	chemical	NN	O	17	compound
17	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	without	without	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	use	use	NN	O	12	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	force	force	NN	O	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	3	punct
24	''	''	''	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	route	route	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	includes	include	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	Russia	Russia	NNP	LOCATION	3	dobj
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	close	close	JJ	O	10	amod
10	ally	ally	NN	O	4	acl:relcl
11	with	with	IN	O	12	case
12	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	3	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	good	good	JJ	O	17	nsubj
17	is	be	VBZ	O	3	conj
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	encourage	encourage	VB	O	17	xcomp
20	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	19	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	give	give	VB	O	19	xcomp
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	chemical	chemical	NN	O	25	compound
25	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	22	iobj
26	to	to	TO	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	UN	UN	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	compound
29	Security	security	NN	ORGANIZATION	25	nmod
30	Council	Council	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	dobj
31	so	so	IN	O	37	mark
32	that	that	IN	O	31	mwe
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	37	nsubjpass
35	will	will	MD	O	37	aux
36	be	be	VB	O	37	auxpass
37	destroyed	destroy	VBN	O	22	advcl
38	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	larger	larger	JJR	O	3	amod
3	part	part	NN	O	9	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	audience	audience	NN	O	3	nmod
7	will	will	MD	O	9	aux
8	likely	likely	RB	O	9	advmod
9	support	support	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	peaceful	peaceful	JJ	O	12	amod
12	route	route	NN	O	9	dobj
13	especially	especially	RB	O	15	advmod
14	military	military	JJ	O	15	amod
15	families	family	NNS	O	9	nmod
16	because	because	IN	O	20	mark
17	these	these	DT	O	18	det
18	families	family	NNS	O	20	nsubjpass
19	are	be	VBP	O	20	auxpass
20	tired	tire	VBN	O	9	advcl
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	23	compound
23	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	9	dep
24	being	be	VBG	O	25	auxpass
25	involved	involve	VBN	O	23	acl
26	in	in	IN	O	27	case
27	war	war	NN	O	25	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Here	here	RB	O	4	advmod
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	aux
4	persuading	persuade	VBG	O	0	ROOT
5	all	all	DT	O	6	det
6	audiences	audience	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
8	he	he	PRP	O	10	nsubj
9	will	will	MD	O	10	aux
10	pursue	pursue	VB	O	4	ccomp
11	all	all	DT	O	13	det
12	peaceful	peaceful	JJ	O	13	amod
13	routes	route	NNS	O	10	dobj
14	until	until	IN	O	18	mark
15	military	military	JJ	O	16	amod
16	action	action	NN	O	18	nsubjpass
17	is	be	VBZ	O	18	auxpass
18	needed	need	VBN	O	10	advcl
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	placed	place	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	peaceful	peaceful	JJ	O	5	amod
5	path	path	NN	O	2	dobj
6	after	after	IN	O	10	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
8	targeted	target	VBN	O	10	amod
9	military	military	JJ	O	10	amod
10	strike	strike	NN	O	2	nmod
11	because	because	IN	O	13	mark
12	that	that	DT	O	13	nsubj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	2	advcl
14	what	what	WP	O	16	dobj
15	he	he	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	wants	want	VBZ	O	13	ccomp
17	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	fellow	fellow	JJ	O	19	amod
19	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	16	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	take	take	VB	O	19	acl
22	away	away	RP	O	21	compound:prt
23	from	from	IN	O	25	case
24	his	he	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	address	address	NN	O	21	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	way	way	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	audience	audience	NN	O	2	dep
5	a	a	DT	O	7	dep
6	can	can	MD	O	7	aux
7	put	put	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	military	military	JJ	O	10	amod
10	strike	strike	NN	O	7	dobj
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	back	back	NN	O	7	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	their	they	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	minds	mind	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
18	know	know	VB	O	7	conj
19	that	that	IN	O	22	mark
20	he	he	PRP	O	22	nsubj
21	is	be	VBZ	O	22	aux
22	searching	search	VBG	O	18	ccomp
23	for	for	IN	O	26	case
24	a	a	DT	O	26	det
25	passive	passive	JJ	O	26	amod
26	solution	solution	NN	O	22	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	4	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	had	have	VBD	O	4	aux
4	spoke	speak	VBN	O	13	advcl
5	about	about	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	peaceful	peaceful	JJ	O	8	amod
8	solution	solution	NN	O	4	nmod
9	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	4	advmod
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	address	address	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
13	lose	lose	VB	O	0	ROOT
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	strength	strength	NN	O	13	dobj
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	cohesion	cohesion	NN	O	15	conj
18	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	intimidation	intimidation	NN	O	3	compound
3	factor	factor	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
5	fade	fade	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubjpass
8	would	would	MD	O	10	aux
9	be	be	VB	O	10	auxpass
10	perceived	perceive	VBN	O	5	conj
11	as	as	IN	O	12	case
12	weak	weak	JJ	O	10	advcl
13	;	;	:	O	5	punct
14	With	with	IN	O	16	case
15	this	this	DT	O	16	det
16	path	path	NN	O	25	nmod
17	placed	place	VBN	O	16	acl
18	after	after	IN	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	military	military	JJ	O	21	amod
21	strike	strike	NN	O	17	nmod
22	he	he	PRP	O	25	nsubj
23	does	do	VBZ	O	25	aux
24	not	not	RB	O	25	neg
25	lose	lose	VB	O	5	parataxis
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	intimidation	intimidation	NN	O	28	compound
28	factor	factor	NN	O	25	dobj
29	,	,	,	O	25	punct
30	but	but	CC	O	25	cc
31	audience	audience	NN	O	33	nsubj
32	will	will	MD	O	33	aux
33	have	have	VB	O	25	conj
34	peace	peace	NN	O	33	dobj
35	knowing	know	VBG	O	34	acl
36	that	that	IN	O	40	mark
37	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	40	nsubj
38	is	be	VBZ	O	40	aux
39	not	not	RB	O	40	neg
40	looking	look	VBG	O	35	ccomp
41	for	for	IN	O	43	case
42	another	another	DT	O	43	det
43	war	war	NN	O	40	nmod
44	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	then	then	RB	O	4	advmod
4	takes	take	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	an	a	DT	O	7	det
6	interesting	interesting	JJ	O	7	amod
7	turn	turn	NN	O	4	dobj
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	speech	speech	NN	O	7	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	3	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	explains	explain	VBZ	O	13	advcl
4	the	the	DT	O	8	det
5	military	military	JJ	O	8	amod
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	diplomatic	diplomatic	JJ	O	5	conj
8	options	option	NNS	O	3	dobj
9	for	for	IN	O	10	case
10	action	action	NN	O	8	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	13	punct
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	answers	answer	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
14	some	some	DT	O	15	det
15	questions	question	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	from	from	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	audience	audience	NN	O	13	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Letters	letter	NNS	O	10	nsubj
2	from	from	IN	O	4	case
3	American	american	JJ	MISC	4	amod
4	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	concerns	concern	NNS	O	4	conj
7	from	from	IN	O	8	case
8	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
9	have	have	VBP	O	10	aux
10	questioned	question	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	the	the	DT	O	14	det
12	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	14	compound
13	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	14	compound
14	involvement	involvement	NN	O	10	dobj
15	in	in	IN	O	16	case
16	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	2	dobj
4	because	because	IN	O	6	mark
5	it	it	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	ensures	ensure	VBZ	O	2	advcl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	audience	audience	NN	O	6	dobj
9	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
10	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	has	have	VBZ	O	12	aux
12	thought	think	VBN	O	6	ccomp
13	about	about	IN	O	15	case
14	this	this	DT	O	15	det
15	situation	situation	NN	O	12	nmod
16	carefully	carefully	RB	O	12	advmod
17	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
18	looked	look	VBD	O	12	conj
19	at	at	IN	O	21	case
20	opposing	oppose	VBG	O	21	amod
21	views	view	NNS	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	directly	directly	RB	O	3	advmod
3	answers	answer	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	questions	question	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	concerned	concerned	JJ	O	8	amod
8	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	display	display	VB	O	3	xcomp
11	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
12	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	has	have	VBZ	O	14	aux
14	read	read	VBN	O	10	ccomp
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	concerns	concern	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	19	case
18	American	american	JJ	MISC	19	amod
19	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	16	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	2	dobj
4	after	after	IN	O	6	mark
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	explains	explain	VBZ	O	2	advcl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	options	option	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	because	because	IN	O	11	mark
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	wants	want	VBZ	O	6	advcl
12	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
13	be	be	VB	O	15	cop
14	more	more	RBR	O	15	advmod
15	personable	personable	JJ	O	11	xcomp
16	to	to	TO	O	18	case
17	his	he	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	audience	audience	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	structure	structure	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	supports	support	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	strength	strength	NN	O	3	dobj
6	that	that	IN	O	9	mark
7	he	he	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	has	have	VBZ	O	9	aux
9	implemented	implement	VBN	O	3	ccomp
10	earlier	earlier	JJR	O	9	advmod
11	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
12	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
13	a	a	DT	O	16	det
14	strategic	strategic	JJ	O	15	amod
15	persuasive	persuasive	JJ	O	16	amod
16	tool	tool	NN	O	9	conj
17	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	starts	start	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	by	by	IN	O	4	mark
4	saying	say	VBG	O	2	advcl
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	``	``	``	O	4	punct
7	Many	many	JJ	O	11	nsubj
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	you	you	PRP	O	7	nmod
10	have	have	VBP	O	11	aux
11	asked	ask	VBN	O	4	ccomp
12	...	...	:	O	2	punct
13	''	''	''	O	2	punct
14	This	this	DT	O	15	nsubj
15	shows	show	VBZ	O	2	parataxis
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	audience	audience	NN	O	15	dobj
18	that	that	WDT	O	22	dobj
19	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
20	really	really	RB	O	22	advmod
21	has	have	VBZ	O	22	aux
22	thought	think	VBN	O	17	acl:relcl
23	about	about	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	American	american	JJ	MISC	26	amod
26	public	public	NN	O	22	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	cares	care	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	about	about	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	DATE	5	det
5	future	future	NN	DATE	2	nmod
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	nation	nation	NN	O	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	but	but	CC	O	2	cc
11	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	does	do	VBZ	O	14	aux
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	want	want	VB	O	2	conj
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
17	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	14	dobj
18	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
19	just	just	RB	O	20	advmod
20	sit	sit	VB	O	14	xcomp
21	back	back	RB	O	20	advmod
22	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
23	watch	watch	VB	O	20	conj
24	as	as	IN	O	28	mark
25	the	the	DT	O	27	det
26	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	27	compound
27	regime	regime	NN	O	28	nsubj
28	gains	gain	VBZ	O	23	advcl
29	momentum	momentum	NN	O	28	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	question	question	NN	O	5	compound
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	answer	answer	NN	O	2	conj
5	section	section	NN	O	10	nsubj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	speech	speech	NN	O	5	nmod
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
10	important	important	JJ	O	0	ROOT
11	to	to	TO	O	13	case
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	audience	audience	NN	O	10	nmod
14	because	because	IN	O	16	mark
15	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	became	become	VBD	O	10	advcl
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	conversation	conversation	NN	O	16	xcomp
19	between	between	IN	O	20	case
20	him	he	PRP	O	18	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	audience	audience	NN	O	20	conj
24	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	3	aux
3	do	do	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	3	dobj
5	because	because	IN	O	8	case
6	of	of	IN	O	5	mwe
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	strength	strength	NN	O	3	nmod
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	beginning	beginning	NN	O	8	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	address	address	NN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	4	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	had	have	VBD	O	4	aux
4	started	start	VBN	O	11	advcl
5	with	with	IN	O	7	case
6	this	this	DT	O	7	det
7	conversation	conversation	NN	O	4	nmod
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	speech	speech	NN	O	11	nsubj
10	may	may	MD	O	11	aux
11	seem	seem	VB	O	0	ROOT
12	redundant	redundant	JJ	O	14	amod
13	,	,	,	O	14	punct
14	weak	weak	JJ	O	11	xcomp
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
17	confusing	confuse	VBG	O	14	conj
18	to	to	TO	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	audience	audience	NN	O	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	4	case
2	his	he	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
3	strategic	strategic	JJ	O	4	amod
4	layout	layout	NN	O	7	nmod
5	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
6	has	have	VBZ	O	7	aux
7	created	create	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	strong	strong	JJ	O	10	amod
10	conversation	conversation	NN	O	7	dobj
11	between	between	IN	O	12	case
12	him	he	PRP	O	10	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	American	american	JJ	MISC	15	amod
15	citizens	citizen	NNS	O	12	conj
16	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	layout	layout	NN	O	10	nsubjpass
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	entire	entire	JJ	O	6	amod
6	address	address	NN	O	2	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	10	auxpass
8	not	not	RB	O	10	neg
9	solely	solely	RB	O	10	advmod
10	considered	consider	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	when	when	WRB	O	12	advmod
12	writing	write	VBG	O	10	advcl
13	this	this	DT	O	14	det
14	speech	speech	NN	O	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	word	word	NN	O	3	compound
3	use	use	NN	O	8	nsubjpass
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	sentence	sentence	NN	O	6	compound
6	structure	structure	NN	O	3	conj
7	are	be	VBP	O	8	auxpass
8	considered	consider	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	;	;	:	O	8	punct
10	For	for	IN	O	11	case
11	example	example	NN	O	8	parataxis
12	when	when	WRB	O	17	advmod
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	member	member	NN	O	17	nsubj
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod
17	asked	ask	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
18	if	if	IN	O	24	mark
19	a	a	DT	O	22	det
20	pinprick	pinprick	NN	O	22	compound
21	military	military	JJ	O	22	amod
22	strike	strike	NN	O	24	nsubj
23	will	will	MD	O	24	aux
24	do	do	VB	O	17	advcl
25	anything	anything	NN	O	24	dobj
26	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
27	intimidate	intimidate	VB	O	24	advcl
28	the	the	DT	O	30	det
29	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	30	compound
30	regime	regime	NN	O	27	dobj
31	to	to	TO	O	32	mark
32	give	give	VB	O	27	xcomp
33	up	up	RP	O	32	compound:prt
34	their	they	PRP$	O	36	nmod:poss
35	chemical	chemical	NN	O	36	compound
36	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	32	dobj
37	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	address	address	NN	O	3	nmod
7	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
8	,	,	,	O	15	punct
9	``	``	``	O	15	punct
10	Even	even	RB	O	13	advmod
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	limited	limited	JJ	O	13	amod
13	strike	strike	NN	O	15	nsubj
14	will	will	MD	O	15	aux
15	send	send	VB	O	3	ccomp
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	massage	massage	NN	O	15	dobj
18	to	to	TO	O	19	case
19	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	15	nmod
20	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
21	no	no	DT	O	23	neg
22	other	other	JJ	O	23	amod
23	nation	nation	NN	O	25	nsubj
24	can	can	MD	O	25	aux
25	deliver	deliver	VB	O	15	ccomp
26	.	.	.	O	3	punct
27	''	''	''	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	encouraging	encourage	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	audience	audience	NN	O	3	nmod
7	because	because	IN	O	9	mark
8	it	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	assures	assure	VBZ	O	3	advcl
10	them	they	PRP	O	9	dobj
11	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
12	we	we	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	have	have	VBP	O	9	ccomp
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	stronger	stronger	JJR	O	16	dep
16	military	military	JJ	O	13	dobj
17	than	than	IN	O	18	case
18	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	16	nmod
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	military	military	JJ	O	18	amod
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Those	those	DT	O	7	nsubj
2	who	who	WP	O	4	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	aux
4	watching	watch	VBG	O	1	acl:relcl
5	internationally	internationally	RB	O	4	advmod
6	might	might	MD	O	7	aux
7	feel	feel	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	intimidated	intimidate	VBN	O	7	dep
9	by	by	IN	O	11	case
10	this	this	DT	O	11	det
11	statement	statement	NN	O	8	nmod
12	because	because	IN	O	24	mark
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	leader	leader	NN	O	24	nsubj
15	of	of	IN	O	19	case
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	most	most	RBS	O	18	advmod
18	powerful	powerful	JJ	O	19	amod
19	nation	nation	NN	O	14	nmod
20	in	in	IN	O	22	case
21	this	this	DT	O	22	det
22	world	world	NN	O	19	nmod
23	is	be	VBZ	O	24	aux
24	pressuring	pressure	VBG	O	8	advcl
25	another	another	DT	O	26	det
26	nation	nation	NN	O	24	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	2	det
2	sense	sense	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	authority	authority	NN	O	2	nmod
5	over	over	IN	O	7	case
6	other	other	JJ	O	7	amod
7	nations	nation	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	comes	come	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	from	from	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	word	word	NN	O	12	compound
12	choices	choice	NNS	O	8	nmod
13	within	within	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	answer	answer	NN	O	8	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	An	a	DT	O	2	det
2	example	example	NN	O	9	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	word	word	NN	O	5	compound
5	choice	choice	NN	O	2	nmod
6	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	word	word	NN	O	9	nmod:npmod
9	limited	limited	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	because	because	IN	O	12	mark
11	it	it	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	implies	imply	VBZ	O	9	advcl
13	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	16	compound
16	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	18	nsubj
17	is	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
18	able	able	JJ	O	12	ccomp
19	do	do	VBP	O	18	ccomp
20	far	far	RB	O	21	advmod
21	worse	worse	JJR	O	19	xcomp
22	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	example	example	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	phrase	phrase	NN	O	2	nmod
6	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	``	``	``	O	12	punct
8	no	no	DT	O	10	neg
9	other	other	JJ	O	10	amod
10	nation	nation	NN	O	12	nsubj
11	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
12	deliver	deliver	VB	O	6	ccomp
13	''	''	''	O	12	punct
14	because	because	IN	O	16	mark
15	this	this	DT	O	16	nsubj
16	implies	imply	VBZ	O	12	advcl
17	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
18	other	other	JJ	O	19	amod
19	nations	nation	NNS	O	21	nsubj
20	are	be	VBP	O	21	cop
21	inferior	inferior	JJ	O	16	ccomp
22	in	in	IN	O	23	case
23	power	power	NN	O	21	nmod
24	when	when	WRB	O	25	advmod
25	compared	compare	VBN	O	21	advcl
26	to	to	TO	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	29	compound
29	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	word	word	NN	O	5	compound
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	phrase	phrase	NN	O	2	conj
5	choices	choice	NNS	O	8	nsubjpass
6	were	be	VBD	O	8	auxpass
7	strategically	strategically	RB	O	8	advmod
8	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	by	by	IN	O	10	case
10	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
11	when	when	WRB	O	12	advmod
12	writing	write	VBG	O	8	advcl
13	this	this	DT	O	14	det
14	speech	speech	NN	O	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	end	end	NN	O	6	nmod
4	President	President	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	implores	implore	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	audience	audience	NN	O	6	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	come	come	VB	O	8	acl
11	together	together	RB	O	10	advmod
12	in	in	IN	O	15	case
13	this	this	DT	O	15	det
14	critical	critical	JJ	O	15	amod
15	situation	situation	NN	O	10	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
17	take	take	VB	O	10	conj
18	away	away	RP	O	17	compound:prt
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	threat	threat	NN	O	17	dobj
21	in	in	IN	O	23	case
22	this	this	DT	O	23	det
23	world	world	NN	O	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	protests	protest	NNS	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
4	have	have	VBP	O	5	aux
5	merged	merge	VBN	O	2	acl:relcl
6	into	into	IN	O	10	case
7	a	a	DT	O	10	det
8	chemical	chemical	NN	O	10	compound
9	weapon	weapon	NN	O	10	compound
10	war	war	NN	O	5	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
14	has	have	VBZ	O	15	aux
15	changed	change	VBN	O	5	conj
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	dynamic	dynamic	NN	O	15	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	23	case
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
21	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	23	nmod:poss
22	'	'	POS	O	21	case
23	involvement	involvement	NN	O	17	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Because	because	IN	O	5	case
2	of	of	IN	O	1	mwe
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	chemical	chemical	NN	O	5	compound
5	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	15	nmod
6	used	use	VBN	O	5	acl
7	by	by	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Assad	Assad	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
10	regime	regime	NN	O	6	nmod
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
13	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	15	nsubj
14	is	be	VBZ	O	15	aux
15	pursuing	pursue	VBG	O	0	ROOT
16	ways	way	NNS	O	15	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	obtain	obtain	VB	O	15	advcl
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	chemical	chemical	NN	O	21	compound
21	weapons	weapon	NNS	O	18	dobj
22	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	efforts	effort	NNS	O	7	nsubj
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	address	address	NN	O	3	nmod
7	described	describe	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	what	what	WP	O	9	nsubj
9	happened	happen	VBD	O	7	ccomp
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	late	late	JJ	DATE	12	amod
12	august	august	NNP	DATE	9	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	organization	organization	NN	O	11	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	address	address	NN	O	3	nmod
7	to	to	TO	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	nation	nation	NN	O	6	nmod
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	explained	explain	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	why	why	WRB	O	15	advmod
13	we	we	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	must	must	MD	O	15	aux
15	act	act	VB	O	11	advcl
16	in	in	IN	O	19	case
17	this	this	DT	O	19	det
18	critical	critical	JJ	O	19	amod
19	situation	situation	NN	O	15	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	what	what	WDT	O	25	dobj
22	plans	plan	NNS	O	25	nsubj
23	are	be	VBP	O	25	cop
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	place	place	NN	O	19	acl:relcl
26	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
27	answered	answer	VBN	O	25	conj
28	uncertainties	uncertainty	NNS	O	27	dobj
29	that	that	IN	O	32	mark
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	audience	audience	NN	O	32	nsubj
32	has	have	VBZ	O	27	ccomp
33	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	structure	structure	NN	O	3	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	persuade	persuade	VB	O	5	acl
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	audience	audience	NN	O	7	dobj
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	address	address	NN	O	7	nmod
13	on	on	IN	O	14	case
14	Syria	Syria	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

