1	What	what	WP	O	0	ROOT
2	are	be	VBP	O	1	cop
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	1	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	foods	food	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	?	?	.	O	1	punct

1	What	what	WP	O	0	ROOT
2	are	be	VBP	O	1	cop
3	their	they	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	risks	risk	NNS	O	1	nsubj
5	?	?	.	O	1	punct

1	Should	should	MD	O	5	aux
2	GMO	GMO	NNP	O	3	compound
3	foods	food	NNS	O	5	nsubjpass
4	be	be	VB	O	5	auxpass
5	labeled	label	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	?	?	.	O	5	punct

1	How	how	WRB	O	2	advmod
2	healthy	healthy	JJ	O	3	dep
3	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	foods	food	NNS	O	3	nsubj
6	for	for	IN	O	7	case
7	humans	human	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	12	det
2	more	more	RBR	O	12	amod
3	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	consumers	consumer	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	know	know	VBP	O	2	ccomp
7	about	about	IN	O	9	case
8	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	foods	food	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	the	the	DT	O	11	dep
11	more	more	RBR	O	6	advmod
12	questions	question	NNS	O	14	nsubjpass
13	are	be	VBP	O	14	auxpass
14	asked	ask	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	What	what	WDT	O	5	nsubj
2	exactly	exactly	RB	O	5	advmod
3	are	be	VBP	O	5	cop
4	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	foods	food	NNS	O	0	ROOT
6	?	?	.	O	5	punct

1	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	foods	food	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	cop
4	crops	crop	NNS	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	WDT	O	6	nsubj
6	have	have	VBP	O	4	acl:relcl
7	their	they	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	DNA	dna	NN	O	6	dobj
9	modified	modify	VBN	O	8	acl
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	resist	resist	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	certain	certain	JJ	O	13	amod
13	diseases	disease	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	bugs	bug	NNS	O	13	conj
16	,	,	,	O	13	punct
17	weather	weather	NN	O	13	conj
18	,	,	,	O	13	punct
19	inhabitable	inhabitable	JJ	O	21	amod
20	soil	soil	NN	O	21	compound
21	conditions	condition	NNS	O	13	conj
22	,	,	,	O	13	punct
23	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
24	other	other	JJ	O	25	amod
25	problems	problem	NNS	O	13	conj
26	that	that	WDT	O	28	nsubj
27	could	could	MD	O	28	aux
28	hinder	hinder	VB	O	8	acl:relcl
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	supply	supply	NN	O	28	dobj
31	of	of	IN	O	32	case
32	food	food	NN	O	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	To	to	TO	O	2	mark
2	gain	gain	VB	O	8	dep
3	knowledge	knowledge	NN	O	2	dobj
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	these	these	DT	O	6	det
6	questions	question	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	gathered	gather	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	following	follow	VBG	O	12	amod
11	annotated	annotated	JJ	O	12	amod
12	bibliography	bibliography	NN	O	8	dobj
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	research	research	NN	O	15	compound
15	reflection	reflection	NN	O	12	conj
16	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Aschbrenner	Aschbrenner	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Joel	Joel	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Eller	Eller	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Donnelle	Donnelle	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	4	punct
2	GMO	GMO	NNP	O	3	compound
3	discussion	discussion	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	sharply	sharply	RB	O	4	advmod
6	opposing	opposing	JJ	O	7	amod
7	views	view	NNS	O	4	dobj
8	''	''	''	O	7	punct
9	DesMoinesRegister.com	DesMoinesRegister.com	NNP	O	7	appos
10	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	15	15	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Web	web	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	19	19	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	det
2	article	article	NN	O	3	compound
3	reports	report	NNS	O	0	ROOT
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	discussion	discussion	NN	O	3	nmod
7	among	among	IN	O	8	case
8	farmers	farmer	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	researchers	researcher	NNS	O	8	conj
11	,	,	,	O	8	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
13	others	other	NNS	O	8	conj
14	who	who	WP	O	15	nsubj
15	work	work	VBP	O	6	acl:relcl
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	industry	industry	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	debate	debate	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	brought	bring	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	up	up	RB	O	3	advmod
5	different	different	JJ	O	6	amod
6	arguments	argument	NNS	O	4	nmod:npmod
7	such	such	JJ	O	8	case
8	as	as	IN	O	3	advcl
9	:	:	:	O	3	punct
10	there	there	EX	O	11	expl
11	is	be	VBZ	O	3	parataxis
12	no	no	DT	O	13	neg
13	proof	proof	NN	O	11	nsubj
14	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
15	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
16	foods	food	NNS	O	18	nsubj
17	are	be	VBP	O	18	cop
18	bad	bad	JJ	O	11	ccomp
19	for	for	IN	O	22	case
20	peoples	people	NNS	O	22	nmod:poss
21	'	'	POS	O	20	case
22	health	health	NN	O	18	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	3	punct
24	there	there	EX	O	25	expl
25	is	be	VBZ	O	3	parataxis
26	less	less	JJR	O	28	amod
27	land	land	NN	O	28	compound
28	erosion	erosion	NN	O	25	nsubj
29	from	from	IN	O	30	case
30	it	it	PRP	O	28	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	3	punct
32	less	less	JJR	O	34	amod
33	pesticide	pesticide	NN	O	34	compound
34	use	use	NN	O	3	parataxis
35	,	,	,	O	34	punct
36	less	less	JJR	O	37	amod
37	diversity	diversity	NN	O	34	appos
38	within	within	IN	O	39	case
39	plants	plant	NNS	O	37	nmod
40	,	,	,	O	34	punct
41	among	among	IN	O	42	case
42	others	other	NNS	O	34	dep
43	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	participant	participant	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	Ruth	Ruth	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	MacDonald	MacDonald	NNP	PERSON	2	appos
6	,	,	,	O	2	punct
7	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
9	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	foods	food	NNS	O	12	nsubj
11	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
12	safe	safe	JJ	O	7	ccomp
13	for	for	IN	O	14	case
14	consumers	consumer	NNS	O	12	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	leads	lead	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	food	food	NN	O	5	compound
5	science	science	NN	O	2	dobj
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	human	human	JJ	O	8	amod
8	nutrition	nutrition	NN	O	5	conj
9	at	at	IN	O	12	case
10	Iowa	Iowa	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
11	State	State	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	University	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	farmers	farmer	NNS	O	11	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	who	who	WP	O	5	nsubj
5	plant	plant	VBP	O	2	acl:relcl
6	the	the	DT	O	9	det
7	genetically	genetically	RB	O	8	advmod
8	modified	modify	VBN	O	9	amod
9	crops	crop	NNS	O	5	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	2	punct
11	lashed	lash	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	back	back	RB	O	11	advmod
13	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
14	said	say	VBD	O	11	conj
15	their	they	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
16	pesticide	pesticide	NN	O	17	compound
17	use	use	NN	O	20	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
19	more	more	RBR	O	20	advmod
20	frequent	frequent	JJ	O	14	ccomp
21	now	now	RB	DATE	20	advmod
22	compared	compare	VBN	O	25	case
23	to	to	TO	O	25	case
24	a	a	DT	DATE	25	det
25	couple	couple	NN	DATE	20	advcl
26	years	year	NNS	DATE	27	nmod:npmod
27	ago	ago	RB	DATE	25	advmod
28	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	large	large	JJ	O	3	amod
3	amount	amount	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	pesticide	pesticide	NN	O	6	compound
6	use	use	NN	O	3	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	aux
8	costing	cost	VBG	O	0	ROOT
9	them	they	PRP	O	8	iobj
10	thousands	thousand	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	dollars	dollar	NNS	O	10	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	issue	issue	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	labeling	labeling	NN	O	2	nmod
5	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	up	up	RB	O	7	advmod
7	later	later	RB	O	5	advmod
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	conversation	conversation	NN	O	5	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	6	nsubj
2	would	would	MD	O	6	aux
3	be	be	VB	O	6	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	reliable	reliable	JJ	O	6	amod
6	source	source	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	because	because	IN	O	13	mark
8	many	many	JJ	O	13	nsubj
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	people	people	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	involved	involve	VBN	O	11	acl
13	give	give	VBP	O	6	advcl
14	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	15	amod
15	hand	hand	NN	O	13	iobj
16	accounts	account	NNS	O	13	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	leads	lead	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	credibility	credibility	NN	O	2	dobj
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	value	value	NN	O	3	conj
6	of	of	IN	O	10	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	stakeholders	stakeholder	NNS	O	10	nmod:poss
9	'	'	POS	O	8	case
10	stories	story	NNS	O	3	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	good	good	JJ	O	5	amod
5	collection	collection	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	7	case
7	arguments	argument	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	that	that	WDT	O	10	nsubjpass
9	are	be	VBP	O	10	auxpass
10	made	make	VBN	O	7	acl:relcl
11	on	on	IN	O	13	case
12	this	this	DT	O	13	det
13	issue	issue	NN	O	10	nmod
14	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
15	can	can	MD	O	17	aux
16	be	be	VB	O	17	auxpass
17	used	use	VBN	O	10	conj
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	DATE	20	det
20	future	future	NN	DATE	17	nmod
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	argue	argue	VB	O	17	xcomp
23	different	different	JJ	O	24	amod
24	points	point	NNS	O	22	dobj
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	view	view	NN	O	24	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Bartolotto	Bartolotto	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Carole	Carole	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	8	punct
2	Why	why	WRB	O	4	advmod
3	Genetically	genetically	RB	O	4	advmod
4	Modified	modify	VBN	O	8	advcl
5	Foods	Foods	NNP	O	8	nsubjpass
6	Should	should	MD	O	8	aux
7	Be	be	VB	O	8	auxpass
8	Labeled	label	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	.	.	.	O	8	punct
10	''	''	''	O	8	punct

1	Dick	Dick	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
2	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
3	Sharon	Sharon	NNP	PERSON	1	conj
4	's	's	POS	O	1	case
5	LA	LA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Progressive	Progressive	NNP	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
7	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	7	7	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	September	September	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2012	2012	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Web	web	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	19	19	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Bartolotto	Bartolotto	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
4	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	foods	food	NNS	O	8	nsubjpass
6	should	should	MD	O	8	aux
7	be	be	VB	O	8	auxpass
8	labeled	label	VBN	O	2	ccomp
9	because	because	IN	O	13	mark
10	we	we	PRP	O	13	nsubj
11	do	do	VBP	O	13	aux
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	know	know	VB	O	8	advcl
14	their	they	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	full	full	JJ	O	16	amod
16	effects	effect	NNS	O	13	dobj
17	on	on	IN	O	18	case
18	humans	human	NNS	O	13	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	least	least	JJS	O	10	nsubj
3	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
4	these	these	DT	O	5	det
5	companies	company	NNS	O	7	nsubj
6	can	can	MD	O	7	aux
7	do	do	VB	O	2	dep
8	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
9	label	label	NN	O	10	compound
10	products	product	NNS	O	0	ROOT
11	that	that	WDT	O	12	nsubj
12	contain	contain	VBP	O	10	acl:relcl
13	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
14	foods	food	NNS	O	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Bartolotto	Bartolotto	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	bias	bias	NN	O	2	dobj
5	for	for	IN	O	8	case
6	no	no	DT	O	8	neg
7	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	foods	food	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
10	does	do	VBZ	O	2	conj
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	present	present	JJ	DATE	13	amod
13	arguments	argument	NNS	O	10	dobj
14	for	for	IN	O	16	case
15	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
16	foods	food	NNS	O	10	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	even	even	RB	O	3	advmod
3	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	companies	company	NNS	O	8	nsubj
7	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
8	greedy	greedy	JJ	O	3	ccomp
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	power	power	NN	O	11	nmod:npmod
11	hungry	hungry	JJ	O	8	conj
12	so	so	IN	O	14	mark
13	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	spend	spend	VBP	O	8	advcl
15	millions	million	NNS	MONEY	14	dobj
16	of	of	IN	MONEY	17	case
17	dollars	dollar	NNS	MONEY	15	nmod
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	avoid	avoid	VB	O	14	xcomp
20	labeling	labeling	NN	O	19	dobj
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	3	mark
2	she	she	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	13	advcl
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	bias	bias	NN	O	3	dobj
6	toward	toward	IN	O	7	mark
7	labeling	label	VBG	O	5	acl
8	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	foods	food	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	this	this	DT	O	11	det
11	article	article	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
13	reliable	reliable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
14	because	because	IN	O	16	mark
15	she	she	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	provides	provide	VBZ	O	13	advcl
17	statistics	statistics	NNS	O	16	dobj
18	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
19	I	I	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	found	find	VBD	O	16	ccomp
21	in	in	IN	O	23	case
22	other	other	JJ	O	23	amod
23	sources	source	NNS	O	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	masters	master	NNS	O	5	compound
5	degree	degree	NN	O	2	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	exercise	exercise	NN	O	8	compound
8	physiology	physiology	NN	O	5	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
10	has	have	VBZ	O	12	aux
11	been	be	VBN	O	12	aux
12	working	work	VBG	O	2	conj
13	in	in	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	diet	diet	NN	O	16	compound
16	field	field	NN	O	12	nmod
17	for	for	IN	O	20	case
18	over	over	IN	O	20	amod
19	twenty	twenty	CD	DURATION	20	nummod
20	years	year	NNS	DURATION	16	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Bech-Larson	Bech-Larson	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Tino	Tino	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Grunert	Grunert	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Klaus	Klaus	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
4	G.	G.	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Lahteenmaki	Lahteenmaki	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	Liisa	Liisa	NNP	PERSON	5	appos
8	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Attitudes	attitude	NNS	O	0	ROOT
3	Towards	towards	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	Use	use	NN	O	2	nmod
6	of	of	IN	O	7	case
7	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	Food	Food	NNP	O	10	compound
10	Production	Production	NNP	O	7	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
12	Their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	Impact	impact	NN	O	5	conj
14	on	on	IN	O	16	case
15	Buying	buy	VBG	O	16	amod
16	Intention	intention	NN	O	13	nmod
17	:	:	:	O	13	punct
18	The	the	DT	O	19	det
19	Role	role	NN	O	13	dep
20	of	of	IN	O	23	case
21	Positive	positive	JJ	O	23	amod
22	Sensory	sensory	NN	O	23	compound
23	Experience	experience	NN	O	19	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct
25	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	Agribusiness	agribusiness	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	20.1	20.1	NN	NUMBER	0	ROOT
2	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	3	punct
3	2004	2004	CD	DATE	1	appos
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	3	punct
5	:	:	:	O	1	punct
6	95-107	95-107	CD	NUMBER	1	dep
7	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Biological	Biological	NNP	O	5	compound
2	&	&	CC	O	1	cc
3	Agricultural	Agricultural	NNP	O	1	conj
4	Index	Index	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Plus	Plus	NNP	O	0	ROOT
6	Web	web	NN	O	5	dep
7	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	19	19	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	det
2	academic	academic	JJ	O	4	amod
3	article	article	NN	O	4	compound
4	reports	report	NNS	O	28	nsubj
5	on	on	IN	O	7	case
6	an	a	DT	O	7	det
7	experiment	experiment	NN	O	4	nmod
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	which	which	WDT	O	11	nmod
10	researchers	researcher	NNS	O	11	nsubj
11	chose	choose	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	sample	sample	NN	O	11	dobj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	people	people	NNS	O	13	nmod
16	from	from	IN	O	18	case
17	four	four	CD	NUMBER	18	nummod
18	countries	country	NNS	O	11	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	11	punct
20	in	in	IN	O	23	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	European	European	NNP	LOCATION	23	compound
23	Union	Union	NNP	LOCATION	11	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	23	punct
25	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	participants	participant	NNS	O	23	conj
28	tasted	taste	VBD	O	0	ROOT
29	different	different	JJ	O	30	amod
30	cheeses	cheese	NNS	O	28	dobj
31	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	experiment	experiment	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	don	don	VB	O	3	ccomp
5	in	in	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	European	European	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
8	Union	Union	NNP	LOCATION	4	nmod
9	because	because	IN	O	15	mark
10	people	people	NNS	O	15	nsubj
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	those	those	DT	O	13	det
13	countries	country	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	are	be	VBP	O	15	cop
15	skeptical	skeptical	JJ	O	4	advcl
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	foods	food	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	researchers	researcher	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	then	then	RB	O	4	advmod
4	asked	ask	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	participants	participant	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	if	if	IN	O	9	mark
8	they	they	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	thought	think	VBD	O	4	advcl
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	cheese	cheese	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	13	cop
13	tasteful	tasteful	JJ	O	9	ccomp
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	experimental	experimental	JJ	O	3	amod
3	group	group	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	positive	positive	JJ	O	7	amod
7	experience	experience	NN	O	4	dobj
8	tasting	tasting	NN	O	10	dep
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	cheeses	cheese	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	reliable	reliable	JJ	O	5	amod
5	journal	journal	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	because	because	IN	O	8	mark
7	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	found	find	VBD	O	5	advcl
9	it	it	PRP	O	8	dobj
10	on	on	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	database	database	NN	O	8	nmod
13	through	through	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	library	library	NN	O	16	compound
16	system	system	NN	O	8	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	authors	author	NNS	O	5	nsubj
5	work	work	VBP	O	0	ROOT
6	within	within	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	field	field	NN	O	5	nmod
9	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	in	in	IN	O	4	case
3	text	text	NN	O	4	compound
4	citations	citation	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	inform	inform	VBP	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	reader	reader	NN	O	5	dobj
8	where	where	WRB	O	11	advmod
9	they	they	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	can	can	MD	O	11	aux
11	go	go	VB	O	7	acl:relcl
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	find	find	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	out	out	RP	O	13	compound:prt
15	more	more	JJR	O	13	dobj
16	about	about	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	subject	subject	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	more	more	JJR	O	4	amod
4	accuracy	accuracy	NN	O	2	nsubj
5	with	with	IN	O	7	case
6	this	this	DT	O	7	det
7	article	article	NN	O	4	nmod
8	than	than	IN	O	13	mark
9	with	with	IN	O	10	case
10	others	other	NNS	O	13	nmod
11	I	I	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	have	have	VBP	O	13	aux
13	found	find	VBN	O	2	advcl
14	because	because	IN	O	18	mark
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	results	result	NNS	O	18	nsubjpass
17	are	be	VBP	O	18	auxpass
18	posted	post	VBN	O	13	advcl
19	within	within	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	journal	journal	NN	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	useful	useful	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	see	see	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	how	how	WRB	O	8	advmod
7	people	people	NNS	O	8	nsubj
8	react	react	VBP	O	5	ccomp
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	eating	eat	VBG	O	8	advcl
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	food	food	NN	O	10	dobj
14	that	that	WDT	O	16	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
16	tasteful	tasteful	JJ	O	13	acl:relcl
17	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Eng	Eng	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Monica	Monica	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	4	punct
2	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	supporter	supporter	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	tells	tell	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	food	food	NN	O	7	compound
6	industry	industry	NN	O	7	compound
7	meeting	meeting	NN	O	4	dobj
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	Chicago	Chicago	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	stop	stop	VB	O	4	xcomp
12	opposing	oppose	VBG	O	11	xcomp
13	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	dobj
14	labeling	labeling	NN	O	16	compound
15	''	''	''	O	16	punct
16	wbez.org	wbez.org	NN	O	13	dep
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	16	16	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Web	web	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	19	19	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	features	feature	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	strong	strong	JJ	O	6	amod
6	supporter	supporter	NN	O	3	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	foods	food	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Lynas	Lynas	NNP	PERSON	9	appos
13	,	,	,	O	9	punct
14	who	who	WP	O	15	nsubj
15	supports	support	VBZ	O	9	acl:relcl
16	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	labeling	labeling	NN	O	15	dobj
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Lynas	Lynas	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	presentation	presentation	NN	O	2	dobj
5	that	that	IN	O	9	mark
6	many	many	JJ	O	8	amod
7	agricultural	agricultural	JJ	O	8	amod
8	companies	company	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	attended	attend	VBD	O	2	ccomp
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	have	have	VBP	O	12	aux
12	taken	take	VBN	O	9	conj
13	time	time	NN	O	12	nmod:tmod
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	think	think	VB	O	12	xcomp
16	about	about	IN	O	19	mark
17	what	what	WP	O	19	dobj
18	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	had	have	VBD	O	15	advcl
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	say	say	VB	O	19	xcomp
22	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	main	main	JJ	O	3	amod
3	argument	argument	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
5	for	for	IN	O	8	case
6	these	these	DT	O	8	det
7	large	large	JJ	O	8	amod
8	companies	company	NNS	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
10	be	be	VB	O	12	cop
11	more	more	RBR	O	12	advmod
12	transparent	transparent	JJ	O	8	xcomp
13	to	to	TO	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	consumer	consumer	NN	O	12	nmod
16	by	by	IN	O	17	mark
17	labeling	label	VBG	O	12	advcl
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	food	food	NN	O	17	dobj
20	that	that	WDT	O	21	nsubj
21	contain	contain	VBP	O	19	acl:relcl
22	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	21	dobj
23	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	many	many	JJ	O	5	amod
5	quotes	quote	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	from	from	IN	O	9	case
7	these	these	DT	O	9	det
8	agricultural	agricultural	JJ	O	9	amod
9	companies	company	NNS	O	5	nmod
10	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
11	prove	prove	VBP	O	9	acl:relcl
12	it	it	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	's	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
14	authority	authority	NN	O	11	ccomp
15	to	to	TO	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	audience	audience	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Eng	eng	NN	O	3	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	show	show	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
5	those	those	DT	O	12	nsubj
6	who	who	WP	O	8	nsubjpass
7	are	be	VBP	O	8	auxpass
8	quoted	quote	VBN	O	5	acl:relcl
9	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
10	pro	pro	JJ	O	12	amod
11	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	foods	food	NNS	O	3	dep
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	but	but	CC	O	12	cc
15	against	against	IN	O	17	case
16	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	labeling	labeling	NN	O	12	conj
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Lynas	Lynas	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	mixture	mixture	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	8	case
6	pro	pro	JJ	O	8	amod
7	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	foods	food	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	Pro	pro	FW	O	12	compound
11	GMO	gmo	FW	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	labeling	labeling	NN	O	8	conj
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	an	a	DT	O	5	det
4	interesting	interesting	JJ	O	5	amod
5	article	article	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	WDT	O	7	nsubj
7	gives	give	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
8	this	this	DT	O	9	det
9	issue	issue	NN	O	7	iobj
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	different	different	JJ	O	12	amod
12	point	point	NN	O	7	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	view	view	NN	O	12	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	very	very	RB	O	5	advmod
5	useful	useful	JJ	O	0	ROOT
6	for	for	IN	O	7	mark
7	explaining	explain	VBG	O	5	advcl
8	other	other	JJ	O	9	amod
9	thoughts	thought	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	on	on	IN	O	12	case
11	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	foods	food	NNS	O	7	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	credible	credible	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	because	because	IN	O	7	mark
6	Eng	Eng	NNP	O	7	nsubj
7	gives	give	VBZ	O	4	advcl
8	background	background	NN	O	7	iobj
9	information	information	NN	O	7	dobj
10	about	about	IN	O	11	case
11	Lynas	Lynas	NNP	PERSON	9	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	only	only	RB	O	3	advmod
3	reports	report	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	what	what	WP	O	5	nsubj
5	happened	happen	VBD	O	3	ccomp
6	at	at	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	presentation	presentation	NN	O	5	nmod
9	she	she	PRP	O	12	nsubj
10	does	do	VBZ	O	12	aux
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	put	put	VB	O	8	acl:relcl
13	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	opinion	opinion	NN	O	12	dobj
15	into	into	IN	O	17	case
16	this	this	DT	O	17	det
17	article	article	NN	O	12	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Food	Food	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Inc.	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Dir	Dir	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Robert	Robert	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Kenner	Kenner	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Perf	perf	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Eric	Eric	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Schlosser	Schlosser	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Magnolia	Magnolia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
2	Home	Home	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	Entertianment	Entertianment	NNP	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	2009	2009	CD	DATE	3	amod
6	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	DVD	dvd	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Food	Food	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Inc.	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	documentary	documentary	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	about	about	IN	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	food	food	NN	O	9	compound
9	industry	industry	NN	O	5	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
13	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	9	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Kenner	Kenner	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	dives	dive	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	deep	deep	RB	O	2	advmod
4	into	into	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	darkness	darkness	NN	O	3	nmod
7	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	food	food	NN	O	10	compound
10	industry	industry	NN	O	11	nsubj
11	puts	put	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	consumer	consumer	NN	O	11	dobj
14	in	in	IN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	shines	shine	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	light	light	NN	O	2	dobj
5	on	on	IN	O	8	mark
6	how	how	WRB	O	8	advmod
7	they	they	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	raise	raise	VBP	O	4	acl
9	meet	meet	VB	O	8	xcomp
10	,	,	,	O	4	punct
11	poultry	poultry	NN	O	4	appos
12	,	,	,	O	4	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
14	pork	pork	NN	O	4	conj
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	good	good	JJ	O	3	amod
3	portion	portion	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	Food	Food	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Inc.	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nmod
7	focuses	focus	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	on	on	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	meat	meat	NN	O	11	compound
11	production	production	NN	O	7	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	packing	packing	NN	O	14	compound
14	industry	industry	NN	O	11	conj
15	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Later	later	RB	O	3	advmod
2	Kenner	Kenner	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	moves	move	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	into	into	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	crops	crop	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	gives	give	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	history	history	NN	O	2	iobj
5	lesson	lesson	NN	O	2	dobj
6	on	on	IN	O	7	case
7	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	chemical	chemical	NN	O	11	compound
11	company	company	NN	O	7	appos
12	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
13	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	14	advmod
14	produced	produce	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
15	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
16	seeds	seed	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	interviews	interview	NNS	O	4	dep
3	many	many	JJ	O	4	amod
4	farmers	farmer	NNS	O	0	ROOT
5	about	about	IN	O	6	case
6	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
8	what	what	WP	O	12	dobj
9	precautions	precaution	NNS	O	12	nsubj
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	company	company	NN	O	9	dep
12	takes	take	VBZ	O	4	conj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	prevent	prevent	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	farmers	farmer	NNS	O	14	dobj
16	from	from	IN	O	17	mark
17	saving	save	VBG	O	14	advcl
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	seeds	seed	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	from	from	IN	O	23	case
21	their	they	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
22	last	last	JJ	O	23	amod
23	crop	crop	NN	O	17	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	7	advmod
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	end	end	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	documentary	documentary	NN	O	3	nmod
7	dives	dive	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	into	into	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	argument	argument	NN	O	7	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	labeling	labeling	NN	O	10	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
14	how	how	WRB	O	18	advmod
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	large	large	JJ	O	17	amod
17	companies	company	NNS	O	18	nsubj
18	want	want	VBP	O	10	conj
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	prevent	prevent	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	it	it	PRP	O	20	dobj
22	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	an	a	DT	O	5	det
4	empowering	empower	VBG	O	5	amod
5	film	film	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	for	for	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	consumer	consumer	NN	O	5	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
10	tells	tell	VBZ	O	5	conj
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	consumer	consumer	NN	O	10	dobj
13	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
14	they	they	PRP	O	16	nsubj
15	can	can	MD	O	16	aux
16	do	do	VB	O	10	ccomp
17	something	something	NN	O	16	dobj
18	about	about	IN	O	19	case
19	it	it	PRP	O	16	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	documentary	documentary	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	very	very	RB	O	5	advmod
5	detailed	detailed	JJ	O	0	ROOT
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	contains	contain	VBZ	O	5	conj
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	couple	couple	NN	O	7	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	case	case	NN	O	12	compound
12	studies	study	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	interviews	interview	NNS	O	12	conj
15	,	,	,	O	12	punct
16	history	history	NN	O	12	conj
17	,	,	,	O	12	punct
18	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
19	statistics	statistics	NNS	O	12	conj
20	for	for	IN	O	21	case
21	credibility	credibility	NN	O	7	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	will	will	MD	O	3	aux
3	use	use	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	information	information	NN	O	3	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	my	my	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	essay	essay	NN	O	3	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	explain	explain	VB	O	8	acl
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	industries	industry	NNS	O	13	compound
13	power	power	NN	O	10	dobj
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	government	government	NN	O	10	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
18	give	give	VB	O	10	conj
19	statistics	statistics	NNS	O	18	dobj
20	on	on	IN	O	22	case
21	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
22	foods	food	NNS	O	18	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Haslberger	Haslberger	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Alexander	Alexander	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
4	G.	G.	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
5	``	``	``	PERSON	6	punct
6	Monitoring	monitoring	NN	PERSON	1	appos
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	labeling	labeling	NN	O	6	conj
9	for	for	IN	O	12	case
10	genetically	genetically	RB	O	11	advmod
11	modified	modify	VBN	O	12	amod
12	products	product	NNS	O	6	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	1	punct
14	''	''	''	O	1	punct

1	Science	science	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	287.5452	287.5452	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
2	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	3	punct
3	2000	2000	CD	DATE	1	appos
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	3	punct
5	:	:	:	O	1	punct
6	431-432	431-432	CD	NUMBER	1	dep
7	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Biological	Biological	NNP	O	5	compound
2	&	&	CC	O	1	cc
3	Agricultural	Agricultural	NNP	O	1	conj
4	Index	Index	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Plus	Plus	NNP	O	0	ROOT
6	Web	web	NN	O	5	dep
7	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	19	19	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	det
2	academic	academic	JJ	O	3	amod
3	journal	journal	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	aux
5	informing	inform	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	10	case
7	the	the	DT	O	10	det
8	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
9	food	food	NN	O	10	compound
10	situation	situation	NN	O	5	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	other	other	JJ	O	13	amod
13	countries	country	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	4	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	3	case
3	them	they	PRP	O	1	nmod
4	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	legislation	legislation	NN	O	4	dobj
6	put	put	VBD	O	5	acl:relcl
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	place	place	NN	O	6	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	regulate	regulate	VB	O	6	xcomp
11	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	foods	food	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	countries	country	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	label	label	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	foods	food	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	that	that	WDT	O	7	nsubj
7	contain	contain	VBP	O	5	acl:relcl
8	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	12	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	some	some	DT	O	11	det
11	countries	country	NNS	O	8	conj
12	refuse	refuse	VBP	O	7	ccomp
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	accept	accept	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	them	they	PRP	O	14	dobj
16	from	from	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	19	compound
19	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	14	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	causing	cause	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	many	many	JJ	O	5	amod
5	issues	issue	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	with	with	IN	O	7	case
7	exports	export	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	from	from	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	7	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Haslberger	Haslberger	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	gives	give	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	information	information	NN	O	2	dobj
4	from	from	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	European	European	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	Union	Union	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
8	with	with	IN	O	9	case
9	references	reference	NNS	O	7	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	make	make	VB	O	2	advcl
12	this	this	DT	O	14	det
13	academic	academic	JJ	O	14	amod
14	journal	journal	NN	O	15	nsubj
15	reliable	reliable	JJ	O	11	xcomp
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	seems	seem	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
4	be	be	VB	O	6	cop
5	no	no	DT	O	6	neg
6	bias	bias	NN	O	2	xcomp
7	here	here	RB	O	11	advmod
8	because	because	IN	O	11	mark
9	Haslberger	Haslberger	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	11	aux
11	informing	inform	VBG	O	6	advcl
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	audience	audience	NN	O	11	dobj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	13	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	other	other	JJ	O	18	amod
18	countries	country	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	compared	compare	VBN	O	23	case
20	to	to	TO	O	23	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	23	compound
23	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	11	advcl
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Leiser	Leiser	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Ken	Ken	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	2	punct
2	Hundreds	hundred	NNS	O	0	ROOT
3	protest	protest	NN	O	2	dep
4	outside	outside	IN	O	6	case
5	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	headquarters	headquarters	NN	O	3	nmod
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	St.	St.	NNP	LOCATION	9	compound
9	Louis	Louis	NNP	LOCATION	2	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	2	punct
11	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	stltoday.com	stltoday.com	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	:	:	:	O	1	punct
3	St.	St.	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
4	Louis	Louis	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Post-Dispatch	Post-Dispatch	NNP	PERSON	1	dep
6	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	13	13	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Web	web	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	19	19	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Leiser	Leiser	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	main	main	JJ	O	5	amod
5	objective	objective	NN	O	1	dep
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	article	article	NN	O	1	nmod
9	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	inform	inform	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	audience	audience	NN	O	11	dobj
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	protest	protest	NN	O	13	nmod
17	that	that	WDT	O	18	nsubj
18	occurred	occur	VBD	O	16	acl:relcl
19	outside	outside	IN	O	18	advmod
20	of	of	IN	O	23	case
21	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	headquarters	headquarters	NN	O	18	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	More	more	JJR	O	3	advmod
2	than	than	IN	O	1	mwe
3	five-hundred	five-hundred	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
4	people	people	NNS	O	5	nsubj
5	showed	show	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	up	up	IN	O	5	compound:prt
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	make	make	VB	O	5	xcomp
9	their	they	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	grievances	grievance	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	known	know	VBN	O	10	acl
12	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	chemical	chemical	NN	O	5	compound
5	company	company	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	WDT	O	8	nsubj
7	genetically	genetically	RB	O	8	advmod
8	modifies	modify	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
9	plants	plant	NNS	O	8	dobj
10	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	crowd	crowd	NN	O	10	nmod
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	farmer	farmer	NN	O	10	nsubj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	Mark	Mark	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Brown	Brown	NNP	PERSON	5	appos
9	,	,	,	O	5	punct
10	stepped	step	VBD	O	0	ROOT
11	out	out	RP	O	10	compound:prt
12	for	for	IN	O	15	case
13	a	a	DT	O	15	det
14	short	short	JJ	O	15	amod
15	interview	interview	NN	O	10	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	does	do	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	have	have	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	strong	strong	JJ	O	8	amod
8	bias	bias	NN	O	5	dobj
9	because	because	IN	O	11	mark
10	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	presents	present	VBZ	O	5	advcl
12	news	news	NN	O	11	dobj
13	from	from	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	protest	protest	NN	O	11	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Leiser	Leiser	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	more	more	RBR	O	4	nummod
4	access	access	NN	O	2	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	protesters	protester	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	because	because	IN	O	10	mark
9	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	nsubj
10	made	make	VBD	O	2	advcl
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	statement	statement	NN	O	10	dobj
13	on	on	IN	O	14	case
14	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	10	nmod
15	before	before	IN	DATE	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	protest	protest	NN	O	10	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	provides	provide	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	information	information	NN	O	3	dobj
5	on	on	IN	O	6	case
6	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	on	on	IN	O	10	case
9	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	crops	crop	NNS	O	6	conj
11	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	credible	credible	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	because	because	IN	O	7	mark
5	Lesier	Lesier	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	aux
7	reporting	report	VBG	O	3	advcl
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	protest	protest	NN	O	7	dobj
10	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	adding	add	VBG	O	7	conj
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	opinion	opinion	NN	O	12	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	issue	issue	NN	O	12	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
3	be	be	VB	O	4	cop
4	good	good	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	use	use	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	as	as	IN	O	9	case
8	an	a	DT	O	9	det
9	example	example	NN	O	6	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	14	mark
11	how	how	WRB	O	14	advmod
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	stakeholders	stakeholder	NNS	O	14	nsubj
14	feel	feel	VBP	O	9	acl
15	about	about	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	issue	issue	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Round	Round	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Christopher	Christopher	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	``	``	``	O	3	punct
2	One	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	thing	thing	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	Everyone	everyone	NN	O	3	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	Missing	miss	VBG	O	3	acl
7	About	about	RB	O	6	advmod
8	GMO	GMO	NNP	O	9	compound
9	Foods	Foods	NNPS	O	6	dobj
10	''	''	''	O	6	punct
11	PolicyMic	PolicyMic	NNP	O	6	dobj
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	16	16	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Web	web	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	19	19	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
2	October	October	NNP	DATE	1	dep
3	2013	2013	CD	DATE	2	nummod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	mentions	mention	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	protest	protest	NN	O	3	dobj
6	from	from	IN	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	Leiser	leiser	NN	PERSON	9	compound
9	article	article	NN	O	3	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
11	goes	go	VBZ	O	3	conj
12	into	into	IN	O	14	case
13	more	more	JJR	O	14	amod
14	detail	detail	NN	O	11	nmod
15	about	about	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	negatives	negative	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
19	positive	positive	JJ	O	14	conj
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
22	crops	crop	NNS	O	19	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Round	Round	NNP	O	2	nsubj
2	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	two	two	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
4	good	good	JJ	O	5	amod
5	points	point	NNS	O	2	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	article	article	NN	O	5	nmod
9	;	;	:	O	2	punct
10	an	a	DT	O	11	det
11	argument	argument	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	against	against	IN	O	11	acl
13	is	be	VBZ	O	2	parataxis
14	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	diversity	diversity	NN	O	20	nsubj
17	among	among	IN	O	18	case
18	plants	plant	NNS	O	16	nmod
19	will	will	MD	O	20	aux
20	diminish	diminish	VB	O	13	ccomp
21	,	,	,	O	13	punct
22	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	argument	argument	NN	O	26	nsubj
25	for	for	IN	O	24	acl
26	is	be	VBZ	O	13	conj
27	that	that	IN	O	31	mark
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	plants	plant	NNS	O	31	nsubj
30	could	could	MD	O	31	aux
31	become	become	VB	O	26	ccomp
32	resistant	resistant	JJ	O	37	amod
33	to	to	TO	O	34	case
34	heat	heat	NN	O	32	nmod
35	or	or	CC	O	32	cc
36	inhospitable	inhospitable	JJ	O	32	conj
37	soil	soil	NN	O	31	xcomp
38	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	main	main	JJ	O	3	amod
3	part	part	NN	O	20	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	article	article	NN	O	7	compound
7	focus	focus	NN	O	3	nmod
8	on	on	IN	O	12	case
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	diminishing	diminish	VBG	O	12	amod
11	genetic	genetic	JJ	O	12	amod
12	diversity	diversity	NN	O	7	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	complications	complication	NNS	O	12	conj
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	acres	acre	NNS	O	15	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	19	case
19	crops	crop	NNS	O	17	nmod
20	wiped	wipe	VBD	O	0	ROOT
21	out	out	RP	O	20	compound:prt
22	by	by	IN	O	23	case
23	diseases	disease	NNS	O	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	Mentions	mention	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	at	at	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	end	end	NN	O	2	nmod
6	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
7	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	12	nsubj
8	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
9	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
10	all	all	DT	O	12	advmod
11	around	around	IN	O	10	case
12	terrible	terrible	JJ	O	2	ccomp
13	because	because	IN	O	16	mark
14	we	we	PRP	O	16	nsubj
15	can	can	MD	O	16	aux
16	feed	feed	VB	O	12	ccomp
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	world	world	NN	O	16	dobj
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	hungry	hungry	JJ	O	18	amod
21	with	with	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	amount	amount	NN	O	16	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	25	case
25	food	food	NN	O	23	nmod
26	that	that	WDT	O	29	nsubjpass
27	can	can	MD	O	29	aux
28	be	be	VB	O	29	auxpass
29	produced	produce	VBN	O	23	acl:relcl
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	source	source	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	credible	credible	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	because	because	IN	O	10	mark
6	Round	Round	NNP	O	10	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	graduate	graduate	JJ	O	10	amod
10	student	student	NN	O	4	advcl
11	pursuing	pursue	VBG	O	10	acl
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	masters	master	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	environmental	environmental	JJ	O	16	amod
16	science	science	NN	O	11	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	political	political	JJ	O	19	amod
19	affairs	affair	NNS	O	16	conj
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Though	though	IN	O	6	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	article	article	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	does	do	VBZ	O	6	aux
5	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
6	mention	mention	VB	O	14	csubjpass
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	labeling	labeling	NN	O	9	compound
9	issue	issue	NN	O	6	dobj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	14	aux
11	can	can	MD	O	14	aux
12	still	still	RB	O	14	advmod
13	be	be	VB	O	14	auxpass
14	used	use	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	for	for	IN	O	16	case
16	facts	fact	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	examples	example	NNS	O	16	conj
19	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Reflection	reflection	NN	O	2	compound
2	Essay	essay	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	I	I	PRP	O	2	dep
4	knew	know	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	little	little	JJ	O	4	dobj
7	about	about	IN	O	9	case
8	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	foods	food	NNS	O	4	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
11	wanted	want	VBD	O	4	conj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	learn	learn	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	more	more	RBR	O	13	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	4	punct
16	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
17	some	some	DT	O	18	det
18	people	people	NNS	O	21	nsubjpass
19	are	be	VBP	O	21	auxpass
20	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
21	informed	inform	VBN	O	4	conj
22	about	about	IN	O	23	case
23	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	21	nmod
24	at	at	IN	O	25	case
25	all	all	DT	O	23	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	4	aux
3	n't	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	realize	realize	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
6	many	many	JJ	O	14	nsubjpass
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	foods	food	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	they	they	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	ingest	ingest	VBP	O	9	acl:relcl
12	are	be	VBP	O	14	auxpass
13	genetically	genetically	RB	O	14	advmod
14	modified	modify	VBN	O	4	ccomp
15	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	So	so	RB	O	8	advmod
2	with	with	IN	O	6	mark
3	what	what	WP	O	6	dobj
4	little	little	RB	O	5	advmod
5	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	knew	know	VBD	O	1	advcl
7	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	thought	think	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
10	it	it	PRP	O	13	nsubj
11	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
12	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
13	good	good	JJ	O	8	ccomp
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	find	find	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	out	out	RP	O	15	compound:prt
17	more	more	RBR	O	15	advmod
18	on	on	IN	O	20	case
19	this	this	DT	O	20	det
20	topic	topic	NN	O	15	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	held	hold	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	belief	belief	NN	O	2	dobj
5	that	that	WDT	O	9	dobj
6	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	foods	food	NNS	O	9	nsubj
8	are	be	VBP	O	9	cop
9	bad	bad	JJ	O	4	acl:relcl
10	for	for	IN	O	12	case
11	your	you	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	health	health	NN	O	9	nmod
13	because	because	IN	O	23	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	DNA	dna	NN	MISC	23	nsubj
16	in	in	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	pure	pure	JJ	O	19	amod
19	crop	crop	NN	O	15	nmod
20	is	be	VBZ	O	23	cop
21	naturally	naturally	RB	O	23	advmod
22	that	that	DT	O	23	det
23	way	way	NN	O	9	advcl
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	people	people	NNS	O	6	nsubj
4	have	have	VBP	O	6	aux
5	been	be	VBN	O	6	aux
6	eating	eat	VBG	O	0	ROOT
7	non-GMO	non-gmo	JJ	O	8	amod
8	foods	food	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	for	for	IN	O	10	case
10	centuries	century	NNS	DURATION	8	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	So	so	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	formulated	formulate	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	my	my	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
6	research	research	NN	O	7	compound
7	question	question	NN	O	4	dobj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	be	be	VB	O	4	advcl
10	:	:	:	O	4	punct
11	are	be	VBP	O	14	cop
12	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	foods	food	NNS	O	14	nsubj
14	good	good	JJ	O	4	parataxis
15	for	for	IN	O	17	case
16	your	you	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	health	health	NN	O	14	nmod
18	?	?	.	O	4	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	because	because	IN	O	4	case
4	there	there	EX	O	5	nmod
5	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
7	definitive	definitive	JJ	O	8	amod
8	evidence	evidence	NN	O	5	dep
9	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
10	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
11	foods	food	NNS	O	12	nsubj
12	diminish	diminish	VBP	O	5	ccomp
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	person	person	NN	O	16	nmod:poss
15	's	's	POS	O	14	case
16	health	health	NN	O	5	nsubj
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	changed	change	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	my	my	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	question	question	NN	O	2	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	2	nmod
6	:	:	:	O	2	punct
7	What	what	WP	O	10	nsubj
8	are	be	VBP	O	10	cop
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	arguments	argument	NNS	O	2	dep
11	made	make	VBN	O	10	acl
12	for	for	IN	O	16	case
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	against	against	IN	O	12	conj
15	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
16	food	food	NN	O	11	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
18	what	what	WP	O	20	dobj
19	evidence	evidence	NN	O	20	nsubj
20	is	be	VBZ	O	10	conj
21	there	there	RB	O	20	advmod
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	support	support	VB	O	20	xcomp
24	either	either	DT	O	25	det
25	side	side	NN	O	23	dobj
26	?	?	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	question	question	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	opened	open	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	up	up	RP	O	3	compound:prt
5	several	several	JJ	O	7	amod
6	research	research	NN	O	7	compound
7	opportunities	opportunity	NNS	O	3	dobj
8	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	case
4	Google	Google	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
5	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	2	advmod
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	see	see	VB	O	2	xcomp
8	what	what	WP	O	11	dobj
9	I	I	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	could	could	MD	O	11	aux
11	find	find	VB	O	7	ccomp
12	on	on	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	topic/issue	topic/issue	NN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	2	mark
2	finding	find	VBG	O	6	advcl
3	several	several	JJ	O	4	amod
4	articles	article	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	moved	move	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	on	on	IN	O	12	case
8	to	to	TO	O	12	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	library	library	NN	O	12	nmod:poss
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	website	website	NN	O	6	nmod
13	for	for	IN	O	14	case
14	databases	database	NNS	O	6	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	3	expl
2	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	found	find	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	two	two	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	articles	article	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	under	under	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	Biological	Biological	NNP	O	3	nmod
9	&	&	CC	O	8	cc
10	Agricultural	Agricultural	NNP	O	13	compound
11	Index	Index	NNP	O	13	compound
12	Plus	plus	NN	O	13	compound
13	database	database	NN	O	8	conj
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	det
2	two	two	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	articles	article	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	provided	provide	VBD	O	13	ccomp
5	me	I	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	with	with	IN	O	8	case
7	good	good	JJ	O	8	amod
8	information	information	NN	O	4	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	13	punct
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	only	only	JJ	O	12	amod
12	problem	problem	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
14	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
15	they	they	PRP	O	17	nsubjpass
16	are	be	VBP	O	17	auxpass
17	dated	date	VBN	O	13	ccomp
18	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	news	news	NN	O	3	compound
3	articles	article	NNS	O	9	nsubj
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	found	find	VBD	O	3	dep
7	are	be	VBP	O	9	cop
8	very	very	RB	O	9	advmod
9	recent	recent	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	are	be	VBP	O	19	auxpass
12	up	up	RB	O	19	advmod
13	to	to	TO	O	14	case
14	date	date	NN	O	12	nmod
15	on	on	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	new	new	JJ	O	18	amod
18	strides	stride	NNS	O	14	nmod
19	made	make	VBN	O	9	conj
20	by	by	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	government	government	NN	O	19	nmod
23	for	for	IN	O	25	case
24	stricter	stricter	JJR	O	25	amod
25	regulations	regulation	NNS	O	22	nmod
26	on	on	IN	O	27	case
27	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	25	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	used	use	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	references	reference	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	from	from	IN	O	7	case
6	other	other	JJ	O	7	amod
7	articles	article	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	find	find	VB	O	3	advcl
10	out	out	RP	O	9	compound:prt
11	more	more	JJR	O	12	amod
12	information	information	NN	O	9	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	expanded	expand	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	my	my	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	search	search	NN	O	2	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	find	find	VB	O	4	acl
7	out	out	RP	O	6	compound:prt
8	about	about	IN	O	9	case
9	companies	company	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
11	create	create	VBP	O	9	acl:relcl
12	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	seeds	seed	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
15	sell	sell	VB	O	6	conj
16	them	they	PRP	O	15	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	farmers	farmer	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	later	later	RB	O	3	advmod
3	found	find	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	documentary	documentary	NN	O	3	dobj
6	named	name	VBN	O	5	acl
7	Food	Food	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	Inc.	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	dobj
9	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
10	added	add	VBD	O	3	conj
11	it	it	PRP	O	10	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	my	my	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	sources	source	NNS	O	10	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	opened	open	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	my	my	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	eyes	eye	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	6	case
6	a	a	DT	O	2	nmod
7	who	who	WP	O	9	dep
8	new	new	JJ	O	9	amod
9	world	world	NN	O	6	acl:relcl
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	food	food	NN	O	13	compound
13	industry	industry	NN	O	9	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	companies	company	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	intentionally	intentionally	RB	O	4	advmod
4	leave	leave	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	consumers	consumer	NNS	O	4	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	dark	dark	NN	O	5	nmod
9	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	companies	company	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	so	so	RB	O	5	advmod
5	much	much	JJ	O	6	amod
6	power	power	NN	O	3	dobj
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	government	government	NN	O	3	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	support	support	NN	O	13	compound
12	government	government	NN	O	13	compound
13	leaders	leader	NNS	O	9	conj
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	turned	turn	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	tables	table	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	on	on	IN	O	7	mark
6	just	just	RB	O	7	advmod
7	focusing	focus	VBG	O	2	advcl
8	on	on	IN	O	10	case
9	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	foods	food	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	expanding	expand	VBG	O	7	advcl
13	to	to	TO	O	18	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	food	food	NN	O	16	compound
16	company	company	NN	O	18	nmod:poss
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	role	role	NN	O	12	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	government	government	NN	O	12	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	learned	learn	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	more	more	RBR	O	2	advmod
4	about	about	IN	O	5	case
5	Monsanto	Monsanto	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	chemical	chemical	NN	O	9	compound
9	company	company	NN	O	5	appos
10	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
11	introduced	introduce	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
12	the	the	DT	O	15	det
13	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	15	amod
14	GMO	GMO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
15	soybean	soybean	NN	O	11	dobj
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Food	Food	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Inc.	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
3	introduced	introduce	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	more	more	RBR	O	3	advmod
5	about	about	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	topic	topic	NN	O	3	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	7	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	labeling	labeling	NN	O	13	compound
13	effort	effort	NN	O	9	conj
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	shaped	shaped	JJ	O	1	amod
3	my	my	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	argument	argument	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	further	further	RB	O	4	advmod
6	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
7	strengthened	strengthen	VBD	O	4	conj
8	my	my	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	beliefs	belief	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	on	on	IN	O	12	case
11	this	this	DT	O	12	det
12	topic	topic	NN	O	7	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	issue	issue	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	been	be	VBN	O	5	aux
5	developing	develop	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	for	for	IN	O	7	case
7	years	year	NNS	DURATION	5	nmod
8	because	because	IN	O	10	mark
9	there	there	EX	O	10	expl
10	is	be	VBZ	O	5	advcl
11	still	still	RB	O	10	advmod
12	no	no	DT	O	13	neg
13	evidence	evidence	NN	O	10	nsubj
14	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
15	GMOs	gmo	NNS	LOCATION	17	nsubj
16	are	be	VBP	O	17	cop
17	safe	safe	JJ	O	10	ccomp
18	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	topic	topic	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	still	still	RB	O	6	advmod
5	too	too	RB	O	6	advmod
6	young	young	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	8	case
8	anyone	anyone	NN	O	6	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	have	have	VB	O	6	xcomp
11	proof	proof	NN	O	10	dobj
12	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
13	these	these	DT	O	14	det
14	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	17	nsubj
15	are	be	VBP	O	17	cop
16	either	either	RB	O	17	advmod
17	good	good	JJ	O	10	ccomp
18	or	or	CC	O	17	cc
19	bad	bad	JJ	O	17	conj
20	for	for	IN	O	22	case
21	human	human	JJ	O	22	amod
22	health	health	NN	O	17	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	My	my	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	research	research	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	informed	inform	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	me	I	PRP	O	3	dobj
5	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
6	GMOs	gmo	NNS	LOCATION	8	nsubj
7	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
8	recent	recent	JJ	O	3	ccomp
9	;	;	:	O	3	punct
10	they	they	PRP	O	13	nsubjpass
11	were	be	VBD	O	13	auxpass
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	developed	develop	VBN	O	3	parataxis
14	until	until	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	DATE	17	det
16	early	early	JJ	DATE	17	amod
17	1990s	1990s	CD	DATE	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	why	why	WRB	O	5	advmod
4	there	there	EX	O	5	expl
5	is	be	VBZ	O	2	advcl
6	still	still	RB	O	5	advmod
7	so	so	RB	O	8	advmod
8	much	much	JJ	O	5	xcomp
9	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
10	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
11	unknown	unknown	JJ	O	5	ccomp
12	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	still	still	RB	O	3	advmod
3	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	same	same	JJ	O	6	amod
6	position	position	NN	O	3	dobj
7	as	as	IN	O	9	mark
8	I	I	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	did	do	VBD	O	6	acl:relcl
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	beginning	beginning	NN	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	3	punct
14	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
15	I	I	PRP	O	17	nsubj
16	am	be	VBP	O	17	cop
17	glad	glad	JJ	O	3	conj
18	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
19	I	I	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	chose	choose	VBD	O	17	ccomp
21	this	this	DT	O	22	det
22	topic	topic	NN	O	20	dobj
23	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	opened	open	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	my	my	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	eyes	eye	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	arguments	argument	NNS	O	3	nmod
9	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubjpass
10	are	be	VBP	O	11	auxpass
11	made	make	VBN	O	8	acl:relcl
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	still	still	RB	O	2	advmod
4	so	so	RB	O	6	advmod
5	much	much	RB	O	6	advmod
6	more	more	JJR	O	2	xcomp
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	learn	learn	VB	O	2	dep
9	about	about	IN	O	10	case
10	GMOs	gmo	NNS	O	8	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
12	what	what	WP	O	17	dobj
13	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	17	nsubj
14	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
15	consequences	consequence	NNS	O	13	conj
16	can	can	MD	O	17	aux
17	come	come	VB	O	8	conj
18	from	from	IN	O	19	case
19	them	they	PRP	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	mark
2	time	time	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	goes	go	VBZ	O	9	csubjpass
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	more	more	JJR	O	6	amod
6	research	research	NN	O	3	nmod
7	will	will	MD	O	9	aux
8	be	be	VB	O	9	auxpass
9	done	do	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	obtain	obtain	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	proof	proof	NN	O	11	dobj
13	,	,	,	O	9	punct
14	but	but	CC	O	9	cc
15	for	for	IN	O	16	case
16	now	now	RB	DATE	19	nmod
17	we	we	PRP	O	19	nsubj
18	must	must	MD	O	19	aux
19	find	find	VB	O	9	conj
20	out	out	RP	O	19	compound:prt
21	what	what	WP	O	24	dobj
22	arguments	argument	NNS	O	24	nsubjpass
23	are	be	VBP	O	24	auxpass
24	made	make	VBN	O	19	ccomp
25	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
26	decide	decide	VB	O	19	conj
27	for	for	IN	O	28	case
28	ourselves	ourselves	PRP	O	26	nmod
29	if	if	IN	O	33	mark
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	33	nsubj
32	out	out	IN	O	33	advmod
33	weigh	weigh	VBP	O	26	advcl
34	the	the	DT	O	35	det
35	costs	cost	NNS	O	33	dobj
36	.	.	.	O	9	punct

