1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	revolutionized	revolutionize	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	fashion	fashion	NN	O	3	dobj
5	with	with	IN	O	8	case
6	her	she	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
7	bright	bright	JJ	O	8	amod
8	colors	color	NNS	O	3	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	bold	bold	JJ	O	11	amod
11	prints	print	NNS	O	8	conj
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	What	what	WDT	O	2	nsubj
2	started	start	VBD	O	13	csubj
3	out	out	RP	O	2	compound:prt
4	as	as	IN	O	12	mark
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	uniform	uniform	NN	O	12	nsubj
7	for	for	IN	O	11	case
8	her	she	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
9	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
10	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	juice	juice	NN	O	6	nmod
12	stand	stand	VB	O	2	advcl
13	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	well-known	well-known	JJ	O	16	amod
16	brand	brand	NN	O	13	xcomp
17	loved	love	VBN	O	16	acl
18	by	by	IN	O	19	case
19	many	many	JJ	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	5	compound
5	website	website	NN	O	7	nsubj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	celebrates	celebrate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	official	official	JJ	O	10	amod
10	establishment	establishment	NN	O	7	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	brand	brand	NN	O	10	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	1959	1959	CD	DATE	13	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	15	punct
17	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	15	appos
19	,	,	,	O	15	punct
20	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	15	appos
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	23	punct
22	Our	we	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	Story	Story	NNP	O	15	dep
24	:	:	:	O	23	punct
25	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	compound
26	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	dep
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	23	punct
28	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	foundation	foundation	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	occurred	occur	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	during	during	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	time	time	NN	O	3	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	drastic	drastic	JJ	O	10	amod
10	transformation	transformation	NN	O	6	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	fashion	fashion	NN	O	14	compound
14	industry	industry	NN	O	3	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Paul	Paul	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	PERSON	19	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	author	author	NN	O	2	appos
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	article	article	NN	O	4	nmod
8	``	``	``	O	7	punct
9	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	10	nummod
10	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	7	dep
11	for	for	IN	O	12	case
12	Women	Women	NNP	O	10	nmod
13	&	&	CC	O	12	cc
14	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	12	conj
15	''	''	''	O	7	punct
16	on	on	IN	O	17	case
17	RetroWaste.com	RetroWaste.com	NNP	O	4	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	2	punct
19	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
20	how	how	WRB	O	25	advmod
21	women	woman	NNS	O	23	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	fashion	fashion	NN	O	25	nsubj
24	was	be	VBD	O	25	aux
25	changing	change	VBG	O	19	ccomp
26	drastically	drastically	RB	O	25	advmod
27	during	during	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	1960	1960	CD	DATE	25	nmod
30	's	's	POS	O	29	case
31	from	from	IN	O	32	case
32	feminine	feminine	JJ	O	29	nmod
33	and	and	CC	O	32	cc
34	dressy	dressy	JJ	O	32	conj
35	to	to	TO	O	36	case
36	casual	casual	JJ	O	29	acl
37	and	and	CC	O	36	cc
38	boxy	boxy	JJ	O	36	conj
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	36	dep
41	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct
42	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	3	nsubj
3	debuted	debut	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	her	she	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	line	line	NN	O	3	dobj
6	during	during	IN	O	9	case
7	this	this	DT	O	9	det
8	time	time	NN	O	9	compound
9	period	period	NN	O	3	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
11	was	be	VBD	O	13	auxpass
12	significantly	significantly	RB	O	13	advmod
13	influenced	influence	VBN	O	3	conj
14	by	by	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	changing	change	VBG	O	17	amod
17	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	13	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	time	time	NN	O	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	2	neg
2	only	only	RB	O	5	cc:preconj
3	did	do	VBD	O	5	aux
4	she	she	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	pick	pick	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	up	up	RP	O	5	compound:prt
7	on	on	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	changing	change	VBG	O	10	amod
10	styles	style	NNS	O	5	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	5	punct
12	but	but	CC	O	5	cc
13	she	she	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	also	also	RB	O	15	advmod
15	contributed	contribute	VBD	O	5	conj
16	to	to	TO	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	changing	change	VBG	O	19	amod
19	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	15	nmod
20	of	of	IN	O	21	case
21	the	the	DT	O	19	nmod
22	1960	1960	CD	DATE	21	nmod:poss
23	's	's	POS	O	22	case
24	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
3	created	create	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	7	det
5	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	7	compound
6	brand	brand	NN	O	7	compound
7	name	name	NN	O	3	dobj
8	for	for	IN	O	9	case
9	herself	herself	PRP	O	3	nmod
10	by	by	IN	O	11	mark
11	recreating	recreate	VBG	O	3	advcl
12	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	11	xcomp
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	positively	positively	RB	O	5	advmod
5	affected	affect	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	women	woman	NNS	O	5	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	men	man	NNS	O	6	conj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	fashion	fashion	NN	O	13	compound
13	industry	industry	NN	O	6	conj
14	from	from	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	1959	1959	CD	DATE	5	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	today	today	NN	DATE	5	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	effected	effect	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	continues	continue	VBZ	O	6	conj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	effect	effect	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	women	woman	NNS	O	10	dobj
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	men	man	NNS	O	11	conj
14	,	,	,	O	11	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	fashion	fashion	NN	O	18	compound
18	industry	industry	NN	O	11	conj
19	today	today	NN	DATE	10	nmod:tmod
20	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	style	style	NN	O	13	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	clothing	clothing	NN	O	2	nmod
5	the	the	DT	O	8	det
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	brand	brand	NN	O	9	nsubj
9	produces	produce	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
10	is	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	main	main	JJ	O	13	amod
13	contribution	contribution	NN	O	0	ROOT
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	label	label	NN	O	13	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	brand	brand	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	auxpass
4	known	know	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	for	for	IN	O	10	case
6	its	its	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
7	``	``	``	O	10	punct
8	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	10	amod
9	''	''	''	O	10	punct
10	look	look	NN	O	4	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	clean-cut	clean-cut	JJ	O	13	amod
13	look	look	NN	O	10	conj
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	3	det
2	major	major	JJ	O	3	amod
3	contribution	contribution	NN	O	9	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	brand	brand	NN	O	3	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	market	market	NN	O	0	ROOT
10	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	targets	target	VBZ	O	9	acl:relcl
12	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	aims	aim	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	create	create	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	clothing	clothing	NN	O	10	compound
10	line	line	NN	O	7	dobj
11	that	that	WDT	O	13	nsubj
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
13	appropriate	appropriate	JJ	O	10	acl:relcl
14	for	for	IN	O	16	case
15	all	all	DT	O	16	det
16	ages	age	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	13	punct
18	with	with	IN	O	20	case
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	focus	focus	NN	O	13	nmod
21	on	on	IN	O	24	case
22	an	a	DT	O	24	det
23	exclusive	exclusive	JJ	O	24	amod
24	group	group	NN	O	20	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	customers	customer	NNS	O	24	nmod
27	that	that	WDT	O	28	nsubj
28	live	live	VBP	O	26	acl:relcl
29	in	in	IN	O	28	nmod
30	or	or	CC	O	7	cc
31	travel	travel	VB	O	7	conj
32	to	to	TO	O	36	case
33	warm	warm	JJ	O	36	amod
34	,	,	,	O	36	punct
35	tropical	tropical	JJ	O	36	amod
36	locations	location	NNS	O	31	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	10	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	10	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	7	det
5	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
6	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	brand	brand	NN	O	10	nsubjpass
8	is	be	VBZ	O	10	auxpass
9	mostly	mostly	RB	O	10	advmod
10	recognized	recognize	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	for	for	IN	O	16	case
12	its	its	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
13	colorful	colorful	JJ	O	16	amod
14	,	,	,	O	16	punct
15	bold	bold	JJ	O	16	amod
16	prints	print	NNS	O	10	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	16	conj
19	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	designs	design	NNS	O	6	nsubj
3	on	on	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	fabric	fabric	NN	O	2	nmod
6	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
7	what	what	WP	O	8	nsubj
8	set	set	VBD	O	6	ccomp
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	brand	brand	NN	O	8	dobj
13	apart	apart	RB	O	8	advmod
14	from	from	IN	O	18	case
15	other	other	JJ	O	16	amod
16	designer	designer	NN	O	18	nmod:poss
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	labels	label	NNS	O	8	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	William	William	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Norwich	Norwich	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	author	author	NN	O	2	appos
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	article	article	NN	O	5	nmod
9	``	``	``	O	8	punct
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	13	nmod:poss
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	Uniforms	Uniforms	NNPS	O	8	dep
14	for	for	IN	O	17	case
15	an	a	DT	O	17	det
16	Entire	Entire	NNP	O	17	compound
17	Class	Class	NNP	O	13	nmod
18	''	''	''	O	8	punct
19	for	for	IN	O	23	case
20	the	the	DT	O	23	det
21	New	New	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
22	York	York	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
23	Times	Times	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	2	punct
25	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
26	how	how	WRB	O	30	advmod
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	MISC	29	compound
29	brand	brand	NN	O	30	nsubj
30	brought	bring	VBD	O	25	ccomp
31	a	a	DT	O	33	det
32	new	new	JJ	O	33	amod
33	look	look	NN	O	30	dobj
34	to	to	TO	O	36	case
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	1960	1960	CD	DATE	30	nmod
37	's	's	POS	O	36	case
38	and	and	CC	O	36	cc
39	1970	1970	CD	DATE	36	conj
40	's	's	POS	O	39	case
41	by	by	IN	O	42	mark
42	introducing	introduce	VBG	O	30	advcl
43	the	the	DT	O	45	det
44	shift	shift	NN	O	45	compound
45	dress	dress	NN	O	42	dobj
46	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	47	punct
47	Norwich	Norwich	NNP	LOCATION	45	appos
48	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	47	punct
49	.	.	.	O	25	punct

1	Norwich	Norwich	NNP	LOCATION	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	comments	comment	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	12	advmod
5	,	,	,	O	12	punct
6	as	as	IN	O	8	case
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	result	result	NN	O	12	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	12	punct
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
12	created	create	VBD	O	3	ccomp
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	uniform	uniform	NN	O	12	dobj
15	for	for	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	people	people	NNS	O	12	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	vacationers	vacationer	NNS	O	17	conj
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	22	compound
22	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	17	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	22	appos
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
26	Norwich	Norwich	NNP	LOCATION	24	appos
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
28	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	many	many	JJ	O	8	amod
8	contributions	contribution	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	fashion	fashion	NN	O	12	compound
12	industry	industry	NN	O	8	nmod
13	since	since	IN	O	14	case
14	its	its	PRP$	O	12	nmod
15	'	'	''	O	8	punct
16	founding	founding	NN	O	8	dep
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	1959	1959	CD	DATE	16	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	8	punct
20	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
21	continues	continue	VBZ	O	6	conj
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	remain	remain	VB	O	21	xcomp
24	an	a	DT	O	26	det
25	important	important	JJ	O	26	amod
26	contribution	contribution	NN	O	23	xcomp
27	to	to	TO	O	30	case
28	the	the	DT	O	30	det
29	fashion	fashion	NN	O	30	compound
30	industry	industry	NN	O	23	nmod
31	today	today	NN	DATE	23	nmod:tmod
32	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Trends	trend	NNS	O	4	nsubj
2	in	in	IN	O	3	case
3	fashion	fashion	NN	O	1	nmod
4	changed	change	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	drastically	drastically	RB	O	4	advmod
6	during	during	IN	O	7	case
7	the	the	DT	O	4	nmod
8	1960	1960	CD	DATE	7	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Paul	Paul	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	author	author	NN	O	2	appos
5	of	of	IN	O	10	case
6	the	the	DT	O	10	det
7	article	article	NN	O	10	dep
8	``	``	``	O	10	punct
9	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	10	nummod
10	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	4	nmod
11	for	for	IN	O	12	case
12	Women	Women	NNP	O	10	nmod
13	&	&	CC	O	12	cc
14	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	12	conj
15	,	,	,	O	10	punct
16	''	''	''	O	10	punct
17	states	state	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	that	that	DT	O	17	advmod
19	up	up	IN	O	18	case
20	until	until	IN	O	23	mark
21	1965	1965	CD	DATE	22	nummod
22	fashion	fashion	NN	O	23	nsubj
23	remained	remain	VBD	O	17	advcl
24	stagnant	stagnant	JJ	O	23	xcomp
25	to	to	TO	O	27	case
26	those	those	DT	O	27	det
27	popular	popular	JJ	O	24	nmod
28	in	in	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	1950	1950	CD	DATE	23	nmod
31	's	's	POS	O	30	case
32	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	33	punct
33	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	appos
34	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	33	punct
35	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Women	woman	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	continued	continue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	wear	wear	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	6	amod
6	cuts	cut	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	combination	combination	NN	O	6	nmod
9	with	with	IN	O	13	case
10	a	a	DT	O	13	det
11	dull	dull	JJ	O	13	amod
12	color	color	NN	O	13	compound
13	palette	palette	NN	O	4	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	4	det
2	dull	dull	JJ	O	4	amod
3	color	color	NN	O	4	compound
4	palette	palette	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	consists	consist	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	mostly	mostly	RB	O	5	advmod
7	of	of	IN	O	11	case
8	pale	pale	JJ	O	11	amod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	neutral	neutral	JJ	O	8	conj
11	colors	color	NNS	O	5	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	5	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
14	bright	bright	JJ	O	17	amod
15	,	,	,	O	17	punct
16	vibrant	vibrant	JJ	O	17	amod
17	colors	color	NNS	O	21	nsubjpass
18	were	be	VBD	O	21	auxpass
19	typically	typically	RB	O	21	advmod
20	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
21	used	use	VBN	O	5	conj
22	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	9	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	9	punct
4	women	woman	NNS	O	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	clothing	clothing	NN	O	9	nsubj
7	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
8	very	very	RB	O	9	advmod
9	feminine	feminine	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	body	body	NN	O	12	nmod:npmod
12	conscious	conscious	JJ	O	9	conj
13	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Traditionally	traditionally	RB	O	7	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	feminine	feminine	JJ	O	4	amod
4	clothing	clothing	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	combination	combination	NN	O	0	ROOT
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	dresses	dress	NNS	O	7	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	skirts	skirt	VBZ	O	9	dep
12	,	,	,	O	9	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
14	blouses	blouse	NNS	O	7	conj
15	that	that	WDT	O	14	acl:relcl
16	hug	hug	NN	O	14	dep
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	woman	woman	NN	O	20	nmod:poss
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	figure	figure	NN	O	16	dep
21	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	kind	kind	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	clothing	clothing	NN	O	2	nmod
5	accentuates	accentuate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	female	female	NN	O	9	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	body	body	NN	O	5	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	showing	show	VBG	O	9	acl
12	off	off	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	curves	curve	NNS	O	11	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	Victoria	Victoria	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	Albert	Albert	NNP	PERSON	2	conj
5	Museum	Museum	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	published	publish	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	an	a	DT	O	8	det
8	article	article	NN	O	6	dobj
9	titled	title	VBN	O	8	acl
10	``	``	``	O	11	punct
11	History	history	NN	O	9	xcomp
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	14	nummod
14	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	11	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	14	conj
17	,	,	,	O	11	punct
18	''	''	''	O	11	punct
19	which	which	WDT	O	20	nsubj
20	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	8	acl:relcl
21	how	how	WRB	O	34	advmod
22	because	because	IN	O	27	case
23	of	of	IN	O	27	case
24	these	these	DT	O	27	det
25	specific	specific	JJ	O	27	amod
26	fashion	fashion	NN	O	27	compound
27	characteristics	characteristic	NNS	O	34	nmod
28	,	,	,	O	34	punct
29	the	the	DT	O	31	det
30	typical	typical	JJ	O	31	amod
31	attire	attire	NN	O	34	nsubj
32	for	for	IN	O	33	case
33	women	woman	NNS	O	31	nmod
34	consisted	consist	VBD	O	20	ccomp
35	of	of	IN	O	36	case
36	dresses	dress	NNS	O	34	nmod
37	with	with	IN	O	38	mark
38	accentuated	accentuate	VBN	O	34	advcl
39	busts	bust	NNS	O	38	dobj
40	and	and	CC	O	34	cc
41	pulled	pull	VBD	O	34	conj
42	in	in	IN	O	43	case
43	waistlines	waistline	NNS	O	41	nmod
44	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	45	punct
45	History	history	NN	O	43	dep
46	of	of	IN	O	48	case
47	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	48	nummod
48	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	45	nmod
49	and	and	CC	O	48	cc
50	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	48	conj
51	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	45	punct
52	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	type	type	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	clothing	clothing	NN	O	2	nmod
5	was	be	VBD	O	6	auxpass
6	meant	mean	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	show	show	VB	O	6	xcomp
9	off	off	RP	O	8	compound:prt
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	woman	woman	NN	O	13	nmod:poss
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	body	body	NN	O	8	dobj
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	make	make	VB	O	13	acl
16	her	she	PRP$	O	17	nsubj
17	appear	appear	VBP	O	15	ccomp
18	feminine	feminine	JJ	O	17	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	15	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	15	punct
3	as	as	IN	O	4	mark
4	discussed	discuss	VBN	O	15	advcl
5	by	by	IN	O	7	case
6	Paul	Paul	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	15	punct
9	this	this	DT	O	13	det
10	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	13	amod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	traditional	traditional	JJ	O	10	conj
13	attire	attire	NN	O	15	nsubj
14	quickly	quickly	RB	O	15	advmod
15	vanished	vanish	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	during	during	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	mid	mid	JJ	O	15	nmod
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	late	late	JJ	DATE	21	amod
21	1960	1960	CD	DATE	18	conj
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	appos
25	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
26	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Paul	Paul	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	goes	go	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	discuss	discuss	VB	O	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	how	how	WRB	O	15	advmod
9	the	the	DT	DATE	11	det
10	late	late	JJ	DATE	11	amod
11	1960	1960	CD	DATE	8	dep
12	's	's	POS	O	15	nsubj
13	were	be	VBD	O	15	cop
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	time	time	NN	O	6	dep
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	wild	wild	JJ	O	18	amod
18	colors	color	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	bold	bold	JJ	O	21	amod
21	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	18	appos
22	,	,	,	O	18	punct
23	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
24	shortened	shorten	VBD	O	3	conj
25	hemlines	hemline	NNS	O	24	dobj
26	for	for	IN	O	29	case
27	women	woman	NNS	O	29	nmod:poss
28	's	's	POS	O	27	case
29	fashion	fashion	NN	O	24	nmod
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	appos
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
33	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	9	nmod
3	to	to	TO	O	6	case
4	these	these	DT	O	6	det
5	drastic	drastic	JJ	O	6	amod
6	characteristics	characteristic	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	9	punct
8	fashion	fashion	NN	O	9	nsubj
9	strayed	stray	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	away	away	RB	O	9	compound:prt
11	from	from	IN	O	12	case
12	feminine	feminine	JJ	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	body	body	NN	O	12	appos
15	hugging	hug	VBG	O	9	xcomp
16	attire	attire	NN	O	15	dobj
17	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
18	shifted	shift	VBD	O	9	conj
19	to	to	TO	O	21	case
20	boxier	boxier	JJR	O	21	amod
21	cuts	cut	NNS	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	discussed	discuss	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	10	advmod
5	these	these	DT	O	7	det
6	new	new	JJ	O	7	amod
7	cuts	cut	NNS	O	10	nsubj
8	not	not	RB	O	9	dep
9	only	only	RB	O	10	advmod
10	showed	show	VBD	O	3	ccomp
11	up	up	RP	O	10	compound:prt
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	form	form	NN	O	10	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	baggy	baggy	JJ	O	17	amod
17	tunics	tunic	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	10	punct
19	but	but	CC	O	10	cc
20	also	also	RB	O	23	advmod
21	in	in	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	form	form	NN	O	10	conj
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	manly	manly	JJ	O	26	amod
26	pantsuits	pantsuit	NNS	O	23	nmod
27	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	28	punct
28	Phipps	Phipps	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	appos
29	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	28	punct
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	revolutions	revolution	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	shocked	shock	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	those	those	DT	O	6	nsubj
6	accustomed	accustom	VBN	O	4	ccomp
7	to	to	TO	O	6	xcomp
8	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
9	comfortable	comfortable	JJ	O	6	conj
10	with	with	IN	O	16	case
11	the	the	DT	O	16	det
12	old	old	JJ	O	16	amod
13	,	,	,	O	16	punct
14	more	more	RBR	O	15	advmod
15	traditional	traditional	JJ	O	16	amod
16	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	9	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	10	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	10	punct
3	it	it	PRP	O	10	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	10	auxpass
5	not	not	RB	O	10	neg
6	long	long	RB	O	10	advmod
7	before	before	IN	O	9	case
8	these	these	DT	O	9	det
9	trends	trend	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	caught	catch	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	on	on	IN	O	10	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	fashion	fashion	NN	O	15	dep
15	keen	keen	JJ	O	10	conj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	1960	1960	CD	DATE	15	nmod
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	adopted	adopt	VBN	O	18	acl
21	these	these	DT	O	22	det
22	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	20	dobj
23	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Radical	Radical	NNP	O	2	compound
2	change	change	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	fashion	fashion	NN	O	2	nmod
5	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	about	about	IN	O	10	case
7	through	through	IN	O	10	case
8	two	two	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
9	particular	particular	JJ	O	10	amod
10	parties	party	NNS	O	5	nmod
11	:	:	:	O	10	punct
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	youth	youth	NN	O	10	dep
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	1960	1960	CD	DATE	13	nmod
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
19	designers	designer	NNS	O	16	conj
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	published	publish	VBN	O	2	acl
4	by	by	IN	O	9	case
5	the	the	DT	O	9	det
6	Victoria	Victoria	NNP	O	9	compound
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	Albert	Albert	NNP	PERSON	6	conj
9	Museum	Museum	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod
10	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
11	how	how	WRB	O	18	advmod
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	youth	youth	NN	O	11	dep
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	1960	1960	CD	DATE	13	nmod
17	's	's	POS	O	18	nsubj
18	decided	decide	VBD	O	10	ccomp
19	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
20	they	they	PRP	O	21	nsubj
21	wanted	want	VBD	O	18	ccomp
22	their	they	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	ideas	idea	NNS	O	21	dobj
24	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
25	be	be	VB	O	26	auxpass
26	voiced	voice	VBN	O	21	advcl
27	,	,	,	O	21	punct
28	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
29	that	that	IN	O	33	mark
30	they	they	PRP	O	33	nsubj
31	did	do	VBD	O	33	aux
32	not	not	RB	O	33	neg
33	agree	agree	VB	O	21	conj
34	with	with	IN	O	37	case
35	the	the	DT	O	37	det
36	previous	previous	JJ	O	37	amod
37	notion	notion	NN	O	33	nmod
38	of	of	IN	O	40	case
39	the	the	DT	O	40	det
40	time	time	NN	O	37	nmod
41	that	that	WDT	O	47	dobj
42	fashion	fashion	NN	O	47	nsubj
43	was	be	VBD	O	47	cop
44	only	only	RB	O	47	advmod
45	for	for	IN	O	47	case
46	the	the	DT	O	47	det
47	wealthy	wealthy	JJ	O	40	acl:relcl
48	and	and	CC	O	47	cc
49	elite	elite	NN	O	47	conj
50	of	of	IN	O	51	case
51	society	society	NN	O	49	nmod
52	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	53	punct
53	History	history	NN	O	40	dep
54	of	of	IN	O	56	case
55	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	56	nummod
56	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	53	nmod
57	and	and	CC	O	56	cc
58	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	56	conj
59	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	53	punct
60	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	they	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	inspired	inspire	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	push	push	NN	O	7	nmod:npmod
7	away	away	RB	O	4	advmod
8	from	from	IN	O	15	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	elites	elite	NNS	O	15	nmod:poss
11	'	'	POS	O	10	case
12	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	15	amod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	traditional	traditional	JJ	O	12	conj
15	ways	way	NNS	O	4	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	3	amod
3	party	party	NN	O	14	nsubj
4	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	effected	effect	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	change	change	NN	O	5	dobj
8	in	in	IN	O	11	case
9	1960	1960	CD	DATE	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	fashion	fashion	NN	O	5	nmod
12	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	designers	designer	NNS	O	0	ROOT
15	in	in	IN	O	16	case
16	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	designers	designer	NNS	O	4	nsubjpass
3	were	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	inspired	inspire	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	by	by	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	pop	pop	NN	O	8	compound
8	culture	culture	NN	O	4	nmod
9	occurring	occur	VBG	O	8	acl
10	around	around	IN	O	11	case
11	them	they	PRP	O	9	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	published	publish	VBN	O	2	acl
4	by	by	IN	O	9	case
5	the	the	DT	O	9	det
6	Victoria	Victoria	NNP	LOCATION	9	compound
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	Albert	Albert	NNP	PERSON	6	conj
9	Museum	Museum	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod
10	also	also	RB	O	11	advmod
11	comments	comment	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	on	on	IN	O	27	mark
13	how	how	WRB	O	27	advmod
14	one	one	CD	NUMBER	27	nsubj
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	major	major	JJ	O	18	amod
18	influences	influence	NNS	O	14	nmod
19	on	on	IN	O	23	case
20	British	british	JJ	MISC	21	amod
21	designer	designer	NN	O	23	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	clothing	clothing	NN	O	18	nmod
24	was	be	VBD	O	27	cop
25	the	the	DT	O	27	det
26	mod	mod	NN	O	27	compound
27	look	look	NN	O	11	advcl
28	,	,	,	O	27	punct
29	a	a	DT	O	30	det
30	look	look	NN	O	27	appos
31	consisting	consist	VBG	O	30	acl
32	of	of	IN	O	35	case
33	bold	bold	JJ	O	35	amod
34	geometric	geometric	JJ	O	35	amod
35	shapes	shape	NNS	O	31	nmod
36	and	and	CC	O	35	cc
37	designs	design	NNS	O	35	conj
38	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	39	punct
39	History	history	NN	O	35	dep
40	of	of	IN	O	42	case
41	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	42	nummod
42	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	39	nmod
43	and	and	CC	O	42	cc
44	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	42	conj
45	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	39	punct
46	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	3	compound
2	fashion	fashion	NN	O	3	compound
3	designers	designer	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	incorporated	incorporate	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	these	these	DT	O	9	det
6	bright	bright	JJ	O	9	amod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	bold	bold	JJ	O	6	conj
9	colors	color	NNS	O	4	dobj
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	shapes	shape	NNS	O	9	conj
12	with	with	IN	O	14	case
13	boxy	boxy	JJ	O	14	amod
14	cuts	cut	NNS	O	4	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	shorter	shorter	JJR	O	17	amod
17	hemlines	hemline	NNS	O	14	conj
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	article	article	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	concludes	conclude	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
5	soon	soon	RB	O	9	advmod
6	after	after	IN	O	9	mark
7	these	these	DT	O	8	det
8	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	became	become	VBD	O	15	advcl
10	popular	popular	JJ	O	9	xcomp
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	they	they	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	migrated	migrate	VBD	O	3	ccomp
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	inspired	inspire	VBD	O	15	conj
18	designers	designer	NNS	O	17	dobj
19	in	in	IN	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	22	compound
22	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	17	nmod
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	History	history	NN	O	17	dep
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	27	nummod
27	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	24	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
29	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	27	conj
30	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
31	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	15	nsubj
2	did	do	VBD	O	1	acl:relcl
3	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
4	only	only	JJ	O	5	amod
5	change	change	NN	O	2	dobj
6	for	for	IN	O	7	case
7	women	woman	NNS	O	2	nmod
8	during	during	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	1960	1960	CD	DATE	2	nmod
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	,	,	,	O	10	punct
13	it	it	PRP	O	10	appos
14	also	also	RB	O	15	advmod
15	changed	change	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	dramatically	dramatically	RB	O	15	advmod
17	for	for	IN	O	18	case
18	men	man	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Victoria	Victoria	NNP	LOCATION	8	nsubj
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	Albert	Albert	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
5	Museum	Museum	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	article	article	NN	O	2	conj
7	also	also	RB	O	2	advmod
8	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	how	how	WRB	O	19	advmod
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	``	``	``	O	13	punct
12	Peacock	Peacock	NNP	O	13	compound
13	Revolution	Revolution	NNP	O	19	nsubj
14	''	''	''	O	13	punct
15	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
16	a	a	DT	O	19	det
17	major	major	JJ	O	19	amod
18	turning	turning	NN	O	19	compound
19	point	point	NN	O	8	ccomp
20	in	in	IN	O	23	case
21	men	man	NNS	O	23	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	fashion	fashion	NN	O	19	nmod
24	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
25	History	history	NN	O	23	dep
26	of	of	IN	O	28	case
27	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	28	nummod
28	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	25	nmod
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	28	conj
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
32	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	revolution	revolution	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	entailed	entail	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	designers	designer	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	adding	add	VBG	O	3	xcomp
6	color	color	NN	O	5	dobj
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	prints	print	NNS	O	6	conj
9	to	to	TO	O	12	case
10	men	man	NNS	O	12	nmod:poss
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	apparel	apparel	NN	O	5	nmod
13	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
14	History	history	NN	O	12	dep
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	17	nummod
17	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	14	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	17	conj
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Men	men	NN	O	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	shirts	shirt	NNS	O	9	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	pants	pants	NNS	O	3	appos
6	,	,	,	O	3	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
8	suits	suit	NNS	O	3	conj
9	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	embody	embody	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	color	color	NN	O	15	compound
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	bold	bold	JJ	O	12	conj
15	prints	print	NNS	O	11	dobj
16	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	change	change	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	6	case
4	men	man	NNS	O	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	clothing	clothing	NN	O	2	nmod
7	was	be	VBD	O	8	aux
8	groundbreaking	groundbreak	VBG	O	0	ROOT
9	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Prior	prior	RB	O	4	case
2	to	to	TO	O	1	mwe
3	this	this	DT	O	4	det
4	shift	shift	NN	O	9	nmod
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	style	style	NN	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	9	punct
8	men	man	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	worn	worn	JJ	O	12	amod
12	colors	color	NNS	O	9	dobj
13	other	other	JJ	O	15	case
14	than	than	IN	O	15	case
15	neutrals	neutral	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	19	case
17	over	over	IN	O	18	advmod
18	150	150	CD	DURATION	19	nummod
19	years	year	NNS	DURATION	15	nmod
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	History	history	NN	O	19	dep
22	of	of	IN	O	24	case
23	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	24	nummod
24	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	21	nmod
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	24	conj
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
28	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	introduced	introduce	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	her	she	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	men	man	NNS	O	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	line	line	NN	O	3	dobj
8	shortly	shortly	RB	O	3	advmod
9	after	after	IN	O	12	case
10	this	this	DT	O	12	det
11	fashion	fashion	NN	O	12	compound
12	revolution	revolution	NN	O	3	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	author	author	NN	O	26	nsubj
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	of	of	IN	O	10	case
5	the	the	DT	O	10	det
6	article	article	NN	O	10	compound
7	``	``	``	O	10	punct
8	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	MISC	10	compound
9	,	,	,	O	10	punct
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	26	punct
12	''	''	''	O	26	punct
13	published	publish	VBN	O	26	dep
14	on	on	IN	O	18	case
15	the	the	DT	O	18	det
16	Fashion	Fashion	NNP	MISC	18	compound
17	Encyclopedia	Encyclopedia	NNP	MISC	18	compound
18	website	website	NN	O	13	nmod
19	by	by	IN	O	21	case
20	Richard	Richard	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
21	Martin	Martin	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	Owen	Owen	NNP	PERSON	24	compound
24	James	James	NNP	PERSON	21	conj
25	,	,	,	O	26	punct
26	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	premier	premier	NN	O	39	nsubj
29	of	of	IN	O	36	case
30	the	the	DT	O	36	det
31	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	32	compound
32	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	nmod:poss
33	's	's	POS	O	32	case
34	men	man	NNS	O	36	nmod:poss
35	's	's	POS	O	34	case
36	line	line	NN	O	28	nmod
37	in	in	IN	O	38	case
38	1969	1969	CD	DATE	36	nmod
39	named	name	VBD	O	26	ccomp
40	the	the	DT	O	41	det
41	line	line	NN	O	39	iobj
42	``	``	``	O	45	punct
43	Men	Men	NNP	O	45	nmod:poss
44	's	's	POS	O	43	case
45	Stuff	stuff	NN	O	39	dobj
46	''	''	''	O	45	punct
47	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	48	punct
48	Martin	Martin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	45	appos
49	&	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	48	cc
50	James	James	NNP	ORGANIZATION	48	conj
51	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	48	punct
52	.	.	.	O	26	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	line	line	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	embodied	embody	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	qualities	quality	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	from	from	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	Peacock	Peacock	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Revolution	Revolution	NNP	O	3	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	such	such	JJ	O	13	case
11	as	as	IN	O	10	mwe
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	introduction	introduction	NN	O	8	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	color	color	NN	O	13	nmod
16	into	into	IN	O	19	case
17	men	man	NNS	O	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	wear	wear	NN	O	3	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	``	``	``	O	7	punct
5	Men	Men	NNP	O	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	Stuff	stuff	NN	O	0	ROOT
8	''	''	''	O	7	punct
9	line	line	NN	O	7	dep
10	incorporated	incorporate	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
11	the	the	DT	O	15	det
12	bright	bright	JJ	O	15	amod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	bold	bold	JJ	O	12	conj
15	prints	print	NNS	O	10	dobj
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	colors	color	NNS	O	15	conj
18	that	that	WDT	O	21	nsubjpass
19	were	be	VBD	O	21	auxpass
20	already	already	RB	O	21	advmod
21	showcased	showcase	VBN	O	17	acl:relcl
22	in	in	IN	O	25	case
23	both	both	DT	O	25	dep
24	her	she	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	women	woman	NNS	O	21	nmod
26	's	's	POS	O	25	case
27	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
28	children	child	NNS	O	30	nmod:poss
29	's	's	POS	O	28	case
30	lines	line	NNS	O	25	conj
31	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	state	state	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	fashion	fashion	NN	O	4	nmod
7	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
8	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
10	premiered	premiere	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
11	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
12	signature	signature	NN	O	14	compound
13	shift	shift	NN	O	14	compound
14	dress	dress	NN	O	10	dobj
15	at	at	IN	O	18	case
16	her	she	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
17	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	10	punct
20	FL	fl	NN	LOCATION	21	compound
21	lemonade	lemonade	NN	O	22	nsubj
22	stand	stand	VB	O	10	dep
23	in	in	IN	O	24	case
24	1959	1959	CD	DATE	22	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	lemonade	lemonade	NN	O	5	compound
5	stand	stand	NN	O	8	nsubj
6	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
7	eventually	eventually	RB	O	8	advmod
8	become	become	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	location	location	NN	O	8	xcomp
11	where	where	WRB	O	14	advmod
12	she	she	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	unintentionally	unintentionally	RB	O	14	advmod
14	became	become	VBD	O	8	advcl
15	famous	famous	JJ	O	14	xcomp
16	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	2	mark
2	told	tell	VBN	O	22	advcl
3	by	by	IN	O	5	case
4	Lizzie	Lizzie	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Bramlett	Bramlett	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	author	author	NN	O	5	appos
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	article	article	NN	O	7	nmod
11	titled	title	VBN	O	10	acl
12	``	``	``	O	15	punct
13	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	MISC	15	compound
14	,	,	,	O	15	punct
15	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	11	dobj
16	''	''	''	O	15	punct
17	on	on	IN	O	18	case
18	VintageFashiongGuild.org	VintageFashiongGuild.org	NNP	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	22	punct
20	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
21	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
22	decided	decide	VBD	O	0	ROOT
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	make	make	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	a	a	DT	O	27	det
26	brightly	brightly	RB	O	27	advmod
27	colored	color	VBN	O	24	dobj
28	,	,	,	O	27	punct
29	printed	print	VBN	O	27	acl
30	dress	dress	NN	O	29	dobj
31	to	to	TO	O	32	mark
32	hide	hide	VB	O	29	advcl
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	stains	stain	NNS	O	32	dobj
35	she	she	PRP	O	37	nsubj
36	continuously	continuously	RB	O	37	advmod
37	got	get	VBD	O	34	acl:relcl
38	on	on	IN	O	40	case
39	her	she	PRP$	O	40	nmod:poss
40	apron	apron	NN	O	37	nmod
41	from	from	IN	O	42	mark
42	making	make	VBG	O	37	advcl
43	juice	juice	NN	O	42	dobj
44	for	for	IN	O	47	case
45	her	she	PRP$	O	47	nmod:poss
46	lemonade	lemonade	NN	O	47	compound
47	stand	stand	NN	O	42	nmod
48	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	49	punct
49	Bramlett	bramlett	NN	PERSON	47	appos
50	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	49	punct
51	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	4	mark
2	her	she	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	juice	juice	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	stand	stand	VB	O	11	advcl
5	grew	grow	VBD	O	4	dep
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	popularity	popularity	NN	O	5	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	customers	customer	NNS	O	11	nsubj
11	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	notice	notice	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	her	she	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	new	new	JJ	O	16	amod
16	attire	attire	NN	O	13	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	women	woman	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	asking	ask	VBG	O	3	xcomp
5	about	about	IN	O	9	mark
6	where	where	WRB	O	9	advmod
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	dress	dress	NN	O	9	nsubj
9	came	come	VBD	O	4	advcl
10	from	from	IN	O	9	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	9	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
13	quickly	quickly	RB	O	17	advmod
14	after	after	IN	O	17	mark
15	everyone	everyone	NN	O	17	nsubj
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	aux
17	raving	rave	VBG	O	9	advcl
18	about	about	IN	O	19	case
19	it	it	PRP	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Bramlett	Bramlett	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	later	later	RB	O	3	advmod
3	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	how	how	WRB	O	6	advmod
6	soon	soon	RB	O	12	advmod
7	enough	enough	JJ	O	11	amod
8	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	customers	customer	NNS	O	12	nsubj
12	began	begin	VBD	O	3	ccomp
13	asking	ask	VBG	O	12	xcomp
14	her	she	PRP$	O	13	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	make	make	VB	O	13	xcomp
17	them	they	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	one	one	CD	NUMBER	16	xcomp
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	them	they	PRP	O	18	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	which	which	WDT	O	23	nsubj
23	is	be	VBZ	O	20	acl:relcl
24	when	when	WRB	O	26	advmod
25	she	she	PRP	O	26	nsubj
26	became	become	VBD	O	23	advcl
27	more	more	RBR	O	28	advmod
28	popular	popular	JJ	O	26	xcomp
29	for	for	IN	O	31	case
30	her	she	PRP$	O	31	nmod:poss
31	dresses	dress	NNS	O	28	nmod
32	then	then	RB	O	26	advmod
33	her	she	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
34	juice	juice	NN	O	32	nmod:npmod
35	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	36	punct
36	Bramlett	bramlett	NN	PERSON	34	appos
37	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	36	punct
38	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	5	cop
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	official	official	JJ	O	5	amod
5	moment	moment	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	when	when	WRB	O	9	advmod
7	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
9	became	become	VBD	O	5	acl:relcl
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	fashion	fashion	NN	O	12	compound
12	designer	designer	NN	O	9	xcomp
13	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	24	mark
2	stated	state	VBN	O	24	csubj
3	by	by	IN	O	8	case
4	the	the	DT	O	8	det
5	official	official	JJ	O	8	amod
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	website	website	NN	O	2	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	what	what	WDT	O	11	nsubj
11	started	start	VBD	O	8	acl:relcl
12	out	out	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	as	as	IN	O	22	mark
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	small	small	JJ	O	16	amod
16	business	business	NN	O	22	nsubj
17	at	at	IN	O	21	case
18	her	she	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
19	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
20	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
21	juice	juice	NN	O	16	nmod
22	stand	stand	VB	O	11	advcl
23	eventually	eventually	RB	O	22	advmod
24	flourished	flourish	VBD	O	28	csubj
25	into	into	IN	O	27	case
26	a	a	DT	O	27	det
27	national	national	JJ	O	24	nmod
28	loved	love	VBD	O	0	ROOT
29	corporation	corporation	NN	O	28	dobj
30	in	in	IN	O	31	case
31	1959	1959	CD	DATE	28	nmod
32	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
33	Our	we	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
34	Story	Story	NNP	O	28	dep
35	:	:	:	O	34	punct
36	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	37	compound
37	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	dep
38	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
39	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	Kathryn	Kathryn	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Livingston	Livingston	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	author	author	NN	O	2	appos
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	article	article	NN	O	4	nmod
8	``	``	``	O	7	punct
9	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	10	compound
10	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	7	dep
11	:	:	:	O	10	punct
12	The	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Story	Story	NNP	O	10	dep
14	of	of	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	Enterprising	enterprising	JJ	O	17	amod
17	Designer	designer	NN	O	13	nmod
18	''	''	''	O	7	punct
19	on	on	IN	O	20	case
20	NYCityWoman.com	NYCityWoman.com	NNP	O	4	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	2	punct
22	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
23	how	how	WRB	O	29	advmod
24	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	nmod:poss
26	's	's	POS	O	25	case
27	designs	design	NNS	O	29	nsubj
28	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	29	advmod
29	struck	strike	VBD	O	22	ccomp
30	fame	fame	NN	O	29	dobj
31	when	when	WRB	O	40	advmod
32	her	she	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	college	college	NN	O	40	nsubj
34	best	best	JJS	O	35	amod
35	friend	friend	NN	O	33	dep
36	,	,	,	O	33	punct
37	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	38	compound
38	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	33	appos
39	,	,	,	O	33	punct
40	wore	wear	VBD	O	29	advcl
41	them	they	PRP	O	40	dobj
42	in	in	IN	O	46	case
43	a	a	DT	O	46	det
44	LIFE	LIFE	NNP	O	46	compound
45	magazine	magazine	NN	O	46	compound
46	cover	cover	NN	O	40	nmod
47	in	in	IN	O	48	case
48	1962	1962	CD	DATE	40	nmod
49	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	50	punct
50	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	48	appos
51	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	50	punct
52	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	grabbed	grab	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	public	public	NN	O	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	attention	attention	NN	O	3	dobj
8	instantly	instantly	RB	O	3	advmod
9	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Her	she	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
2	high	high	JJ	O	4	amod
3	social	social	JJ	O	4	amod
4	status	status	NN	O	17	nsubj
5	as	as	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	8	amod
8	lady	lady	NN	O	4	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	her	she	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
11	high	high	JJ	O	12	amod
12	respect	respect	NN	O	8	conj
13	as	as	IN	O	16	case
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	fashion	fashion	NN	O	16	compound
16	icon	icon	NN	O	12	nmod
17	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
18	her	she	PRP$	O	17	dep
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	perfect	perfect	JJ	O	21	amod
21	person	person	NN	O	17	dobj
22	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
23	publically	publically	RB	O	24	advmod
24	debut	debut	VB	O	21	acl
25	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	29	nmod:poss
26	's	's	POS	O	25	case
27	classic	classic	JJ	O	29	amod
28	shift	shift	NN	O	29	compound
29	dress	dress	NN	O	24	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	stopped	stop	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	wearing	wear	VBG	O	2	xcomp
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	typical	typical	JJ	O	3	iobj
6	1950	1950	CD	DATE	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	trends	trend	NNS	O	3	dobj
9	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	strayed	stray	VBD	O	19	dep
3	away	away	RB	O	2	advmod
4	from	from	IN	O	6	case
5	formal	formal	JJ	O	6	amod
6	dresses	dress	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	hats	hat	NNS	O	6	conj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	gloves	glove	NNS	O	6	conj
11	,	,	,	O	6	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
13	long	long	RB	O	14	advmod
14	hemlines	hemline	NNS	O	6	conj
15	,	,	,	O	6	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	turn	turn	NN	O	6	conj
19	favored	favor	VBD	O	0	ROOT
20	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nsubj
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	more	more	JJR	O	21	amod
24	casual	casual	JJ	O	21	amod
25	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
26	simple	simple	JJ	O	27	amod
27	designs	design	NNS	O	21	conj
28	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	Livingston	Livingston	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	later	later	RB	O	3	advmod
3	declares	declare	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
5	as	as	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	result	result	NN	O	15	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	11	case
9	this	this	DT	O	11	det
10	newfound	newfound	JJ	O	11	amod
11	popularity	popularity	NN	O	7	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	15	punct
13	American	american	JJ	MISC	14	amod
14	women	woman	NNS	O	15	nsubj
15	followed	follow	VBD	O	3	ccomp
16	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	lead	lead	NN	O	15	dobj
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	19	appos
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
23	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Livingston	Livingston	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	notes	note	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	6	nsubj
6	raved	rave	VBD	O	3	ccomp
7	about	about	IN	O	11	case
8	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	dress	dress	NN	O	6	nmod
12	soon	soon	RB	O	17	advmod
13	after	after	IN	O	17	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	magazine	magazine	NN	O	17	nsubjpass
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	auxpass
17	released	release	VBN	O	6	advcl
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	which	which	WDT	O	20	nsubj
20	was	be	VBD	O	17	dep
21	when	when	WRB	O	24	advmod
22	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	23	compound
23	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	24	nsubj
24	became	become	VBD	O	20	advcl
25	publically	publically	RB	O	26	advmod
26	recognized	recognize	VBN	O	24	xcomp
27	as	as	IN	O	29	case
28	a	a	DT	O	29	det
29	designer	designer	NN	O	26	nmod
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	29	appos
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
33	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Women	woman	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	loved	love	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	combination	combination	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	comfort	comfort	NN	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	femininity	femininity	NN	O	6	conj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
11	color	color	NN	O	6	conj
12	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubjpass
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	embodied	embody	VBN	O	6	acl:relcl
15	in	in	IN	O	19	case
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	designs	design	NNS	O	14	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	which	which	WDT	O	22	nsubj
22	began	begin	VBD	O	19	acl:relcl
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	phenomenon	phenomenon	NN	O	22	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	loud	loud	JJ	O	5	amod
5	prints	print	NNS	O	9	nsubj
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	bold	bold	JJ	O	8	amod
8	colors	color	NNS	O	5	conj
9	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	pop	pop	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	up	up	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	all	all	DT	O	11	dobj
14	over	over	IN	O	15	case
15	1960	1960	CD	DATE	13	nmod
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
18	1970	1970	CD	DATE	20	nmod:poss
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	fashion	fashion	NN	O	13	conj
21	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Livingston	Livingston	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	7	advmod
5	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	helped	help	VBD	O	3	ccomp
8	bring	bring	VB	O	7	xcomp
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	new	new	JJ	O	8	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	casual	casual	JJ	O	10	conj
13	,	,	,	O	10	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
15	weather	weather	NN	O	17	compound
16	appropriate	appropriate	JJ	O	17	amod
17	look	look	NN	O	10	conj
18	to	to	TO	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	women	woman	NNS	O	8	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	1960	1960	CD	DATE	20	nmod
24	's	's	POS	O	23	case
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
26	Livingston	Livingston	NNP	PERSON	23	appos
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
28	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	women	woman	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	fascinated	fascinate	VBN	O	3	xcomp
5	with	with	IN	O	8	case
6	this	this	DT	O	8	det
7	new	new	JJ	O	8	amod
8	look	look	NN	O	4	nmod
9	because	because	IN	O	13	case
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	its	its	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	booming	booming	JJ	O	13	amod
13	popularity	popularity	NN	O	4	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	even	even	RB	O	3	advmod
3	caused	cause	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	some	some	DT	O	5	det
5	women	woman	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	want	want	VB	O	3	advcl
8	one	one	CD	NUMBER	7	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	13	case
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	nmod:poss
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	designs	design	NNS	O	8	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Rod	Rod	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
2	S.	S.	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Hagwood	Hagwood	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
6	wrote	write	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	article	article	NN	O	10	nsubj
9	``	``	``	O	10	punct
10	Wanted	want	VBD	O	6	ccomp
11	:	:	:	O	10	punct
12	Dancing	dance	VBG	O	10	parataxis
13	Pink	Pink	NNP	O	14	compound
14	Monkeys	Monkeys	NNPS	O	12	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	3	punct
16	''	''	''	O	3	punct
17	argues	argue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	that	that	IN	O	34	mark
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	reason	reason	NN	O	34	nsubj
21	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	23	compound
22	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	23	compound
23	designs	design	NNS	O	26	nsubjpass
24	were	be	VBD	O	26	auxpass
25	so	so	RB	O	26	advmod
26	desired	desire	VBN	O	20	acl:relcl
27	by	by	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	public	public	NN	O	26	nmod
30	was	be	VBD	O	34	cop
31	because	because	IN	O	34	case
32	of	of	IN	O	34	case
33	their	they	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
34	exclusivity	exclusivity	NN	O	17	ccomp
35	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	36	punct
36	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	PERSON	34	appos
37	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	36	punct
38	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	2	case
2	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	18	advcl
3	,	,	,	O	18	punct
4	as	as	IN	O	5	mark
5	noted	note	VBN	O	18	advcl
6	by	by	IN	O	11	case
7	the	the	DT	O	11	det
8	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
9	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
10	official	official	JJ	O	11	amod
11	website	website	NN	O	5	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	18	punct
13	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
14	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
15	designs	design	NNS	O	18	nsubjpass
16	were	be	VBD	O	18	auxpass
17	only	only	RB	O	18	advmod
18	sold	sell	VBN	O	0	ROOT
19	to	to	TO	O	20	case
20	celebrities	celebrity	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	extreme	extreme	JJ	O	24	amod
24	elite	elite	NN	O	20	conj
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	27	punct
26	Our	we	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
27	Story	Story	NNP	O	24	dep
28	:	:	:	O	27	punct
29	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
30	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	dep
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
32	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	Hagwood	Hagwood	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	contributes	contribute	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	5	case
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	argument	argument	NN	O	2	nmod
6	by	by	IN	O	7	mark
7	stating	state	VBG	O	2	advcl
8	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
9	families	family	NNS	O	27	nsubj
10	such	such	JJ	O	13	case
11	as	as	IN	O	10	mwe
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Vanderbilts	Vanderbilts	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	Rockefellers	Rockefellers	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	13	conj
17	,	,	,	O	13	punct
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	Whitneys	Whitneys	NNP	MISC	13	conj
20	,	,	,	O	13	punct
21	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	Kennedys	Kennedys	NNPS	PERSON	13	conj
24	were	be	VBD	O	27	cop
25	the	the	DT	O	27	det
26	only	only	JJ	O	27	amod
27	ones	one	NNS	O	7	ccomp
28	who	who	WP	O	30	nsubj
29	could	could	MD	O	30	aux
30	afford	afford	VB	O	27	acl:relcl
31	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	33	compound
32	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	33	compound
33	clothing	clothing	NN	O	30	dobj
34	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	35	punct
35	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	LOCATION	33	appos
36	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	35	punct
37	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	8	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	8	punct
3	over	over	IN	O	4	case
4	time	time	NN	O	8	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	brand	brand	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	less	less	RBR	O	10	advmod
10	exclusive	exclusive	JJ	O	8	xcomp
11	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
12	trickled	trickle	VBD	O	8	conj
13	down	down	RP	O	12	compound:prt
14	to	to	TO	O	15	case
15	those	those	DT	O	12	nmod
16	who	who	WP	O	17	nsubj
17	had	have	VBD	O	15	acl:relcl
18	wealth	wealth	NN	O	17	dobj
19	but	but	CC	O	24	cc
20	were	be	VBD	O	24	cop
21	not	not	RB	O	24	neg
22	necessarily	necessarily	RB	O	24	advmod
23	American	american	JJ	MISC	24	amod
24	icons	icon	NNS	O	18	dep
25	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	admiration	admiration	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	for	for	IN	O	5	case
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	2	nmod
6	quickly	quickly	RB	O	7	advmod
7	spread	spread	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	people	people	NNS	O	10	nsubj
10	began	begin	VBD	O	7	conj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	recognize	recognize	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	value	value	NN	O	12	dobj
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	status	status	NN	O	14	conj
17	a	a	DT	O	20	det
18	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	20	compound
19	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	20	compound
20	design	design	NN	O	21	nsubj
21	held	hold	VBD	O	14	acl:relcl
22	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	woman	woman	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	wearing	wear	VBG	O	2	acl
4	a	a	DT	O	7	det
5	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	7	compound
6	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	7	compound
7	dress	dress	NN	O	3	dobj
8	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
9	instantly	instantly	RB	O	10	advmod
10	deemed	deem	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	be	be	VB	O	10	dep
12	well	well	RB	O	13	advmod
13	off	off	RB	O	11	advmod
14	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	2	mark
2	stated	state	VBN	O	9	advcl
3	by	by	IN	O	4	case
4	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	PERSON	2	nmod
5	earlier	earlier	RBR	O	2	advmod
6	,	,	,	O	9	punct
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	recognition	recognition	NN	O	9	nsubj
9	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	with	with	IN	O	17	case
11	the	the	DT	O	17	det
12	brand	brand	NN	O	17	amod
13	because	because	IN	O	15	case
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	its	its	PRP$	O	12	nmod
16	'	'	''	O	17	punct
17	exclusivity	exclusivity	NN	O	9	nmod
18	when	when	WRB	O	20	advmod
19	it	it	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	began	begin	VBD	O	9	advcl
21	in	in	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	1960	1960	CD	DATE	20	nmod
24	's	's	POS	O	23	case
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
26	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	LOCATION	23	appos
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
28	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	brand	brand	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
4	always	always	RB	O	6	advmod
5	most	most	RBS	O	6	advmod
6	popular	popular	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	9	compound
9	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	FL	fl	NN	LOCATION	9	appos
12	because	because	IN	O	16	mark
13	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubj
14	was	be	VBD	O	16	cop
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	location	location	NN	O	6	advcl
17	where	where	WRB	O	22	advmod
18	the	the	DT	O	21	det
19	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
20	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	brand	brand	NN	O	22	nsubj
22	originated	originate	VBD	O	16	acl:relcl
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	New	New	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
2	York	York	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
3	Times	Times	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
4	author	author	NN	O	6	compound
5	William	William	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Norwich	Norwich	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	emphasized	emphasize	VBN	O	6	acl
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	article	article	NN	O	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
14	owning	own	VBG	O	11	acl:relcl
15	a	a	DT	O	18	det
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	18	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	18	compound
18	design	design	NN	O	14	dobj
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
21	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	18	nmod
22	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
23	a	a	DT	O	24	det
24	rite	rite	NN	O	22	xcomp
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	passage	passage	NN	O	24	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	22	punct
28	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
29	over	over	IN	O	30	case
30	time	time	NN	O	34	nmod
31	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	32	compound
32	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	34	nsubjpass
33	was	be	VBD	O	34	auxpass
34	deemed	deem	VBN	O	22	conj
35	the	the	DT	O	37	det
36	``	``	``	O	37	punct
37	uniform	uniform	JJ	O	34	dobj
38	''	''	''	O	37	punct
39	of	of	IN	O	40	case
40	those	those	DT	O	37	nmod
41	who	who	WP	O	42	nsubj
42	vacationed	vacation	VBD	O	40	acl:relcl
43	in	in	IN	O	45	case
44	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	45	compound
45	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	42	nmod
46	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	47	punct
47	Norwich	Norwich	NNP	LOCATION	45	appos
48	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	47	punct
49	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	nickname	nickname	NN	O	12	nsubj
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	brand	brand	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	quickly	quickly	RB	O	8	advmod
8	adopted	adopt	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
9	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	``	``	``	O	12	punct
12	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	0	ROOT
13	.	.	.	O	12	punct
14	''	''	''	O	12	punct

1	Emily	Emily	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Langer	Langer	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	Washington	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
5	Post	Post	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	writer	writer	NN	O	2	appos
7	,	,	,	O	2	punct
8	expands	expand	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	on	on	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	nickname	nickname	NN	O	8	nmod
12	by	by	IN	O	13	mark
13	saying	say	VBG	O	8	advcl
14	it	it	PRP	O	18	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
16	a	a	DT	O	18	det
17	shorthand	shorthand	NN	O	18	compound
18	way	way	NN	O	13	ccomp
19	for	for	IN	O	20	mark
20	referring	refer	VBG	O	18	acl
21	to	to	TO	O	22	case
22	one	one	CD	NUMBER	20	nmod
23	of	of	IN	O	28	case
24	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	28	nmod:poss
26	's	's	POS	O	25	case
27	famous	famous	JJ	O	28	amod
28	sundresses	sundress	NNS	O	22	nmod
29	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	30	punct
30	Langer	langer	NN	ORGANIZATION	28	appos
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	30	punct
32	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	goes	go	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	on	on	IN	O	2	compound:prt
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	explain	explain	VB	O	2	xcomp
6	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	nickname	nickname	NN	O	10	nsubj
9	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	10	advmod
10	began	begin	VBD	O	5	ccomp
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	1959	1959	CD	DATE	10	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	10	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
15	continued	continue	VBD	O	10	conj
16	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
17	be	be	VB	O	19	auxpass
18	commonly	commonly	RB	O	19	advmod
19	used	use	VBN	O	15	xcomp
20	until	until	IN	O	22	case
21	present	present	JJ	DATE	22	amod
22	day	day	NN	DURATION	19	nmod
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	Langer	langer	NN	O	22	appos
25	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Additionally	additionally	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	you	you	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
5	hear	hear	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	people	people	NNS	O	7	nsubj
7	refer	refer	VB	O	5	ccomp
8	to	to	TO	O	9	case
9	all	all	DT	O	7	nmod
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	12	nsubj
12	designs	design	VBZ	O	9	acl:relcl
13	as	as	IN	O	15	case
14	``	``	``	O	15	punct
15	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	12	nmod
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct
18	''	''	''	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	term	term	NN	O	4	amod
3	``	``	``	O	4	punct
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	0	ROOT
5	's	's	POS	O	4	dep
6	''	''	''	O	4	punct
7	refers	refer	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
8	to	to	TO	O	10	case
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	bunch	bunch	NN	O	7	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	designs	design	NNS	O	10	nmod
13	or	or	CC	O	12	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	brand	brand	NN	O	12	conj
16	as	as	IN	O	18	case
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	whole	whole	JJ	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	12	punct
20	rather	rather	RB	O	4	cc
21	than	than	IN	O	20	mwe
22	one	one	CD	NUMBER	23	nummod
23	design	design	NN	O	4	conj
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	particular	particular	JJ	O	23	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	terms	term	NNS	O	4	nsubjpass
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	auxpass
4	used	use	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	by	by	IN	O	6	case
6	those	those	DT	O	4	nmod
7	well	well	RB	O	8	advmod
8	versed	verse	VBN	O	6	acl
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	fashion	fashion	NN	O	11	compound
11	designers	designer	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	brands	brand	NNS	O	11	conj
14	,	,	,	O	11	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	course	course	NN	O	11	conj
18	by	by	IN	O	21	case
19	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
20	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	lovers	lover	NNS	O	8	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Bright	bright	JJ	O	2	amod
2	colors	color	NNS	O	12	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	statement	statement	NN	O	5	compound
5	prints	print	NNS	O	2	conj
6	,	,	,	O	2	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
8	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	9	amod
9	silhouettes	silhouette	NNS	O	2	conj
10	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	recipe	recipe	NN	O	0	ROOT
13	for	for	IN	O	20	case
14	the	the	DT	O	17	det
15	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
16	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	brand	brand	NN	O	20	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	20	amod
20	look	look	NN	O	12	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	reason	reason	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
4	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	clothing	clothing	NN	O	7	nsubjpass
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	auxpass
7	deemed	deem	VBN	O	2	acl:relcl
8	``	``	``	O	9	punct
9	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	7	xcomp
10	''	''	''	O	9	punct
11	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	because	because	IN	O	26	mark
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	market	market	NN	O	26	nmod
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	people	people	NNS	O	15	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	26	punct
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	designer	designer	NN	O	26	nsubj
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
23	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	appos
24	,	,	,	O	20	punct
25	was	be	VBD	O	26	aux
26	trying	try	VBG	O	11	advcl
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	attract	attract	VB	O	26	xcomp
29	when	when	WRB	O	32	advmod
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	brand	brand	NN	O	32	nsubj
32	originated	originate	VBD	O	28	advcl
33	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Langer	Langer	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	gives	give	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	some	some	DT	O	4	det
4	background	background	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
8	by	by	IN	O	9	mark
9	discussing	discuss	VBG	O	2	advcl
10	how	how	WRB	O	12	advmod
11	she	she	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	grew	grow	VBD	O	9	ccomp
13	up	up	RP	O	12	compound:prt
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	wealth	wealth	NN	O	12	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	9	punct
17	attending	attend	VBG	O	9	conj
18	private	private	JJ	O	19	amod
19	school	school	NN	O	17	dobj
20	,	,	,	O	9	punct
21	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
22	eventually	eventually	RB	O	23	advmod
23	marrying	marry	VBG	O	9	conj
24	into	into	IN	O	28	case
25	the	the	DT	O	28	det
26	elite	elite	NN	O	28	compound
27	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	MISC	28	compound
28	family	family	NN	O	23	nmod
29	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	30	punct
30	Langer	langer	NN	PERSON	28	appos
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	30	punct
32	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	background	background	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	social	social	JJ	O	6	amod
6	circle	circle	NN	O	3	conj
7	helps	help	VBZ	O	18	dep
8	explain	explain	VB	O	7	xcomp
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	style	style	NN	O	8	dobj
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	type	type	NN	O	10	conj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	market	market	NN	O	13	nmod
16	she	she	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	18	aux
18	aiming	aim	VBG	O	0	ROOT
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	attract	attract	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	when	when	WRB	O	22	advmod
22	shaping	shape	VBG	O	20	advcl
23	her	she	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
24	brand	brand	NN	O	22	dobj
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	clothing	clothing	NN	O	24	conj
27	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	10	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	styles	style	NNS	O	10	nsubj
4	created	create	VBN	O	3	acl
5	by	by	IN	O	9	case
6	the	the	DT	O	9	det
7	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
8	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	brand	brand	NN	O	4	nmod
10	boomed	boom	VBD	O	18	advcl
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	popularity	popularity	NN	O	10	nmod
13	with	with	IN	O	14	case
14	some	some	DT	O	10	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	18	punct
16	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
17	all	all	DT	O	18	nsubj
18	agreed	agree	VBD	O	0	ROOT
19	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	critiques	critique	NNS	O	2	nsubj
4	written	write	VBN	O	3	acl
5	about	about	IN	O	4	dep
6	both	both	CC	O	11	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	brand	brand	NN	O	11	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	11	amod
11	look	look	NN	O	4	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	cut	cut	NN	O	11	conj
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	clothing	clothing	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Cintra	Cintra	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	commentator	commentator	NN	O	2	appos
6	on	on	IN	O	8	case
7	popular	popular	JJ	O	8	amod
8	culture	culture	NN	O	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	wrote	write	VBD	O	0	ROOT
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	critique	critique	NN	O	10	dobj
13	labeled	label	VBN	O	12	acl
14	``	``	``	O	16	punct
15	The	the	DT	O	16	det
16	color	color	NN	O	13	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	19	case
18	mad	mad	JJ	O	19	amod
19	money	money	NN	O	16	nmod
20	''	''	''	O	16	punct
21	on	on	IN	O	25	case
22	the	the	DT	O	25	det
23	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
24	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	brand	brand	NN	O	13	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	finds	find	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	bold	bold	JJ	O	5	amod
5	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	2	dobj
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	prints	print	NNS	O	5	conj
8	that	that	WDT	O	9	nsubj
9	define	define	VBP	O	5	acl:relcl
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	9	dobj
13	as	as	IN	O	14	case
14	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	9	advcl
15	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
16	be	be	VB	O	17	cop
17	obnoxious	obnoxious	JJ	O	9	advcl
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	19	punct
19	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	17	dep
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	19	punct
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	specifically	specifically	RB	O	3	advmod
3	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	fun	fun	NN	O	3	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	7	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	4	nmod
8	men	man	NNS	O	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	wear	wear	NN	O	7	dep
11	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
12	questions	question	NNS	O	7	conj
13	what	what	WDT	O	14	det
14	kind	kind	NN	O	18	nsubj
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	man	man	NN	O	14	nmod
17	would	would	MD	O	18	aux
18	wear	wear	VB	O	12	acl:relcl
19	brightly	brightly	RB	O	20	advmod
20	colored	color	VBN	O	18	dep
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	patterned	pattern	VBN	O	20	conj
23	garments	garment	NNS	O	20	dobj
24	of	of	IN	O	25	case
25	clothing	clothing	NN	O	23	nmod
26	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	27	punct
27	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	25	appos
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
29	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Next	next	RB	O	7	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	critic	critic	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	moves	move	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	on	on	IN	O	7	compound:prt
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	make	make	VB	O	7	xcomp
11	fun	fun	NN	O	10	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	style	style	NN	O	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	fabric	fabric	NN	O	14	nmod
17	the	the	DT	O	20	det
18	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
19	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
20	brand	brand	NN	O	21	nsubj
21	uses	use	VBZ	O	11	acl:relcl
22	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	mocks	mock	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	animal	animal	NN	O	2	dobj
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	floral	floral	JJ	O	7	amod
7	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	4	conj
8	used	use	VBN	O	7	acl
9	on	on	IN	O	10	case
10	dresses	dress	NNS	O	8	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	8	punct
12	by	by	IN	O	13	mark
13	stating	state	VBG	O	8	advcl
14	``	``	``	O	16	punct
15	lily	lily	NN	O	16	compound
16	pads	pad	NNS	O	13	dobj
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	pandas	panda	NNS	O	16	appos
19	,	,	,	O	16	punct
20	daises	dais	NNS	O	16	appos
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	gooseberries	gooseberry	NNS	O	20	appos
23	,	,	,	O	20	punct
24	oh	oh	UH	O	13	dep
25	my	my	PRP$	O	4	dep
26	''	''	''	O	25	punct
27	in	in	IN	O	29	case
28	her	she	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	article	article	NN	O	25	nmod
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	29	appos
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
33	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	13	advmod
2	though	though	IN	O	13	mark
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	5	amod
5	look	look	NN	O	13	nsubjpass
6	of	of	IN	O	10	case
7	the	the	DT	O	10	det
8	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	10	compound
9	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	10	compound
10	brand	brand	NN	O	5	nmod
11	is	be	VBZ	O	13	auxpass
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	admired	admire	VBN	O	21	advcl
14	by	by	IN	O	15	case
15	all	all	DT	O	13	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	21	punct
17	it	it	PRP	O	21	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	21	cop
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	leading	leading	JJ	O	21	amod
21	reason	reason	NN	O	0	ROOT
22	why	why	WRB	O	27	advmod
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	brand	brand	NN	O	27	nsubjpass
25	is	be	VBZ	O	27	auxpass
26	so	so	RB	O	27	advmod
27	loved	love	VBN	O	21	acl:relcl
28	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
29	appreciated	appreciate	VBN	O	27	conj
30	by	by	IN	O	31	case
31	many	many	JJ	O	27	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	Others	other	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	love	love	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	brand	brand	NN	O	2	dobj
7	because	because	IN	O	10	mark
8	it	it	PRP	O	10	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
10	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	2	advcl
11	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	people	people	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	believe	believe	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
5	bold	bold	JJ	O	8	amod
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	vibrant	vibrant	JJ	O	8	amod
8	colors	color	NNS	O	14	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	repetitive	repetitive	JJ	O	11	amod
11	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	8	conj
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	prints	print	NNS	O	11	conj
14	are	be	VBP	O	3	ccomp
15	what	what	WP	O	16	nsubj
16	set	set	VBD	O	14	ccomp
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	brand	brand	NN	O	19	nmod:npmod
19	apart	apart	RB	O	16	advmod
20	from	from	IN	O	22	case
21	other	other	JJ	O	22	amod
22	designers	designer	NNS	O	16	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
24	make	make	VB	O	16	conj
25	it	it	PRP	O	26	nsubj
26	unique	unique	JJ	O	24	xcomp
27	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	7	dep
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	``	``	``	O	5	punct
5	preppiness	preppiness	NN	O	7	nsubj
6	''	''	''	O	5	punct
7	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	why	why	WRB	O	11	advmod
9	people	people	NNS	O	11	nsubj
10	instantly	instantly	RB	O	11	advmod
11	recognize	recognize	VBP	O	7	advcl
12	it	it	PRP	O	11	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Lizzie	Lizzie	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Bramlett	Bramlett	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	11	advmod
5	the	the	DT	O	8	det
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	brand	brand	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	auxpass
10	best	best	RB	O	11	advmod
11	known	know	VBN	O	3	ccomp
12	for	for	IN	O	14	case
13	its	its	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	whimsical	whimsical	JJ	O	11	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	tropical	tropical	JJ	O	17	amod
17	prints	print	NNS	O	14	conj
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	19	punct
19	Bramlett	bramlett	NN	PERSON	14	appos
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	19	punct
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	such	such	JJ	O	2	xcomp
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	wide	wide	JJ	O	6	amod
6	variety	variety	NN	O	17	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	prints	print	NNS	O	9	compound
9	designers	designer	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	6	punct
11	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
12	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	6	conj
14	herself	herself	PRP	O	13	nmod:npmod
15	,	,	,	O	6	punct
16	have	have	VBP	O	17	aux
17	created	create	VBN	O	3	ccomp
18	over	over	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	DURATION	20	det
20	years	year	NNS	DURATION	17	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	17	punct
22	ranging	range	VBG	O	17	xcomp
23	from	from	IN	O	24	case
24	floral	floral	JJ	O	22	nmod
25	to	to	TO	O	26	case
26	animal	animal	NN	O	24	nmod
27	to	to	TO	O	28	case
28	beach	beach	NN	O	22	nmod
29	to	to	TO	O	30	case
30	shapes	shape	NNS	O	22	nmod
31	to	to	TO	O	32	case
32	lines	line	NNS	O	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Each	each	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	these	these	DT	O	4	det
4	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	a	a	DT	O	9	det
7	specific	specific	JJ	O	9	amod
8	color	color	NN	O	9	compound
9	scheme	scheme	NN	O	5	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	go	go	VB	O	9	acl
12	along	along	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	with	with	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	prints	print	NNS	O	16	compound
16	theme	theme	NN	O	11	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	author	author	NN	O	5	compound
4	Rod	Rod	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Hagwood	Hagwood	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	declares	declare	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	most	most	RBS	O	10	advmod
10	popular	popular	JJ	O	20	nsubj
11	or	or	CC	O	10	cc
12	recognized	recognize	VBN	O	13	amod
13	colors	color	NNS	O	10	conj
14	of	of	IN	O	18	case
15	the	the	DT	O	18	det
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	brand	brand	NN	O	10	nmod
19	are	be	VBP	O	20	cop
20	pink	pink	JJ	O	6	ccomp
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	green	green	JJ	O	20	conj
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	LOCATION	20	dep
25	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
26	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	continues	continue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	go	go	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	on	on	IN	O	4	nmod
6	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
7	state	state	NN	O	2	conj
8	that	that	WDT	O	13	dobj
9	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	13	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
11	most	most	RBS	O	12	advmod
12	well	well	RB	O	13	advmod
13	known	know	VBN	O	2	advcl
14	for	for	IN	O	16	case
15	these	these	DT	O	16	det
16	colors	color	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	because	because	IN	O	21	case
18	of	of	IN	O	21	case
19	their	they	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
20	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	21	amod
21	feel	feel	NN	O	13	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	13	punct
23	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
24	because	because	IN	O	27	mark
25	they	they	PRP	O	27	nsubj
26	have	have	VBP	O	27	aux
27	become	become	VBN	O	13	conj
28	a	a	DT	O	30	det
29	``	``	``	O	30	punct
30	banner	banner	NN	O	27	xcomp
31	of	of	IN	O	36	case
32	the	the	DT	O	36	det
33	authentic	authentic	JJ	O	36	amod
34	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	36	compound
35	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	36	compound
36	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	30	nmod
37	''	''	''	O	30	punct
38	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	39	punct
39	Hagwood	Hagwood	NNP	LOCATION	30	appos
40	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	39	punct
41	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	constantly	constantly	RB	O	7	advmod
7	refreshing	refresh	VBG	O	0	ROOT
8	their	they	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	look	look	NN	O	7	dobj
10	with	with	IN	O	13	case
11	new	new	JJ	O	13	amod
12	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	13	amod
13	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	7	nmod
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	prints	print	NNS	O	13	conj
16	,	,	,	O	7	punct
17	making	make	VBG	O	7	advcl
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	brand	brand	NN	O	17	dobj
20	fresh	fresh	JJ	O	19	amod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	new	new	JJ	O	20	conj
23	each	each	DT	O	24	det
24	season	season	NN	O	17	nmod:tmod
25	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	auxpass
6	known	know	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	loved	love	VBN	O	6	conj
9	by	by	IN	O	10	case
10	many	many	JJ	O	6	advcl
11	because	because	IN	O	19	case
12	of	of	IN	O	19	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	brand	brand	NN	O	19	nmod:poss
15	's	's	POS	O	14	case
16	unique	unique	JJ	O	19	amod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	16	conj
19	look	look	NN	O	10	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	4	det
2	major	major	JJ	O	4	amod
3	contributing	contributing	JJ	O	4	amod
4	factor	factor	NN	O	14	nsubj
5	to	to	TO	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	style	style	NN	O	4	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	11	case
9	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
10	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
11	clothing	clothing	NN	O	7	nmod
12	are	be	VBP	O	14	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	cuts	cut	NNS	O	0	ROOT
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	apparel	apparel	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	people	people	NNS	O	5	nsubj
3	do	do	VBP	O	5	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	like	like	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	8	amod
8	look	look	NN	O	5	dobj
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	12	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	12	compound
12	brand	brand	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	sells	sell	VBZ	O	8	acl:relcl
14	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	boxy	boxy	JJ	O	3	amod
3	cuts	cut	NNS	O	15	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	15	punct
5	long	long	RB	O	6	advmod
6	hemlines	hemline	NNS	O	15	dep
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
9	not	not	RB	O	10	neg
10	too	too	RB	O	6	conj
11	plunging	plunge	VBG	O	10	dep
12	necklines	neckline	NNS	O	11	dobj
13	are	be	VBP	O	15	cop
14	all	all	DT	O	15	det
15	factors	factor	NNS	O	0	ROOT
16	that	that	WDT	O	18	nsubj
17	can	can	MD	O	18	aux
18	turn	turn	VB	O	15	acl:relcl
19	people	people	NNS	O	18	dobj
20	away	away	RB	O	18	advmod
21	from	from	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	brand	brand	NN	O	18	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	16	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	16	punct
3	because	because	IN	O	7	case
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	these	these	DT	O	7	det
6	basic	basic	JJ	O	7	amod
7	cuts	cut	NNS	O	16	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	styles	style	NNS	O	7	conj
10	Richard	Richard	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Martin	Martin	NNP	PERSON	16	nsubj
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	Owen	Owen	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	James	James	NNP	PERSON	11	conj
15	have	have	VBP	O	16	aux
16	deemed	deem	VBN	O	0	ROOT
17	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
18	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	16	dobj
19	as	as	IN	O	20	dep
20	not	not	RB	O	18	cc
21	a	a	DT	O	23	det
22	true	true	JJ	O	23	amod
23	designer	designer	NN	O	18	conj
24	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
25	Martin	Martin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	appos
26	&	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	25	cc
27	James	James	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	conj
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
29	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	claim	claim	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
4	her	she	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	looks	look	NNS	O	8	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	creative	creative	JJ	O	2	ccomp
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
11	she	she	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	did	do	VBD	O	14	aux
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	design	design	VB	O	8	conj
15	anything	anything	NN	O	14	dobj
16	new	new	JJ	O	15	amod
17	,	,	,	O	20	punct
18	instead	instead	RB	O	20	advmod
19	they	they	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	believe	believe	VBP	O	14	parataxis
21	she	she	PRP	O	20	dobj
22	just	just	RB	O	20	advmod
23	simply	simply	RB	O	20	advmod
24	``	``	``	O	14	punct
25	provided	provide	VBN	O	27	case
26	a	a	DT	O	27	det
27	uniform	uniform	NN	O	14	advcl
28	of	of	IN	O	29	case
29	sorts	sort	NNS	O	27	nmod
30	for	for	IN	O	27	case
31	women	woman	NNS	O	27	dep
32	of	of	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	early	early	JJ	O	31	nmod
35	and	and	CC	O	34	cc
36	mid	mid	JJ	O	37	amod
37	1960s	1960	NNS	DATE	34	conj
38	''	''	''	O	37	punct
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	Martin	Martin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	appos
41	&	&	CC	ORGANIZATION	40	cc
42	James	James	NNP	ORGANIZATION	40	conj
43	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct
44	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	3	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	3	compound
3	designs	design	NNS	O	6	nsubjpass
4	have	have	VBP	O	6	aux
5	been	be	VBN	O	6	auxpass
6	labeled	label	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	variety	variety	NN	O	6	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	negative	negative	JJ	O	11	amod
11	terms	term	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	such	such	JJ	O	14	case
13	as	as	IN	O	12	mwe
14	common	common	JJ	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	too	too	RB	O	17	advmod
17	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	14	conj
18	,	,	,	O	14	punct
19	or	or	CC	O	14	cc
20	boring	boring	NN	O	14	conj
21	;	;	:	O	6	punct
22	however	however	RB	O	29	advmod
23	,	,	,	O	29	punct
24	these	these	DT	O	29	nsubj
25	could	could	MD	O	29	aux
26	also	also	RB	O	29	advmod
27	all	all	DT	O	29	advmod
28	be	be	VB	O	29	cop
29	terms	term	NNS	O	6	parataxis
30	could	could	MD	O	29	dep
31	that	that	WDT	O	32	nsubj
32	bring	bring	VBP	O	29	acl:relcl
33	costumers	costumer	NNS	O	32	dobj
34	to	to	TO	O	35	mark
35	want	want	VB	O	32	xcomp
36	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
37	buy	buy	VB	O	35	xcomp
38	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	40	compound
39	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	40	compound
40	clothing	clothing	NN	O	37	dobj
41	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Ever	ever	RB	O	5	advmod
2	since	since	IN	O	5	mark
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	brand	brand	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	originated	originate	VBD	O	17	advcl
6	,	,	,	O	17	punct
7	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	8	amod
8	cuts	cut	NNS	O	17	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	clean	clean	JJ	O	12	amod
11	cut	cut	NN	O	12	compound
12	lines	line	NNS	O	8	conj
13	have	have	VBP	O	17	aux
14	been	be	VBN	O	17	cop
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	selling	selling	NN	O	17	compound
17	point	point	NN	O	0	ROOT
18	for	for	IN	O	22	case
19	the	the	DT	O	22	det
20	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
21	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
22	brand	brand	NN	O	17	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Livingston	Livingston	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	emphasizes	emphasize	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
4	the	the	DT	O	8	det
5	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	8	amod
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	8	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	8	compound
8	design	design	NN	O	12	nsubj
9	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	shift	shift	NN	O	12	compound
12	dress	dress	NN	O	2	ccomp
13	;	;	:	O	12	punct
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	boxy	boxy	JJ	O	16	amod
16	cut	cut	NN	O	12	dep
17	that	that	WDT	O	20	nsubj
18	does	do	VBZ	O	20	aux
19	not	not	RB	O	20	neg
20	cling	cling	VB	O	16	acl:relcl
21	to	to	TO	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	body	body	NN	O	20	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	20	punct
25	but	but	CC	O	20	cc
26	instead	instead	RB	O	27	advmod
27	hangs	hang	VBZ	O	20	conj
28	off	off	RP	O	27	compound:prt
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	body	body	NN	O	27	dobj
31	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	32	punct
32	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	30	appos
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
34	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	then	then	RB	O	3	advmod
3	goes	go	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	on	on	IN	O	3	compound:prt
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	explain	explain	VB	O	3	xcomp
7	how	how	WRB	O	15	advmod
8	this	this	DT	O	10	det
9	straight-cut	straight-cut	JJ	O	10	amod
10	silhouette	silhouette	NN	O	15	nsubj
11	of	of	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	shift	shift	NN	O	14	compound
14	dress	dress	NN	O	10	nmod
15	was	be	VBD	O	6	ccomp
16	exactly	exactly	RB	O	17	advmod
17	what	what	WP	O	19	nsubj
18	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	19	advmod
19	set	set	VBD	O	15	ccomp
20	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	dobj
22	apart	apart	RB	O	19	advmod
23	from	from	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	19	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	1950	1950	CD	DATE	25	nmod
29	's	's	POS	O	28	case
30	,	,	,	O	28	punct
31	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
32	what	what	WP	O	34	nsubj
33	originally	originally	RB	O	34	advmod
34	sparked	spark	VBD	O	28	conj
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	interest	interest	NN	O	34	dobj
37	of	of	IN	O	39	case
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	women	woman	NNS	O	36	nmod
40	of	of	IN	O	42	case
41	the	the	DT	O	42	det
42	time	time	NN	O	39	nmod
43	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	44	punct
44	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	42	appos
45	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	44	punct
46	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	det
2	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	3	amod
3	characteristics	characteristic	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	differentiate	differentiate	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	8	det
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	brand	brand	NN	O	4	dobj
9	from	from	IN	O	10	case
10	others	other	NNS	O	8	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	still	still	RB	O	6	advmod
6	designs	design	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	dresses	dress	NNS	O	6	dobj
8	that	that	WDT	O	9	nsubj
9	follow	follow	VBP	O	7	acl:relcl
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	classic	classic	JJ	O	13	amod
12	shift	shift	NN	O	13	compound
13	silhouette	silhouette	NN	O	9	dobj
14	;	;	:	O	6	punct
15	however	however	RB	O	18	advmod
16	,	,	,	O	18	punct
17	they	they	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	offer	offer	VBP	O	6	parataxis
19	other	other	JJ	O	20	amod
20	styles	style	NNS	O	18	dobj
21	as	as	RB	O	18	advmod
22	well	well	RB	O	21	mwe
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Currently	currently	RB	DATE	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	there	there	EX	O	4	expl
4	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	variety	variety	NN	O	4	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	styles	style	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	dresses	dress	NNS	O	8	nmod
11	including	include	VBG	O	12	case
12	halter	halter	NN	O	10	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	sleeveless	sleeveless	JJ	O	18	amod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
17	sleeved	sleeved	JJ	O	14	conj
18	dresses	dress	NNS	O	12	appos
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	17	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	17	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	one	one	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	thing	thing	NN	O	17	nsubj
6	all	all	DT	O	9	advmod
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	these	these	DT	O	9	det
9	dresses	dress	NNS	O	5	nmod
10	have	have	VBP	O	17	aux
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	common	common	JJ	O	17	nmod
13	are	be	VBP	O	17	cop
14	clean-cut	clean-cut	JJ	O	17	amod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	14	conj
17	lines	line	NNS	O	0	ROOT
18	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	dresses	dress	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	typically	typically	RB	O	4	advmod
4	fall	fall	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	right	right	RB	O	4	advmod
6	above	above	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	knee	knee	NN	O	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
11	do	do	VBP	O	4	conj
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	hug	hug	NN	O	11	dobj
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	body	body	NN	O	11	nsubj
16	too	too	RB	O	17	advmod
17	closely	closely	RB	O	15	advmod
18	from	from	IN	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	waist	waist	NN	O	21	nmod:npmod
21	down	down	RB	O	17	advcl
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	5	advmod
2	though	though	IN	O	5	mark
3	styles	style	NNS	O	5	nsubj
4	have	have	VBP	O	5	aux
5	evolved	evolve	VBN	O	14	csubj
6	since	since	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	1960	1960	CD	DATE	5	nmod
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	,	,	,	O	8	punct
11	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	appos
13	has	have	VBZ	O	14	aux
14	stayed	stay	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	true	true	JJ	O	14	xcomp
16	to	to	TO	O	21	case
17	her	she	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
18	classic	classic	JJ	O	21	amod
19	,	,	,	O	21	punct
20	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	21	amod
21	look	look	NN	O	15	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	while	while	IN	O	25	mark
24	still	still	RB	O	25	advmod
25	remaining	remain	VBG	O	21	dep
26	current	current	JJ	DATE	25	xcomp
27	in	in	IN	O	29	case
28	her	she	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	designs	design	NNS	O	26	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	3	amod
3	look	look	NN	O	13	nsubj
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	clean-cut	clean-cut	JJ	O	6	amod
6	lines	line	NNS	O	3	conj
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
9	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	designs	design	NNS	O	6	nmod
11	are	be	VBP	O	13	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	highlight	highlight	NN	O	0	ROOT
14	of	of	IN	O	18	case
15	the	the	DT	O	18	det
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	brand	brand	NN	O	13	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	a	a	DT	O	9	det
7	specific	specific	JJ	O	9	amod
8	costumer	costumer	NN	O	9	compound
9	market	market	NN	O	5	dobj
10	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Some	some	DT	O	2	det
2	people	people	NNS	O	5	nsubj
3	do	do	VBP	O	5	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	this	this	DT	O	5	dobj
7	as	as	IN	O	10	case
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	positive	positive	JJ	O	10	amod
10	attribute	attribute	NN	O	6	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	brand	brand	NN	O	5	nsubjpass
3	has	have	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	been	be	VBN	O	5	auxpass
5	criticized	criticize	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	once	once	RB	DATE	8	advmod
8	again	again	RB	O	5	advmod
9	,	,	,	O	5	punct
10	by	by	IN	O	12	case
11	Cintra	Cintra	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
13	for	for	IN	O	14	mark
14	having	have	VBG	O	12	acl
15	too	too	RB	O	16	advmod
16	small	small	JJ	O	14	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	20	case
18	a	a	DT	O	20	det
19	costumer	costumer	NN	O	20	compound
20	market	market	NN	O	16	nmod
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	22	punct
22	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	20	appos
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	22	punct
24	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	believes	believe	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	clothing	clothing	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
8	overpriced	overprice	VBN	O	2	ccomp
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	practical	practical	JJ	O	8	conj
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
13	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	11	appos
14	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	her	she	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	article	article	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	critiquing	critique	VBG	O	3	acl
5	the	the	DT	O	8	det
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	brand	brand	NN	O	4	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	comments	comment	NNS	O	8	appos
12	on	on	IN	O	14	case
13	an	a	DT	O	14	det
14	article	article	NN	O	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	children	child	NNS	O	18	nmod:poss
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	clothing	clothing	NN	O	14	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	exclaims	exclaim	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	``	``	``	O	2	punct
5	It	it	PRP	O	8	nsubj
6	's	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
7	$	$	$	MONEY	8	dep
8	58	58	CD	MONEY	2	ccomp
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	pricey	pricey	JJ	O	8	amod
11	for	for	IN	O	14	case
12	a	a	DT	O	14	det
13	washcloth-sized	washcloth-sized	JJ	O	14	amod
14	garment	garment	NN	O	10	nmod
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	growing	grow	VBG	O	17	amod
17	baby	baby	NN	O	19	nsubj
18	might	might	MD	O	19	aux
19	wear	wear	VB	O	14	acl:relcl
20	for	for	IN	O	23	case
21	a	a	DT	O	23	det
22	grand	grand	JJ	O	23	amod
23	total	total	NN	O	19	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	4.8	4.8	CD	DURATION	26	nummod
26	hours	hour	NNS	DURATION	23	nmod
27	''	''	''	O	2	punct
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	2	dep
30	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
31	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Here	here	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	Wilson	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	expresses	express	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	how	how	WRB	O	18	advmod
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	price	price	NN	O	18	nsubj
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	an	a	DT	O	10	det
10	article	article	NN	O	7	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	14	case
12	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	14	compound
13	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	14	compound
14	clothing	clothing	NN	O	10	nmod
15	may	may	MD	O	18	aux
16	not	not	RB	O	18	neg
17	be	be	VB	O	18	cop
18	worth	worth	JJ	O	4	ccomp
19	it	it	PRP	O	18	dep
20	due	due	JJ	O	19	amod
21	to	to	TO	O	24	case
22	its	its	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
23	high	high	JJ	O	24	amod
24	cost	cost	NN	O	20	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	critique	critique	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	9	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	brand	brand	NN	O	9	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	small	small	JJ	O	9	amod
8	costumer	costumer	NN	O	9	compound
9	market	market	NN	O	2	nmod
10	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
11	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	clothing	clothing	NN	O	17	nsubj
14	is	be	VBZ	O	17	cop
15	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
16	always	always	RB	O	17	advmod
17	practical	practical	JJ	O	10	ccomp
18	because	because	IN	O	23	mark
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	clothing	clothing	NN	O	23	nsubjpass
21	is	be	VBZ	O	23	auxpass
22	typically	typically	RB	O	23	advmod
23	geared	gear	VBN	O	17	advcl
24	toward	toward	IN	O	27	case
25	a	a	DT	O	27	det
26	warm-climate	warm-climate	JJ	O	27	amod
27	area	area	NN	O	23	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Some	some	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	may	may	MD	O	3	aux
3	argue	argue	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
5	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	customer	customer	NN	O	9	compound
9	market	market	NN	O	12	nsubjpass
10	is	be	VBZ	O	12	auxpass
11	too	too	RB	O	12	advmod
12	customized	customize	VBN	O	3	ccomp
13	;	;	:	O	3	punct
14	however	however	RB	O	19	advmod
15	,	,	,	O	19	punct
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nsubj
18	herself	herself	PRP	O	17	nmod:npmod
19	worked	work	VBD	O	3	parataxis
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	create	create	VB	O	19	xcomp
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	brand	brand	NN	O	21	dobj
24	that	that	WDT	O	26	nsubj
25	would	would	MD	O	26	aux
26	include	include	VB	O	23	acl:relcl
27	all	all	DT	O	28	det
28	ages	age	NNS	O	26	dobj
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	types	type	NNS	O	28	conj
31	of	of	IN	O	32	case
32	women	woman	NNS	O	28	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	3	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	3	compound
3	clothing	clothing	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
5	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
6	only	only	RB	O	8	advmod
7	for	for	IN	O	8	case
8	those	those	DT	O	0	ROOT
9	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
10	live	live	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	warm	warm	JJ	O	13	amod
13	areas	area	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
15	vacation	vacation	NN	O	13	conj
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	tropics	tropics	NNS	O	10	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Associated	Associated	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Press	Press	NNP	O	8	nsubj
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	Mail	Mail	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Online	Online	NNP	O	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	8	punct
8	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	type	type	NN	O	8	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	client	client	NN	O	10	nmod
13	the	the	DT	O	16	det
14	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	16	compound
15	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	16	compound
16	brand	brand	NN	O	18	nsubj
17	is	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
18	for	for	IN	O	10	acl:relcl
19	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	discuss	discuss	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	how	how	WRB	O	6	advmod
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	wanted	want	VBD	O	2	ccomp
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	make	make	VB	O	6	ccomp
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	``	``	``	O	11	punct
11	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	8	dobj
12	that	that	WDT	O	15	dobj
13	real	real	JJ	O	14	amod
14	people	people	NNS	O	15	nsubj
15	had	have	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
16	,	,	,	O	11	punct
17	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
18	at	at	IN	O	19	case
19	least	least	JJS	O	11	conj
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	wanted	want	VBD	O	19	dep
22	''	''	''	O	6	punct
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
24	Associated	Associated	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	Press	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	dep
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
27	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
7	exclusive	exclusive	JJ	O	11	ccomp
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubjpass
10	is	be	VBZ	O	11	auxpass
11	meant	mean	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
13	be	be	VB	O	16	cop
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	16	compound
16	brand	brand	NN	O	11	xcomp
17	for	for	IN	O	19	case
18	all	all	DT	O	19	det
19	ages	age	NNS	O	16	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	types	type	NNS	O	19	conj
22	of	of	IN	O	23	case
23	women	woman	NNS	O	19	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Associated	Associated	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	Press	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
4	then	then	RB	O	5	advmod
5	moves	move	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	on	on	IN	O	5	compound:prt
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	discuss	discuss	VB	O	5	xcomp
9	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	purpose	purpose	NN	O	16	nsubj
12	of	of	IN	O	15	case
13	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
14	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
15	clothing	clothing	NN	O	11	nmod
16	is	be	VBZ	O	8	ccomp
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	make	make	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	women	woman	NNS	O	20	nsubj
20	feel	feel	VB	O	18	ccomp
21	happy	happy	JJ	O	20	xcomp
22	,	,	,	O	5	punct
23	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
24	there	there	EX	O	25	expl
25	is	be	VBZ	O	5	conj
26	no	no	DT	O	28	neg
27	one	one	NN	NUMBER	28	compound
28	age	age	NN	O	25	nsubj
29	for	for	IN	O	30	case
30	that	that	DT	O	28	nmod
31	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	33	punct
32	Associated	Associated	NNP	ORGANIZATION	33	compound
33	Press	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	appos
34	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	33	punct
35	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Lastly	lastly	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	article	article	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	discusses	discuss	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	how	how	WRB	O	11	advmod
7	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	just	just	RB	O	5	ccomp
12	for	for	IN	O	14	case
13	any	any	DT	O	14	det
14	occasion	occasion	NN	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	because	because	IN	O	20	mark
17	it	it	PRP	O	20	nsubjpass
18	is	be	VBZ	O	20	auxpass
19	not	not	RB	O	20	neg
20	supposed	suppose	VBN	O	14	dep
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	be	be	VB	O	20	xcomp
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
24	Associated	Associated	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	Press	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	appos
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
27	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	3	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	3	compound
3	clothing	clothing	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
6	be	be	VB	O	7	auxpass
7	worn	wear	VBN	O	4	xcomp
8	at	at	IN	O	9	case
9	celebrations	celebration	NNS	O	7	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
12	during	during	IN	O	14	case
13	happy	happy	JJ	O	14	amod
14	times	time	NNS	O	9	conj
15	,	,	,	O	9	punct
16	not	not	RB	O	20	neg
17	for	for	IN	O	20	case
18	every	every	DT	SET	20	det
19	day	day	NN	SET	20	compound
20	activities	activity	NNS	O	9	conj
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	23	punct
22	Associated	Associated	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
23	Press	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	appos
24	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	23	punct
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	auxpass
6	designed	design	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	9	case
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	specific	specific	JJ	O	6	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	customized	customize	VBN	O	12	amod
12	market	market	NN	O	9	conj
13	;	;	:	O	6	punct
14	women	woman	NNS	O	6	parataxis
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	all	all	DT	O	17	det
17	ages	age	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	with	with	IN	O	26	case
19	a	a	DT	O	26	det
20	``	``	``	O	26	punct
21	life	life	NN	O	24	nsubj
22	's	be	VBZ	O	24	cop
23	a	a	DT	O	24	det
24	party	party	NN	O	26	dep
25	''	''	''	O	26	punct
26	attitude	attitude	NN	O	14	dep
27	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
28	Associated	Associated	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	compound
29	Press	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	dep
30	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
31	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	overarching	overarching	JJ	O	3	amod
3	theme	theme	NN	O	14	nsubj
4	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	pulls	pull	VBZ	O	3	acl:relcl
6	the	the	DT	O	9	det
7	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
8	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	brand	brand	NN	O	5	dobj
10	together	together	RB	O	14	advmod
11	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	14	det
13	carefree	carefree	JJ	O	14	amod
14	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	0	ROOT
15	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	created	create	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	her	she	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	brand	brand	NN	O	3	dobj
6	with	with	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	image	image	NN	O	3	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	luxury	luxury	NN	O	8	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	whimsy	whimsy	NN	O	10	conj
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct
