1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	revolutionized	revolutionize	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	fashion	fashion	NN	O	3	dobj
5	with	with	IN	O	8	case
6	her	she	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
7	bright	bright	JJ	O	8	amod
8	colors	color	NNS	O	3	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	bold	bold	JJ	O	11	amod
11	prints	print	NNS	O	8	conj
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	What	what	WDT	O	2	nsubj
2	started	start	VBD	O	13	csubj
3	out	out	RP	O	2	compound:prt
4	as	as	IN	O	12	mark
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	uniform	uniform	NN	O	12	nsubj
7	for	for	IN	O	11	case
8	her	she	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
9	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
10	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	juice	juice	NN	O	6	nmod
12	stand	stand	VB	O	2	advcl
13	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	well-known	well-known	JJ	O	16	amod
16	brand	brand	NN	O	13	xcomp
17	loved	love	VBN	O	16	acl
18	by	by	IN	O	19	case
19	many	many	JJ	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	4	compound
3	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	4	compound
4	brand	brand	NN	O	7	nsubjpass
5	was	be	VBD	O	7	auxpass
6	officially	officially	RB	O	7	advmod
7	established	establish	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	1959	1959	CD	DATE	7	nmod
10	during	during	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	time	time	NN	O	7	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	16	case
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	drastic	drastic	JJ	O	16	amod
16	transformation	transformation	NN	O	12	nmod
17	in	in	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	fashion	fashion	NN	O	20	compound
20	industry	industry	NN	O	16	nmod
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	23	punct
22	Our	we	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	Story	Story	NNP	O	20	dep
24	:	:	:	O	23	punct
25	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	compound
26	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	dep
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	23	punct
28	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
3	brought	bring	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	new	new	JJ	O	6	amod
6	look	look	NN	O	3	dobj
7	into	into	IN	O	17	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	dull	dull	JJ	O	10	amod
10	transition	transition	NN	O	17	nmod:poss
11	between	between	IN	O	12	case
12	1950	1950	CD	DATE	10	nmod
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
15	1960	1960	CD	DATE	12	conj
16	's	's	POS	O	10	case
17	fashion	fashion	NN	O	3	nmod
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
19	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	20	nummod
20	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	17	dep
21	for	for	IN	O	22	case
22	Women	Women	NNP	O	20	nmod
23	&	&	CC	O	22	cc
24	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	22	conj
25	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
26	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	only	only	RB	O	2	dep
5	contributed	contribute	VBD	O	2	conj
6	to	to	TO	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	changing	change	VBG	O	9	amod
9	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	5	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	11	case
11	the	the	DT	O	9	nmod
12	1960	1960	CD	DATE	11	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	,	,	,	O	2	punct
15	but	but	CC	O	2	cc
16	she	she	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	also	also	RB	O	18	advmod
18	created	create	VBD	O	2	conj
19	a	a	DT	O	22	det
20	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	22	compound
21	brand	brand	NN	O	22	compound
22	name	name	NN	O	18	dobj
23	for	for	IN	O	24	case
24	herself	herself	PRP	O	18	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	recreated	recreate	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	2	xcomp
4	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	created	create	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	5	compound
5	brand	brand	NN	O	2	dobj
6	that	that	WDT	O	8	nsubj
7	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
8	go	go	VB	O	5	acl:relcl
9	on	on	IN	O	8	compound:prt
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	effect	effect	VB	O	8	xcomp
12	men	man	NNS	O	11	dobj
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	women	woman	NNS	O	12	conj
15	,	,	,	O	12	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	fashion	fashion	NN	O	19	compound
19	industry	industry	NN	O	12	conj
20	for	for	IN	O	23	case
21	over	over	IN	O	23	amod
22	fifty	fifty	CD	DURATION	23	nummod
23	years	year	NNS	DURATION	19	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Trends	trend	NNS	O	4	nsubj
2	in	in	IN	O	3	case
3	fashion	fashion	NN	O	1	nmod
4	changed	change	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	drastically	drastically	RB	O	4	advmod
6	within	within	IN	O	7	case
7	the	the	DT	O	4	nmod
8	1960	1960	CD	DATE	7	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Up	up	IN	O	3	case
2	until	until	IN	O	3	case
3	1965	1965	CD	DATE	5	nmod
4	fashion	fashion	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	remained	remain	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	stagnant	stagnant	JJ	O	5	xcomp
7	to	to	TO	O	9	case
8	those	those	DT	O	9	det
9	popular	popular	JJ	O	6	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	1950	1950	CD	DATE	5	nmod
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	16	punct
15	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	16	nummod
16	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	12	dep
17	for	for	IN	O	18	case
18	Women	Women	NNP	O	16	nmod
19	&	&	CC	O	18	cc
20	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	18	conj
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	16	punct
22	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Women	woman	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	continued	continue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	wear	wear	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	6	amod
6	cuts	cut	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	combination	combination	NN	O	6	nmod
9	with	with	IN	O	13	case
10	a	a	DT	O	13	det
11	dull	dull	JJ	O	13	amod
12	color	color	NN	O	13	compound
13	palette	palette	NN	O	4	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	9	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	9	punct
4	women	woman	NNS	O	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	clothing	clothing	NN	O	9	nsubj
7	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
8	very	very	RB	O	9	advmod
9	feminine	feminine	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	body	body	NN	O	12	nmod:npmod
12	conscious	conscious	JJ	O	9	conj
13	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	typical	typical	JJ	O	3	amod
3	attire	attire	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	for	for	IN	O	5	case
5	women	woman	NNS	O	3	nmod
6	consisted	consist	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	dresses	dress	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	with	with	IN	O	10	mark
10	accentuated	accentuate	VBN	O	6	advcl
11	busts	bust	NNS	O	10	dobj
12	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
13	pulled	pull	VBD	O	6	conj
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	waistlines	waistline	NNS	O	13	nmod
16	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	17	punct
17	History	history	NN	O	15	dep
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	20	nummod
20	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	17	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	20	conj
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	17	punct
24	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	9	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	9	punct
3	this	this	DT	O	7	det
4	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	7	amod
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	traditional	traditional	JJ	O	4	conj
7	attire	attire	NN	O	9	nsubj
8	quickly	quickly	RB	O	9	advmod
9	vanished	vanish	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	during	during	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	mid	mid	JJ	O	9	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	late	late	JJ	DATE	15	amod
15	1960	1960	CD	DATE	12	conj
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	19	punct
18	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	19	nummod
19	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	12	dep
20	for	for	IN	O	21	case
21	Women	Women	NNP	O	19	nmod
22	&	&	CC	O	21	cc
23	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	21	conj
24	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	19	punct
25	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	DATE	3	det
2	late	late	JJ	DATE	3	amod
3	1960	1960	CD	DATE	0	ROOT
4	's	's	POS	O	3	case
5	were	be	VBD	O	7	cop
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	time	time	NN	O	3	acl:relcl
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	wild	wild	JJ	O	10	amod
10	colors	color	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	bold	bold	JJ	O	13	amod
13	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	10	appos
14	,	,	,	O	10	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
16	shortened	shorten	VBD	O	7	conj
17	hemlines	hemline	NNS	O	16	dobj
18	for	for	IN	O	21	case
19	women	woman	NNS	O	21	nmod:poss
20	's	's	POS	O	19	case
21	fashion	fashion	NN	O	16	nmod
22	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
23	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	24	nummod
24	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	21	dep
25	for	for	IN	O	26	case
26	Women	Women	NNP	O	24	nmod
27	&	&	CC	O	26	cc
28	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	26	conj
29	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	9	nmod
3	to	to	TO	O	6	case
4	these	these	DT	O	6	det
5	drastic	drastic	JJ	O	6	amod
6	characteristics	characteristic	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	9	punct
8	fashion	fashion	NN	O	9	nsubj
9	strayed	stray	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	away	away	RB	O	9	compound:prt
11	from	from	IN	O	12	case
12	feminine	feminine	JJ	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	body	body	NN	O	12	appos
15	hugging	hug	VBG	O	9	xcomp
16	attire	attire	NN	O	15	dobj
17	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
18	shifted	shift	VBD	O	9	conj
19	to	to	TO	O	21	case
20	boxier	boxier	JJR	O	21	amod
21	cuts	cut	NNS	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	cuts	cut	NNS	O	6	nsubj
4	not	not	RB	O	5	dep
5	only	only	RB	O	6	advmod
6	showed	show	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	up	up	RP	O	6	compound:prt
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	form	form	NN	O	6	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	baggy	baggy	JJ	O	13	amod
13	tunics	tunic	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	10	punct
15	but	but	CC	O	10	cc
16	also	also	RB	O	19	advmod
17	in	in	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	form	form	NN	O	10	conj
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	manly	manly	JJ	O	22	amod
22	pantsuits	pantsuit	NNS	O	19	nmod
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
24	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	25	nummod
25	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	22	dep
26	for	for	IN	O	27	case
27	Women	Women	NNP	O	25	nmod
28	&	&	CC	O	27	cc
29	Girls	Girls	NNP	O	27	conj
30	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
31	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	revolutions	revolution	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	shocked	shock	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	people	people	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	society	society	NN	O	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	however	however	RB	O	14	advmod
11	it	it	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	long	long	JJ	O	4	parataxis
15	before	before	IN	O	17	case
16	almost	almost	RB	O	17	advmod
17	everyone	everyone	NN	O	14	nmod
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	1960	1960	CD	DATE	17	nmod
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	had	have	VBD	O	23	aux
23	adopted	adopt	VBN	O	20	acl:relcl
24	these	these	DT	O	26	det
25	new	new	JJ	O	26	amod
26	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	23	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	det
2	radical	radical	JJ	O	3	amod
3	changes	change	NNS	O	6	nsubj
4	in	in	IN	O	5	case
5	fashion	fashion	NN	O	3	nmod
6	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	about	about	IN	O	11	case
8	through	through	IN	O	11	case
9	two	two	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
10	particular	particular	JJ	O	11	amod
11	parties	party	NNS	O	6	nmod
12	;	;	:	O	11	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	youth	youth	NN	O	11	dep
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	1960	1960	CD	DATE	14	nmod
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
20	designers	designer	NNS	O	17	conj
21	in	in	IN	O	22	case
22	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	youth	youth	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	the	the	DT	O	2	nmod
5	1960	1960	CD	DATE	4	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	decided	decide	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
9	they	they	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	wanted	want	VBD	O	7	ccomp
11	their	they	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	ideas	idea	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
14	be	be	VB	O	15	auxpass
15	voiced	voice	VBN	O	10	advcl
16	,	,	,	O	7	punct
17	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
18	they	they	PRP	O	21	nsubj
19	did	do	VBD	O	21	aux
20	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
21	agree	agree	VB	O	7	conj
22	with	with	IN	O	25	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	previous	previous	JJ	O	25	amod
25	notion	notion	NN	O	21	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	time	time	NN	O	25	nmod
29	that	that	WDT	O	35	dobj
30	fashion	fashion	NN	O	35	nsubj
31	was	be	VBD	O	35	cop
32	only	only	RB	O	35	advmod
33	for	for	IN	O	35	case
34	the	the	DT	O	35	det
35	wealthy	wealthy	JJ	O	28	acl:relcl
36	and	and	CC	O	35	cc
37	elite	elite	NN	O	35	conj
38	of	of	IN	O	39	case
39	society	society	NN	O	37	nmod
40	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	41	punct
41	History	history	NN	O	28	dep
42	of	of	IN	O	44	case
43	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	44	nummod
44	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	41	nmod
45	and	and	CC	O	44	cc
46	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	44	conj
47	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	41	punct
48	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	they	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	inspired	inspire	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	push	push	NN	O	7	nmod:npmod
7	away	away	RB	O	4	advmod
8	from	from	IN	O	15	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	elites	elite	NNS	O	15	nmod:poss
11	'	'	POS	O	10	case
12	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	15	amod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	traditional	traditional	JJ	O	12	conj
15	ways	way	NNS	O	4	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	3	amod
3	party	party	NN	O	14	nsubj
4	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	effected	effect	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	change	change	NN	O	5	dobj
8	in	in	IN	O	11	case
9	1960	1960	CD	DATE	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	fashion	fashion	NN	O	5	nmod
12	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	designers	designer	NNS	O	0	ROOT
15	in	in	IN	O	16	case
16	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	designers	designer	NNS	O	4	nsubjpass
3	were	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	inspired	inspire	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	by	by	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	pop	pop	NN	O	8	compound
8	culture	culture	NN	O	4	nmod
9	occurring	occur	VBG	O	8	acl
10	around	around	IN	O	11	case
11	them	they	PRP	O	9	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	14	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	5	case
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	major	major	JJ	O	5	amod
5	influences	influence	NNS	O	1	nmod
6	on	on	IN	O	10	case
7	British	british	JJ	MISC	8	amod
8	designer	designer	NN	O	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	clothing	clothing	NN	O	5	nmod
11	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	mod	mod	NN	O	14	compound
14	look	look	NN	O	0	ROOT
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	look	look	NN	O	14	appos
18	consisting	consist	VBG	O	17	acl
19	of	of	IN	O	22	case
20	bold	bold	JJ	O	22	amod
21	geometric	geometric	JJ	O	22	amod
22	shapes	shape	NNS	O	18	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	designs	design	NNS	O	22	conj
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
26	History	history	NN	O	22	dep
27	of	of	IN	O	29	case
28	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	29	nummod
29	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	26	nmod
30	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
31	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	29	conj
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
33	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	3	compound
2	fashion	fashion	NN	O	3	compound
3	designers	designer	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	incorporated	incorporate	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	these	these	DT	O	9	det
6	bright	bright	JJ	O	9	amod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	bold	bold	JJ	O	6	conj
9	colors	color	NNS	O	4	dobj
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	shapes	shape	NNS	O	9	conj
12	with	with	IN	O	14	case
13	boxy	boxy	JJ	O	14	amod
14	cuts	cut	NNS	O	4	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	shorter	shorter	JJR	O	17	amod
17	hemlines	hemline	NNS	O	14	conj
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Soon	soon	RB	O	5	advmod
2	after	after	IN	O	5	mark
3	these	these	DT	O	4	det
4	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	5	nsubj
5	became	become	VBD	O	11	advcl
6	popular	popular	JJ	O	5	xcomp
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	11	punct
10	they	they	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	migrated	migrate	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	inspired	inspire	VBD	O	11	conj
14	designers	designer	NNS	O	13	dobj
15	in	in	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	13	nmod
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
20	History	history	NN	O	13	dep
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	23	nummod
23	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	20	nmod
24	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
25	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	23	conj
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
27	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	15	nsubj
2	did	do	VBD	O	1	acl:relcl
3	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
4	only	only	JJ	O	5	amod
5	change	change	NN	O	2	dobj
6	for	for	IN	O	7	case
7	women	woman	NNS	O	2	nmod
8	during	during	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	1960	1960	CD	DATE	2	nmod
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	,	,	,	O	10	punct
13	it	it	PRP	O	10	appos
14	also	also	RB	O	15	advmod
15	changed	change	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	dramatically	dramatically	RB	O	15	advmod
17	for	for	IN	O	18	case
18	men	man	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	``	``	``	O	4	punct
3	Peacock	Peacock	NNP	O	4	compound
4	Revolution	Revolution	NNP	O	10	nsubj
5	''	''	''	O	4	punct
6	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	10	det
8	major	major	JJ	O	10	amod
9	turning	turning	NN	O	10	compound
10	point	point	NN	O	0	ROOT
11	in	in	IN	O	14	case
12	men	man	NNS	O	14	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	fashion	fashion	NN	O	10	nmod
15	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	16	punct
16	History	history	NN	O	14	dep
17	of	of	IN	O	19	case
18	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	19	nummod
19	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	16	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	19	conj
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	16	punct
23	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	revolution	revolution	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	entailed	entail	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	designers	designer	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	adding	add	VBG	O	3	xcomp
6	color	color	NN	O	5	dobj
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	prints	print	NNS	O	6	conj
9	to	to	TO	O	12	case
10	men	man	NNS	O	12	nmod:poss
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	apparel	apparel	NN	O	5	nmod
13	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
14	History	history	NN	O	12	dep
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	17	nummod
17	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	14	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	17	conj
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Men	men	NN	O	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	shirts	shirt	NNS	O	9	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	pants	pants	NNS	O	3	appos
6	,	,	,	O	3	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
8	suits	suit	NNS	O	3	conj
9	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	embody	embody	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	color	color	NN	O	15	compound
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	bold	bold	JJ	O	12	conj
15	prints	print	NNS	O	11	dobj
16	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	change	change	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	6	case
4	men	man	NNS	O	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	clothing	clothing	NN	O	2	nmod
7	was	be	VBD	O	8	aux
8	groundbreaking	groundbreak	VBG	O	0	ROOT
9	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Prior	prior	RB	O	4	case
2	to	to	TO	O	1	mwe
3	this	this	DT	O	4	det
4	shift	shift	NN	O	9	nmod
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	style	style	NN	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	9	punct
8	men	man	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	worn	worn	JJ	O	12	amod
12	colors	color	NNS	O	9	dobj
13	other	other	JJ	O	15	case
14	than	than	IN	O	15	case
15	neutrals	neutral	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	19	case
17	over	over	IN	O	18	advmod
18	150	150	CD	DURATION	19	nummod
19	years	year	NNS	DURATION	15	nmod
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	History	history	NN	O	19	dep
22	of	of	IN	O	24	case
23	1960s	1960s	CD	DATE	24	nummod
24	Fashion	fashion	NN	O	21	nmod
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	Textiles	Textiles	NNP	O	24	conj
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
28	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	state	state	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	fashion	fashion	NN	O	4	nmod
7	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
8	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
10	premiered	premiere	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
11	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
12	signature	signature	NN	O	14	compound
13	shift	shift	NN	O	14	compound
14	dress	dress	NN	O	10	dobj
15	at	at	IN	O	18	case
16	her	she	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
17	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	FL	fl	NN	LOCATION	22	compound
21	lemonade	lemonade	NN	O	22	compound
22	stand	stand	NN	O	18	appos
23	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	lemonade	lemonade	NN	O	4	compound
4	stand	stand	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	would	would	MD	O	7	aux
6	eventually	eventually	RB	O	7	advmod
7	become	become	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	location	location	NN	O	7	xcomp
10	where	where	WRB	O	13	advmod
11	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	unintentionally	unintentionally	RB	O	13	advmod
13	became	become	VBD	O	7	advcl
14	famous	famous	JJ	O	13	xcomp
15	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	decided	decide	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	make	make	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	brightly	brightly	RB	O	7	advmod
7	colored	color	VBN	O	4	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	printed	print	VBN	O	7	acl
10	dress	dress	NN	O	9	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	hide	hide	VB	O	9	advcl
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	stains	stain	NNS	O	12	dobj
15	she	she	PRP	O	17	nsubj
16	continuously	continuously	RB	O	17	advmod
17	got	get	VBD	O	14	acl:relcl
18	on	on	IN	O	20	case
19	her	she	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	apron	apron	NN	O	17	nmod
21	from	from	IN	O	22	mark
22	making	make	VBG	O	17	advcl
23	juice	juice	NN	O	22	dobj
24	for	for	IN	O	27	case
25	her	she	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
26	lemonade	lemonade	NN	O	27	compound
27	stand	stand	NN	O	22	nmod
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	Bramlett	bramlett	NN	PERSON	27	appos
30	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
31	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	4	mark
2	her	she	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	juice	juice	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	stand	stand	VB	O	11	advcl
5	grew	grow	VBD	O	4	dep
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	popularity	popularity	NN	O	5	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	customers	customer	NNS	O	11	nsubj
11	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	notice	notice	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	her	she	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	new	new	JJ	O	16	amod
16	attire	attire	NN	O	13	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	women	woman	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	asking	ask	VBG	O	3	xcomp
5	about	about	IN	O	9	mark
6	where	where	WRB	O	9	advmod
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	dress	dress	NN	O	9	nsubj
9	came	come	VBD	O	4	advcl
10	from	from	IN	O	9	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	9	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
13	quickly	quickly	RB	O	17	advmod
14	after	after	IN	O	17	mark
15	everyone	everyone	NN	O	17	nsubj
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	aux
17	raving	rave	VBG	O	9	advcl
18	about	about	IN	O	19	case
19	it	it	PRP	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Soon	soon	RB	O	2	advmod
2	enough	enough	RB	O	6	advmod
3	,	,	,	O	6	punct
4	her	she	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	customers	customer	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	asking	ask	VBG	O	6	xcomp
8	her	she	PRP$	O	7	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	make	make	VB	O	7	xcomp
11	them	they	PRP	O	10	dobj
12	one	one	CD	NUMBER	6	nmod:tmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	which	which	WDT	O	15	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	12	acl:relcl
16	when	when	WRB	O	18	advmod
17	she	she	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	became	become	VBD	O	15	advcl
19	more	more	RBR	O	20	advmod
20	popular	popular	JJ	O	18	xcomp
21	for	for	IN	O	23	case
22	her	she	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	dresses	dress	NNS	O	20	nmod
24	then	then	RB	O	18	advmod
25	her	she	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
26	juice	juice	NN	O	24	nmod:npmod
27	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	28	punct
28	Bramlett	bramlett	NN	PERSON	26	appos
29	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	28	punct
30	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
3	official	official	JJ	O	4	amod
4	moment	moment	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	when	when	WRB	O	8	advmod
6	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nsubj
8	became	become	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	fashion	fashion	NN	O	11	compound
11	designer	designer	NN	O	8	xcomp
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
13	Our	we	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	Story	Story	NNP	O	11	dep
15	:	:	:	O	14	punct
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	dep
18	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	What	what	WDT	O	2	nsubj
2	started	start	VBD	O	15	csubj
3	out	out	RP	O	2	compound:prt
4	as	as	IN	O	13	mark
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	small	small	JJ	O	7	amod
7	business	business	NN	O	13	nsubj
8	at	at	IN	O	12	case
9	her	she	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
10	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
11	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
12	juice	juice	NN	O	7	nmod
13	stand	stand	VB	O	2	advcl
14	eventually	eventually	RB	O	13	advmod
15	flourished	flourish	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	into	into	IN	O	18	case
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	national	national	JJ	O	15	nmod
19	loved	love	VBD	O	18	acl
20	corporation	corporation	NN	O	19	dobj
21	in	in	IN	O	22	case
22	1959	1959	CD	DATE	19	nmod
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
24	Our	we	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	Story	Story	NNP	O	19	dep
26	:	:	:	O	25	punct
27	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	28	compound
28	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	dep
29	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
30	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	designs	design	NNS	O	6	nsubj
5	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	6	advmod
6	struck	strike	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	fame	fame	NN	O	6	dobj
8	when	when	WRB	O	11	advmod
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	college	college	NN	O	11	nsubj
11	best	best	JJS	O	6	advcl
12	friend	friend	NN	O	14	compound
13	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
15	wore	wear	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
16	them	they	PRP	O	15	dobj
17	in	in	IN	O	21	case
18	a	a	DT	O	21	det
19	LIFE	LIFE	NNP	O	21	compound
20	magazine	magazine	NN	O	21	compound
21	cover	cover	NN	O	15	nmod
22	in	in	IN	O	23	case
23	1962	1962	CD	DATE	15	nmod
24	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
25	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	11	dep
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
27	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	grabbed	grab	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	public	public	NN	O	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	attention	attention	NN	O	3	dobj
8	instantly	instantly	RB	O	3	advmod
9	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Her	she	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
2	high	high	JJ	O	4	amod
3	social	social	JJ	O	4	amod
4	status	status	NN	O	17	nsubj
5	as	as	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	8	amod
8	lady	lady	NN	O	4	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	her	she	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
11	high	high	JJ	O	12	amod
12	respect	respect	NN	O	8	conj
13	as	as	IN	O	16	case
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	fashion	fashion	NN	O	16	compound
16	icon	icon	NN	O	12	nmod
17	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
18	her	she	PRP$	O	17	dep
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	perfect	perfect	JJ	O	21	amod
21	person	person	NN	O	17	dobj
22	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
23	publically	publically	RB	O	24	advmod
24	debut	debut	VB	O	21	acl
25	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	29	nmod:poss
26	's	's	POS	O	25	case
27	classic	classic	JJ	O	29	amod
28	shift	shift	NN	O	29	compound
29	dress	dress	NN	O	24	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	stopped	stop	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	wearing	wear	VBG	O	2	xcomp
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	typical	typical	JJ	O	3	iobj
6	1950	1950	CD	DATE	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	trends	trend	NNS	O	3	dobj
9	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	strayed	stray	VBD	O	19	dep
3	away	away	RB	O	2	advmod
4	from	from	IN	O	6	case
5	formal	formal	JJ	O	6	amod
6	dresses	dress	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	hats	hat	NNS	O	6	conj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	gloves	glove	NNS	O	6	conj
11	,	,	,	O	6	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
13	long	long	RB	O	14	advmod
14	hemlines	hemline	NNS	O	6	conj
15	,	,	,	O	6	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	turn	turn	NN	O	6	conj
19	favored	favor	VBD	O	0	ROOT
20	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nsubj
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	more	more	JJR	O	21	amod
24	casual	casual	JJ	O	21	amod
25	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
26	simple	simple	JJ	O	27	amod
27	designs	design	NNS	O	21	conj
28	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	case
2	a	a	DT	O	3	det
3	result	result	NN	O	7	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	7	punct
5	American	american	JJ	MISC	6	amod
6	women	woman	NNS	O	7	nsubj
7	followed	follow	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	her	she	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	lead	lead	NN	O	7	dobj
10	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	11	punct
11	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	9	appos
12	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	11	punct
13	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	2	nsubj
2	raved	rave	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	about	about	IN	O	7	case
4	Jackie	Jackie	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	dress	dress	NN	O	2	nmod
8	soon	soon	RB	O	13	advmod
9	after	after	IN	O	13	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	magazine	magazine	NN	O	13	nsubjpass
12	was	be	VBD	O	13	auxpass
13	released	release	VBN	O	2	advcl
14	,	,	,	O	2	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	18	nsubj
18	became	become	VBD	O	2	conj
19	recognized	recognize	VBN	O	18	xcomp
20	as	as	IN	O	22	case
21	a	a	DT	O	22	det
22	designer	designer	NN	O	19	nmod
23	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
24	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	22	appos
25	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Women	woman	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	loved	love	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	combination	combination	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	comfort	comfort	NN	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	femininity	femininity	NN	O	6	conj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
11	color	color	NN	O	6	conj
12	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubjpass
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	embodied	embody	VBN	O	6	acl:relcl
15	in	in	IN	O	19	case
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	designs	design	NNS	O	14	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	which	which	WDT	O	22	nsubj
22	began	begin	VBD	O	19	acl:relcl
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	phenomenon	phenomenon	NN	O	22	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	loud	loud	JJ	O	5	amod
5	prints	print	NNS	O	9	nsubj
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	bold	bold	JJ	O	8	amod
8	colors	color	NNS	O	5	conj
9	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	pop	pop	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	up	up	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	all	all	DT	O	11	dobj
14	over	over	IN	O	15	case
15	1960	1960	CD	DATE	13	nmod
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
18	1970	1970	CD	DATE	20	nmod:poss
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	fashion	fashion	NN	O	13	conj
21	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	helped	help	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	bring	bring	VB	O	2	xcomp
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	new	new	JJ	O	3	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	casual	casual	JJ	O	5	conj
8	,	,	,	O	5	punct
9	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
10	weather	weather	NN	O	12	compound
11	appropriate	appropriate	JJ	O	12	amod
12	look	look	NN	O	5	conj
13	to	to	TO	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	women	woman	NNS	O	3	nmod
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	1960	1960	CD	DATE	15	nmod
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Livingston	Livingston	NNP	PERSON	18	appos
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Women	woman	NNS	O	4	nsubj
2	were	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	awe	awe	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	by	by	IN	O	8	case
6	this	this	DT	O	8	det
7	new	new	JJ	O	8	amod
8	look	look	NN	O	4	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
11	instantly	instantly	RB	O	13	advmod
12	everyone	everyone	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	wanted	want	VBD	O	4	conj
14	one	one	CD	NUMBER	13	dobj
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod:poss
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	designs	design	NNS	O	14	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	7	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	6	case
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	main	main	JJ	O	6	amod
5	reasons	reason	NNS	O	6	compound
6	women	woman	NNS	O	1	nmod
7	wanted	want	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	a	a	DT	O	11	det
9	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	11	compound
10	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	11	compound
11	design	design	NN	O	16	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	16	cop
13	because	because	IN	O	16	case
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	their	they	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	exclusivity	exclusivity	NN	O	7	ccomp
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	PERSON	16	appos
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
20	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	2	case
2	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	9	advcl
3	,	,	,	O	9	punct
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	designs	design	NNS	O	9	nsubjpass
7	were	be	VBD	O	9	auxpass
8	only	only	RB	O	9	advmod
9	sold	sell	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	case
11	celebrities	celebrity	NNS	O	9	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	extreme	extreme	JJ	O	15	amod
15	elite	elite	NN	O	11	conj
16	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
17	Our	we	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	Story	Story	NNP	O	15	dep
19	:	:	:	O	18	punct
20	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	dep
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
23	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Families	family	NNS	O	19	nsubj
2	such	such	JJ	O	5	case
3	as	as	IN	O	2	mwe
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	Vanderbilts	Vanderbilts	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	1	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	Rockefellers	Rockefellers	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	5	conj
9	,	,	,	O	5	punct
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	Whitneys	Whitneys	NNP	MISC	5	conj
12	,	,	,	O	5	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	Kennedys	Kennedys	NNPS	PERSON	5	conj
16	were	be	VBD	O	19	cop
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	only	only	JJ	O	19	amod
19	ones	one	NNS	O	0	ROOT
20	who	who	WP	O	22	nsubj
21	could	could	MD	O	22	aux
22	afford	afford	VB	O	19	acl:relcl
23	her	she	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
24	clothing	clothing	NN	O	22	dobj
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
26	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	LOCATION	24	appos
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
28	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	7	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	over	over	IN	O	4	case
4	time	time	NN	O	7	nmod
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	brand	brand	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	less	less	RBR	O	9	advmod
9	exclusive	exclusive	JJ	O	7	xcomp
10	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
11	trickled	trickle	VBD	O	7	conj
12	down	down	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	to	to	TO	O	14	case
14	those	those	DT	O	11	nmod
15	who	who	WP	O	16	nsubj
16	had	have	VBD	O	14	acl:relcl
17	wealth	wealth	NN	O	16	dobj
18	,	,	,	O	16	punct
19	but	but	CC	O	16	cc
20	were	be	VBD	O	24	cop
21	not	not	RB	O	24	neg
22	necessarily	necessarily	RB	O	24	advmod
23	American	american	JJ	MISC	24	amod
24	icons	icon	NNS	O	16	conj
25	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	admiration	admiration	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	for	for	IN	O	4	case
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	quickly	quickly	RB	O	6	advmod
6	spread	spread	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	people	people	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	began	begin	VBD	O	6	conj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	recognize	recognize	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	value	value	NN	O	11	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	status	status	NN	O	13	conj
16	a	a	DT	O	19	det
17	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	19	compound
18	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	19	compound
19	design	design	NN	O	20	nsubj
20	held	hold	VBD	O	13	acl:relcl
21	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	woman	woman	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	wearing	wear	VBG	O	2	acl
4	a	a	DT	O	7	det
5	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	7	compound
6	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	7	compound
7	dress	dress	NN	O	3	dobj
8	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
9	instantly	instantly	RB	O	10	advmod
10	deemed	deem	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	be	be	VB	O	10	dep
12	well	well	RB	O	13	advmod
13	off	off	RB	O	11	advmod
14	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	recognition	recognition	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	with	with	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	brand	brand	NN	O	3	nmod
7	because	because	IN	O	10	case
8	of	of	IN	O	7	mwe
9	its	its	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	exclusivity	exclusivity	NN	O	3	nmod
11	when	when	WRB	O	13	advmod
12	it	it	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	began	begin	VBD	O	10	acl:relcl
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	1960	1960	CD	DATE	13	nmod
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	19	punct
19	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	LOCATION	16	appos
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	19	punct
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	brand	brand	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
4	always	always	RB	O	6	advmod
5	most	most	RBS	O	6	advmod
6	popular	popular	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	9	compound
9	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	FL	fl	NN	LOCATION	9	appos
12	because	because	IN	O	16	mark
13	it	it	PRP	O	16	nsubj
14	was	be	VBD	O	16	cop
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	location	location	NN	O	6	advcl
17	where	where	WRB	O	22	advmod
18	the	the	DT	O	21	det
19	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
20	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	brand	brand	NN	O	22	nsubj
22	originated	originate	VBD	O	16	acl:relcl
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Owning	own	VBG	O	9	csubj
2	a	a	DT	O	5	det
3	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
4	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	design	design	NN	O	1	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
8	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
9	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	right	right	NN	O	9	xcomp
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	passage	passage	NN	O	11	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	9	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
16	over	over	IN	O	17	case
17	time	time	NN	O	21	nmod
18	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	21	nsubjpass
20	was	be	VBD	O	21	auxpass
21	deemed	deem	VBN	O	9	conj
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	``	``	``	O	24	punct
24	uniform	uniform	JJ	O	21	dobj
25	''	''	''	O	24	punct
26	of	of	IN	O	27	case
27	those	those	DT	O	24	nmod
28	who	who	WP	O	29	nsubj
29	vacationed	vacation	VBD	O	27	acl:relcl
30	in	in	IN	O	32	case
31	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	32	compound
32	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	29	nmod
33	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
34	Norwich	Norwich	NNP	LOCATION	32	appos
35	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
36	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	nickname	nickname	NN	O	12	nsubj
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
5	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	brand	brand	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	quickly	quickly	RB	O	8	advmod
8	adopted	adopt	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
9	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	``	``	``	O	12	punct
12	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	0	ROOT
13	.	.	.	O	12	punct
14	''	''	''	O	12	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	``	``	``	O	3	punct
3	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	7	nsubj
4	''	''	''	O	3	punct
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	nickname	nickname	NN	O	0	ROOT
8	for	for	IN	O	9	case
9	one	one	CD	NUMBER	7	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	15	case
11	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	famous	famous	JJ	O	15	amod
15	sundresses	sundress	NNS	O	7	nmod
16	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	17	punct
17	Langer	langer	NN	ORGANIZATION	15	appos
18	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	17	punct
19	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	nickname	nickname	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	4	advmod
4	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	1959	1959	CD	DATE	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	4	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
9	continued	continue	VBD	O	4	conj
10	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
11	be	be	VB	O	13	auxpass
12	commonly	commonly	RB	O	13	advmod
13	used	use	VBN	O	9	xcomp
14	until	until	IN	O	16	case
15	present	present	JJ	DATE	16	amod
16	day	day	NN	DURATION	13	nmod
17	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	18	punct
18	Langer	langer	NN	O	16	appos
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	18	punct
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Additionally	additionally	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	you	you	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
5	hear	hear	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	people	people	NNS	O	7	nsubj
7	refer	refer	VB	O	5	ccomp
8	to	to	TO	O	9	case
9	all	all	DT	O	7	nmod
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	12	nsubj
12	designs	design	VBZ	O	9	acl:relcl
13	as	as	IN	O	15	case
14	``	``	``	O	15	punct
15	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	12	nmod
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct
18	''	''	''	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	term	term	NN	O	4	amod
3	``	``	``	O	4	punct
4	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	0	ROOT
5	's	's	POS	O	4	dep
6	''	''	''	O	4	punct
7	refer	refer	VB	O	4	dep
8	to	to	TO	O	10	case
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	bunch	bunch	NN	O	7	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	designs	design	NNS	O	7	nmod
13	or	or	CC	O	12	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	brand	brand	NN	O	12	conj
16	as	as	IN	O	18	case
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	whole	whole	JJ	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	12	punct
20	rather	rather	RB	O	12	cc
21	than	than	IN	O	20	mwe
22	one	one	CD	NUMBER	23	nummod
23	design	design	NN	O	12	conj
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	particular	particular	JJ	O	23	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	terms	term	NNS	O	4	nsubjpass
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	auxpass
4	used	use	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	by	by	IN	O	6	case
6	those	those	DT	O	4	nmod
7	well	well	RB	O	8	advmod
8	versed	verse	VBN	O	6	acl
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	fashion	fashion	NN	O	11	compound
11	designers	designer	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	brands	brand	NNS	O	11	conj
14	,	,	,	O	11	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	course	course	NN	O	11	conj
18	by	by	IN	O	20	case
19	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
20	lovers	lover	NNS	O	8	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	unique	unique	JJ	O	3	amod
3	thing	thing	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	about	about	IN	O	7	case
5	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	7	compound
6	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	7	compound
7	clothing	clothing	NN	O	3	nmod
8	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	how	how	WRB	O	12	advmod
10	people	people	NNS	O	12	nsubj
11	instantly	instantly	RB	O	12	advmod
12	recognize	recognize	VBP	O	8	ccomp
13	it	it	PRP	O	12	dobj
14	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	bold	bold	JJ	O	5	amod
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	vibrant	vibrant	JJ	O	5	amod
5	colors	color	NNS	O	13	nsubj
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	repetitive	repetitive	JJ	O	8	amod
8	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	5	conj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	prints	print	NNS	O	8	conj
11	are	be	VBP	O	13	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	trademark	trademark	NN	O	0	ROOT
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	brand	brand	NN	O	13	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubjpass
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	auxpass
4	best	best	RB	O	5	advmod
5	known	know	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	for	for	IN	O	8	case
7	its	its	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	whimsical	whimsical	JJ	O	5	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	tropical	tropical	JJ	O	11	amod
11	prints	print	NNS	O	8	conj
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
13	Bramlett	bramlett	NN	PERSON	8	appos
14	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	such	such	JJ	O	2	xcomp
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	wide	wide	JJ	O	6	amod
6	variety	variety	NN	O	9	dep
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	prints	print	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	she	she	PRP	O	3	ccomp
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	her	she	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	designers	designer	NNS	O	14	nsubj
13	have	have	VBP	O	14	aux
14	created	create	VBN	O	9	conj
15	over	over	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	DURATION	17	det
17	years	year	NNS	DURATION	14	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	14	punct
19	ranging	range	VBG	O	14	xcomp
20	from	from	IN	O	21	case
21	floral	floral	JJ	O	19	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	23	case
23	animal	animal	NN	O	21	nmod
24	to	to	TO	O	25	case
25	beach	beach	NN	O	19	nmod
26	to	to	TO	O	27	case
27	shapes	shape	NNS	O	19	nmod
28	to	to	TO	O	29	case
29	lines	line	NNS	O	27	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Each	each	DT	O	5	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	these	these	DT	O	4	det
4	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	a	a	DT	O	9	det
7	specific	specific	JJ	O	9	amod
8	color	color	NN	O	9	compound
9	scheme	scheme	NN	O	5	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	go	go	VB	O	9	acl
12	along	along	RP	O	11	compound:prt
13	with	with	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	prints	print	NNS	O	16	compound
16	theme	theme	NN	O	11	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	15	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	15	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	most	most	RBS	O	5	advmod
5	popular	popular	JJ	O	15	nsubj
6	or	or	CC	O	5	cc
7	recognized	recognize	VBN	O	8	amod
8	colors	color	NNS	O	5	conj
9	of	of	IN	O	13	case
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
12	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	brand	brand	NN	O	5	nmod
14	are	be	VBP	O	15	cop
15	pink	pink	JJ	O	0	ROOT
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	green	green	JJ	O	15	conj
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	19	punct
19	Hagwood	hagwood	NN	LOCATION	15	dep
20	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	19	punct
21	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	most	most	RBS	O	4	advmod
4	well	well	RB	O	5	advmod
5	known	know	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	for	for	IN	O	8	case
7	these	these	DT	O	8	det
8	colors	color	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	because	because	IN	O	13	case
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	13	amod
13	feel	feel	NN	O	5	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	5	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
16	have	have	VBP	O	5	conj
17	fact	fact	NN	O	16	dobj
18	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
19	they	they	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	became	become	VBD	O	17	dep
21	a	a	DT	O	23	det
22	``	``	``	O	23	punct
23	banner	banner	NN	O	20	xcomp
24	of	of	IN	O	29	case
25	the	the	DT	O	29	det
26	authentic	authentic	JJ	O	29	amod
27	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	29	compound
28	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	29	compound
29	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	23	nmod
30	''	''	''	O	23	punct
31	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	32	punct
32	Hagwood	Hagwood	NNP	LOCATION	23	appos
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	32	punct
34	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	constantly	constantly	RB	O	5	advmod
5	refreshing	refresh	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	their	they	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	look	look	NN	O	5	dobj
8	with	with	IN	O	10	case
9	new	new	JJ	O	10	amod
10	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	5	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	prints	print	NNS	O	10	conj
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	making	make	VBG	O	5	dep
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	brand	brand	NN	O	14	dobj
17	fresh	fresh	JJ	O	16	amod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	new	new	JJ	O	17	conj
20	each	each	DT	O	21	det
21	season	season	NN	O	14	nmod:tmod
22	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
23	Our	we	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
24	Story	Story	NNP	O	14	dep
25	:	:	:	O	24	punct
26	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	compound
27	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	dep
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
29	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	3	det
2	contributing	contribute	VBG	O	3	amod
3	factor	factor	NN	O	16	nsubj
4	to	to	TO	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	instantaneous	instantaneous	JJ	O	7	amod
7	recognition	recognition	NN	O	3	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	12	case
9	a	a	DT	O	12	det
10	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	12	compound
11	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	12	compound
12	design	design	NN	O	7	nmod
13	are	be	VBP	O	16	cop
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	clean-cut	clean-cut	JJ	O	16	amod
16	lines	line	NNS	O	0	ROOT
17	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	5	amod
3	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	O	5	compound
4	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	O	5	compound
5	design	design	NN	O	9	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	shift	shift	NN	O	9	compound
9	dress	dress	NN	O	0	ROOT
10	;	;	:	O	9	punct
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	boxy	boxy	JJ	O	13	amod
13	cut	cut	NN	O	9	dep
14	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubj
15	does	do	VBZ	O	17	aux
16	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
17	cling	cling	VB	O	13	acl:relcl
18	to	to	TO	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	body	body	NN	O	17	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	17	punct
22	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
23	instead	instead	RB	O	24	advmod
24	hangs	hang	VBZ	O	17	conj
25	off	off	RP	O	24	compound:prt
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	body	body	NN	O	24	dobj
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	27	appos
30	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
31	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	det
2	straight-cut	straight-cut	JJ	O	3	amod
3	silhouette	silhouette	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	shift	shift	NN	O	7	compound
7	dress	dress	NN	O	3	nmod
8	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	what	what	WP	O	11	nsubj
10	first	first	RB	ORDINAL	11	advmod
11	set	set	VBD	O	8	ccomp
12	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	dobj
14	apart	apart	RB	O	11	advmod
15	from	from	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	fashions	fashion	NNS	O	11	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	1950	1950	CD	DATE	17	nmod
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	,	,	,	O	20	punct
23	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
24	what	what	WP	O	26	nsubj
25	originally	originally	RB	O	26	advmod
26	sparked	spark	VBD	O	20	conj
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	interest	interest	NN	O	26	dobj
29	of	of	IN	O	31	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	women	woman	NNS	O	28	nmod
32	of	of	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	O	34	det
34	time	time	NN	O	31	nmod
35	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	36	punct
36	Livingston	livingston	NN	PERSON	34	appos
37	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	36	punct
38	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	brand	brand	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	still	still	RB	O	4	advmod
4	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	dresses	dress	NNS	O	4	dobj
6	that	that	WDT	O	7	nsubj
7	follow	follow	VBP	O	5	acl:relcl
8	the	the	DT	O	11	det
9	classic	classic	JJ	O	11	amod
10	shift	shift	NN	O	11	compound
11	silhouette	silhouette	NN	O	7	dobj
12	,	,	,	O	4	punct
13	however	however	RB	O	15	advmod
14	there	there	EX	O	15	expl
15	are	be	VBP	O	4	parataxis
16	other	other	JJ	O	17	amod
17	styles	style	NNS	O	15	nsubj
18	as	as	RB	O	15	advmod
19	well	well	RB	O	18	mwe
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Today	today	NN	DATE	4	nmod:tmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	there	there	EX	O	4	expl
4	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	variety	variety	NN	O	4	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	styles	style	NNS	O	6	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	10	mark
10	including	include	VBG	O	8	acl
11	halter	halter	NN	O	10	dobj
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	sleeveless	sleeveless	JJ	O	11	amod
14	,	,	,	O	11	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
16	sleeved	sleeved	JJ	O	17	amod
17	dresses	dress	NNS	O	11	conj
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	15	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	15	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	one	one	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	thing	thing	NN	O	15	nsubj
6	all	all	DT	O	9	advmod
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	these	these	DT	O	9	det
9	dresses	dress	NNS	O	5	nmod
10	have	have	VBP	O	15	aux
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	common	common	JJ	O	15	nmod
13	are	be	VBP	O	15	cop
14	their	they	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	clean-cut	clean-cut	JJ	O	0	ROOT
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	18	amod
18	lines	line	NNS	O	15	conj
19	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	dresses	dress	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	typically	typically	RB	O	4	advmod
4	fall	fall	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	right	right	RB	O	4	advmod
6	above	above	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	knee	knee	NN	O	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
11	do	do	VBP	O	4	conj
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	hug	hug	NN	O	11	dobj
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	body	body	NN	O	11	nsubj
16	too	too	RB	O	17	advmod
17	closely	closely	RB	O	15	advmod
18	from	from	IN	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	waist	waist	NN	O	21	nmod:npmod
21	down	down	RB	O	17	advcl
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	5	advmod
2	though	though	IN	O	5	mark
3	styles	style	NNS	O	5	nsubj
4	have	have	VBP	O	5	aux
5	evolved	evolve	VBN	O	14	csubj
6	since	since	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	1960	1960	CD	DATE	5	nmod
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	,	,	,	O	8	punct
11	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	appos
13	has	have	VBZ	O	14	aux
14	stayed	stay	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	true	true	JJ	O	14	xcomp
16	to	to	TO	O	21	case
17	her	she	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
18	classic	classic	JJ	O	21	amod
19	,	,	,	O	21	punct
20	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	21	amod
21	look	look	NN	O	15	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	while	while	IN	O	25	mark
24	still	still	RB	O	25	advmod
25	remaining	remain	VBG	O	21	dep
26	current	current	JJ	DATE	25	xcomp
27	in	in	IN	O	29	case
28	her	she	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	designs	design	NNS	O	26	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	last	last	JJ	O	4	amod
3	contributing	contributing	JJ	O	4	amod
4	factor	factor	NN	O	14	nsubj
5	to	to	TO	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	look	look	NN	O	4	nmod
9	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
10	its	its	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
11	``	``	``	O	14	punct
12	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	14	amod
13	''	''	''	O	14	punct
14	feel	feel	NN	O	0	ROOT
15	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Bright	bright	JJ	O	2	amod
2	colors	color	NNS	O	12	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	statement	statement	NN	O	5	compound
5	prints	print	NNS	O	2	conj
6	,	,	,	O	2	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
8	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	9	amod
9	silhouettes	silhouette	NNS	O	2	conj
10	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	recipe	recipe	NN	O	0	ROOT
13	for	for	IN	O	17	case
14	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	nmod:poss
15	's	's	POS	O	14	case
16	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	17	amod
17	look	look	NN	O	12	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	polo	polo	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
5	another	another	DT	O	6	det
6	piece	piece	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	her	she	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	collection	collection	NN	O	6	nmod
10	that	that	IN	O	11	nsubj
11	fits	fit	VBZ	O	6	acl:relcl
12	perfectly	perfectly	RB	O	11	advmod
13	into	into	IN	O	16	case
14	this	this	DT	O	16	det
15	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	16	amod
16	mold	mold	NN	O	11	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Part	part	NN	O	9	nsubjpass
2	of	of	IN	O	7	case
3	the	the	DT	O	7	det
4	reason	reason	NN	O	7	compound
5	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
6	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	clothing	clothing	NN	O	1	nmod
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	auxpass
9	deemed	deem	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	``	``	``	O	11	punct
11	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	9	xcomp
12	''	''	''	O	11	punct
13	is	be	VBZ	O	11	ccomp
14	because	because	IN	O	22	mark
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	market	market	NN	O	22	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	19	case
19	people	people	NNS	O	17	nmod
20	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
21	was	be	VBD	O	22	aux
22	trying	try	VBG	O	13	advcl
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	attract	attract	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	when	when	WRB	O	28	advmod
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	brand	brand	NN	O	28	nsubj
28	originated	originate	VBD	O	24	advcl
29	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubj
3	herself	herself	PRP	O	2	nmod:npmod
4	grew	grow	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	up	up	RP	O	4	compound:prt
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	wealth	wealth	NN	O	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	4	punct
9	attending	attend	VBG	O	4	ccomp
10	private	private	JJ	O	11	amod
11	school	school	NN	O	9	dobj
12	,	,	,	O	9	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
14	eventually	eventually	RB	O	15	advmod
15	marrying	marry	VBG	O	9	conj
16	into	into	IN	O	20	case
17	the	the	DT	O	20	det
18	elite	elite	NN	O	20	compound
19	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	MISC	20	compound
20	family	family	NN	O	15	nmod
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	22	punct
22	Langer	langer	NN	PERSON	20	appos
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	22	punct
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	background	background	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	social	social	JJ	O	6	amod
6	circle	circle	NN	O	3	conj
7	helps	help	VBZ	O	18	dep
8	explain	explain	VB	O	7	xcomp
9	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	style	style	NN	O	8	dobj
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	type	type	NN	O	10	conj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	market	market	NN	O	13	nmod
16	she	she	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	18	aux
18	aiming	aim	VBG	O	0	ROOT
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	attract	attract	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	when	when	WRB	O	22	advmod
22	shaping	shape	VBG	O	20	advcl
23	her	she	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
24	brand	brand	NN	O	22	dobj
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	clothing	clothing	NN	O	24	conj
27	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	overarching	overarching	JJ	O	3	amod
3	theme	theme	NN	O	14	nsubj
4	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	pulls	pull	VBZ	O	3	acl:relcl
6	the	the	DT	O	9	det
7	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
8	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	brand	brand	NN	O	5	dobj
10	together	together	RB	O	14	advmod
11	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	14	det
13	carefree	carefree	JJ	O	14	amod
14	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	0	ROOT
15	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	created	create	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	her	she	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	brand	brand	NN	O	3	dobj
6	with	with	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	image	image	NN	O	3	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	luxury	luxury	NN	O	8	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	whimsy	whimsy	NN	O	10	conj
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	painted	paint	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	picture	picture	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	4	nmod
8	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
9	people	people	NNS	O	10	nsubj
10	desired	desire	VBN	O	2	ccomp
11	in	in	IN	O	14	case
12	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
13	resort-inspired	resort-inspired	JJ	O	14	amod
14	clothing	clothing	NN	O	10	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	bright	bright	JJ	O	3	amod
3	colors	color	NNS	O	11	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	tropical	tropical	JJ	O	6	amod
6	prints	print	NNS	O	3	conj
7	,	,	,	O	3	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
9	bold	bold	JJ	O	10	amod
10	patterns	pattern	NNS	O	3	conj
11	brought	bring	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	people	people	NNS	O	13	nsubj
13	closer	closer	JJR	O	11	xcomp
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	living	live	VBG	O	13	advcl
16	the	the	DT	O	21	det
17	carefree	carefree	JJ	O	21	amod
18	,	,	,	O	21	punct
19	Palm	Palm	NNP	LOCATION	20	compound
20	Beach	Beach	NNP	LOCATION	21	dep
21	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	15	dobj
22	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Lilly	Lilly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Pulitzer	Pulitzer	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	her	she	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	mark	mark	NN	O	3	dobj
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	fashion	fashion	NN	O	3	nmod
8	by	by	IN	O	9	mark
9	creating	create	VBG	O	3	advcl
10	unique	unique	JJ	O	11	amod
11	clothing	clothing	NN	O	9	dobj
12	that	that	WDT	O	13	nsubj
13	stands	stand	VBZ	O	11	acl:relcl
14	out	out	RP	O	13	compound:prt
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	brought	bring	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	new	new	JJ	O	5	amod
5	twist	twist	NN	O	2	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	case
7	preppy	preppy	JJ	O	2	advcl
8	,	,	,	O	2	punct
9	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
10	created	create	VBD	O	2	conj
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	lifestyle	lifestyle	NN	O	13	compound
13	brand	brand	NN	O	10	dobj
14	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
15	people	people	NNS	O	16	nsubj
16	wanted	want	VBD	O	10	ccomp
17	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
18	be	be	VB	O	20	cop
19	apart	apart	RB	O	20	advmod
20	of	of	IN	O	16	xcomp
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

