1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	essay	essay	NN	O	26	nsubj
3	``	``	``	O	7	punct
4	White	White	NNP	O	7	dep
5	Until	until	IN	O	4	dep
6	Proven	Proven	NNP	O	7	compound
7	Black	Black	NNP	O	14	nsubj
8	''	''	''	O	7	punct
9	by	by	IN	O	11	case
10	Anna	Anna	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod
12	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	reaction	reaction	NN	O	2	acl:relcl
15	to	to	TO	O	16	case
16	events	event	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	that	that	WDT	O	18	nsubj
18	follows	follow	VBZ	O	16	acl:relcl
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	release	release	NN	O	18	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	The	the	DT	O	24	det
23	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	MISC	24	compound
24	Games	Games	NNPS	MISC	20	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	26	punct
26	based	base	VBN	O	0	ROOT
27	on	on	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	trilogy	trilogy	NN	O	26	nmod
30	by	by	IN	O	32	case
31	Suzanne	Suzanne	NNP	PERSON	32	compound
32	Collins	Collins	NNP	PERSON	26	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	26	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	essay	essay	NN	O	5	nmod
4	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	tells	tell	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	story	story	NN	O	5	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	13	case
9	a	a	DT	O	13	det
10	twenty-nine	twenty-nine	CD	DURATION	11	nummod
11	year	year	NN	DURATION	12	nmod:npmod
12	old	old	JJ	DURATION	13	amod
13	man	man	NN	O	7	nmod
14	named	name	VBN	O	13	acl
15	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	14	dobj
16	,	,	,	O	14	punct
17	from	from	IN	O	18	case
18	Canada	Canada	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	who	who	WP	O	21	nsubj
21	came	come	VBD	O	18	acl:relcl
22	across	across	IN	O	24	case
23	a	a	DT	O	24	det
24	string	string	NN	O	21	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	negative	negative	JJ	O	27	amod
27	remarks	remark	NNS	O	24	nmod
28	concerning	concern	VBG	O	30	case
29	two	two	CD	NUMBER	30	nummod
30	characters	character	NNS	O	27	nmod
31	in	in	IN	O	34	case
32	The	the	DT	O	34	det
33	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	MISC	34	compound
34	Games	Games	NNPS	MISC	30	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	During	during	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	essay	essay	NN	O	21	nmod
4	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
5	also	also	RB	O	6	advmod
6	touches	touch	NNS	O	21	nsubj
7	on	on	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	idea	idea	NN	O	6	nmod
10	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
11	many	many	JJ	O	12	amod
12	people	people	NNS	O	13	nsubj
13	read	read	VBP	O	9	dep
14	text	text	NN	O	13	dobj
15	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
16	,	,	,	O	13	punct
17	unless	unless	IN	O	18	mark
18	specified	specify	VBN	O	13	dep
19	,	,	,	O	6	punct
20	will	will	MD	O	21	aux
21	assume	assume	VB	O	0	ROOT
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	race	race	NN	O	21	dobj
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	a	a	DT	O	26	det
26	character	character	NN	O	23	nmod
27	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
28	be	be	VB	O	29	cop
29	white	white	JJ	O	26	acl
30	as	as	IN	O	31	case
31	opposed	oppose	VBN	O	29	advcl
32	to	to	TO	O	35	case
33	any	any	DT	O	35	det
34	other	other	JJ	O	35	amod
35	ethnicity	ethnicity	NN	O	31	advcl
36	,	,	,	O	35	punct
37	despite	despite	IN	O	39	case
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	ethnicity	ethnicity	NN	O	35	nmod
40	of	of	IN	O	42	case
41	the	the	DT	O	42	det
42	reader	reader	NN	O	39	nmod
43	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	2	mark
2	analyzing	analyze	VBG	O	12	advcl
3	the	the	DT	O	6	det
4	three	three	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
5	main	main	JJ	O	6	amod
6	components	component	NNS	O	2	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	rhetoric	rhetoric	NN	O	6	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	12	punct
10	we	we	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
12	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
13	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
14	all	all	DT	O	15	det
15	three	three	CD	NUMBER	19	nsubj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	these	these	DT	O	18	det
18	elements	element	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	played	play	VBD	O	12	ccomp
20	key	key	JJ	O	21	amod
21	roles	role	NNS	O	19	dobj
22	in	in	IN	O	23	mark
23	giving	give	VBG	O	19	advcl
24	significance	significance	NN	O	23	dobj
25	to	to	TO	O	27	case
26	this	this	DT	O	27	det
27	issue	issue	NN	O	23	nmod
28	,	,	,	O	19	punct
29	giving	give	VBG	O	19	advcl
30	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	32	compound
31	justifiable	justifiable	JJ	O	32	amod
32	reason	reason	NN	O	29	dobj
33	to	to	TO	O	34	mark
34	take	take	VB	O	32	acl
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	action	action	NN	O	34	dobj
37	that	that	IN	O	39	mark
38	he	he	PRP	O	39	nsubj
39	did	do	VBD	O	34	ccomp
40	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	4	amod
3	main	main	JJ	O	4	amod
4	element	element	NN	O	11	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	rhetoric	rhetoric	NN	O	4	nmod
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	this	this	DT	O	9	det
9	situation	situation	NN	O	6	nmod
10	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
11	context	context	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	this	this	DT	O	4	det
3	critical	critical	JJ	O	4	amod
4	situation	situation	NN	O	15	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	15	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	context	context	NN	O	15	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	15	cop
9	,	,	,	O	15	punct
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	sense	sense	NN	O	15	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	cause	cause	NN	O	0	ROOT
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	exigence	exigence	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	across	across	IN	O	4	case
4	comments	comment	NNS	O	2	nmod
5	attached	attach	VBN	O	4	acl
6	to	to	TO	O	8	case
7	an	a	DT	O	8	det
8	article	article	NN	O	5	nmod
9	published	publish	VBN	O	8	acl
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	October	October	NNP	DATE	9	nmod
12	2010	2010	CD	DATE	11	nummod
13	by	by	IN	O	15	case
14	Entertainment	Entertainment	NNP	O	15	compound
15	Weekly	Weekly	NNP	SET	9	nmod
16	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubj
17	announced	announce	VBD	O	15	acl:relcl
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	potential	potential	NN	O	17	dobj
20	that	that	WDT	O	26	dobj
21	Willow	Willow	NNP	PERSON	22	compound
22	Smith	Smith	NNP	PERSON	26	nsubj
23	would	would	MD	O	26	aux
24	be	be	VB	O	26	cop
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	actress	actress	NN	O	19	acl:relcl
27	chosen	choose	VBN	O	26	acl
28	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
29	play	play	VB	O	27	xcomp
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	character	character	NN	O	29	dobj
32	of	of	IN	O	33	case
33	Rue	Rue	NNP	O	31	nmod
34	,	,	,	O	33	punct
35	a	a	DT	O	37	det
36	young	young	JJ	O	37	amod
37	character	character	NN	O	33	appos
38	in	in	IN	O	40	case
39	the	the	DT	O	40	det
40	story	story	NN	O	37	nmod
41	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Readers	reader	NNS	O	5	nsubj
2	who	who	WP	O	3	nsubj
3	left	leave	VBD	O	1	acl:relcl
4	comments	comment	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	it	it	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	clear	clear	JJ	O	5	xcomp
8	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
9	they	they	PRP	O	11	nsubjpass
10	were	be	VBD	O	11	auxpass
11	appalled	appal	VBN	O	7	ccomp
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	find	find	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
15	Rue	Rue	NNP	PERSON	19	nsubj
16	is	be	VBZ	O	19	cop
17	a	a	DT	O	19	det
18	black	black	JJ	O	19	amod
19	character	character	NN	O	13	ccomp
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	3	advmod
2	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	saw	see	VBD	O	7	advcl
4	these	these	DT	O	5	det
5	comments	comment	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	decided	decide	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	search	search	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	O	9	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	find	find	VB	O	9	xcomp
13	what	what	WP	O	18	dobj
14	other	other	JJ	O	16	amod
15	statements	statement	NNS	O	16	compound
16	people	people	NNS	O	18	nsubj
17	were	be	VBD	O	18	aux
18	making	make	VBG	O	12	ccomp
19	about	about	IN	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	new	new	JJ	O	22	amod
22	development	development	NN	O	18	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	search	search	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	turned	turn	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	up	up	RP	O	3	compound:prt
5	results	result	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	that	that	WDT	O	7	nsubj
7	mirrored	mirror	VBD	O	5	acl:relcl
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	comments	comment	NNS	O	10	compound
10	section	section	NN	O	7	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	15	case
12	that	that	DT	O	15	det
13	Entertainment	Entertainment	NNP	O	15	compound
14	Weekly	Weekly	NNP	SET	15	compound
15	article	article	NN	O	10	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	users	user	NNS	O	9	nsubj
3	who	who	WP	O	4	nsubj
4	made	make	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
5	remarks	remark	NNS	O	4	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	subject	subject	NN	O	5	nmod
9	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	comments	comment	NNS	O	9	dobj
11	that	that	WDT	O	12	nsubj
12	showed	show	VBD	O	10	acl:relcl
13	clear	clear	JJ	O	14	amod
14	shock	shock	NN	O	12	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	10	punct
16	if	if	IN	O	17	dep
17	not	not	RB	O	10	cc
18	disgust	disgust	NN	O	10	conj
19	in	in	IN	O	25	mark
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	idea	idea	NN	O	25	nsubj
22	of	of	IN	O	23	case
23	Rue	Rue	NNP	O	21	nmod
24	being	be	VBG	O	25	cop
25	black	black	JJ	O	18	acl
26	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	MISC	3	compound
3	Games	Games	NNPS	MISC	4	nsubj
4	started	start	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	as	as	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	trilogy	trilogy	NN	O	4	nmod
8	where	where	WRB	O	13	advmod
9	twenty-four	twenty-four	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
10	kids	kid	NNS	O	13	nsubjpass
11	``	``	``	O	13	punct
12	are	be	VBP	O	13	auxpass
13	thrown	throw	VBN	O	7	acl:relcl
14	into	into	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	life-or-death	life-or-death	JJ	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	Lord	Lord	NNP	O	16	appos
19	of	of	IN	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	Flies-esque	flies-esque	JJ	MISC	22	amod
22	battle	battle	NN	O	18	nmod
23	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	book	book	NN	O	27	nsubjpass
26	is	be	VBZ	O	27	auxpass
27	named	name	VBN	O	13	ccomp
28	for	for	IN	O	27	nmod
29	''	''	''	O	13	punct
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	7	dep
32	,	,	,	O	31	punct
33	``	``	``	O	34	punct
34	White	White	NNP	O	31	appos
35	Until	until	IN	O	37	case
36	Proven	Proven	NNP	O	37	compound
37	Black	Black	NNP	O	34	nmod
38	''	''	''	O	37	punct
39	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
40	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	From	from	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	outside	outside	JJ	O	21	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	reader	reader	NN	O	3	appos
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	this	this	DT	O	9	det
9	article	article	NN	O	6	nmod
10	who	who	WP	O	13	nsubj
11	does	do	VBZ	O	13	aux
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	have	have	VB	O	9	acl:relcl
14	any	any	DT	O	15	det
15	attachment	attachment	NN	O	13	dobj
16	to	to	TO	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	story	story	NN	O	15	nmod
19	itself	itself	PRP	O	21	nsubj
20	would	would	MD	O	21	aux
21	observe	observe	VB	O	0	ROOT
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	urgency	urgency	NN	O	21	dobj
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	plot	plot	NN	O	23	nmod
27	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
28	would	would	MD	O	30	aux
29	not	not	RB	O	30	neg
30	find	find	VB	O	21	conj
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	race	race	NN	O	30	dobj
33	of	of	IN	O	35	case
34	the	the	DT	O	35	det
35	characters	character	NNS	O	32	nmod
36	to	to	TO	O	40	mark
37	be	be	VB	O	40	cop
38	a	a	DT	O	40	det
39	major	major	JJ	O	40	amod
40	concern	concern	NN	O	30	advcl
41	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	4	case
2	my	my	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
3	own	own	JJ	O	4	amod
4	opinion	opinion	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	this	this	DT	O	7	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	what	what	WP	O	9	nsubj
9	motivated	motivate	VBD	O	7	ccomp
10	to	to	TO	O	11	case
11	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	9	nmod
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	take	take	VB	O	9	xcomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	action	action	NN	O	13	dobj
16	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
17	he	he	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	did	do	VBD	O	13	ccomp
19	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	3	amod
3	element	element	NN	O	11	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	rhetoric	rhetoric	NN	O	3	nmod
6	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
7	be	be	VB	O	8	auxpass
8	addressed	address	VBN	O	5	acl
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	audience	audience	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	case	case	NN	O	6	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	6	punct
5	there	there	EX	O	6	expl
6	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
7	two	two	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
8	separate	separate	JJ	O	9	amod
9	audiences	audience	NNS	O	6	nsubj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	those	those	DT	O	9	appos
12	of	of	IN	O	15	case
13	The	the	DT	O	15	det
14	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	O	15	compound
15	Games	Games	NNPS	O	11	nmod
16	who	who	WP	O	17	nsubj
17	reacted	react	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
18	to	to	TO	O	22	case
19	the	the	DT	O	22	det
20	Entertainment	Entertainment	NNP	MISC	22	compound
21	Weekly	Weekly	NNP	SET	22	compound
22	article	article	NN	O	17	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	9	punct
24	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
25	those	those	DT	O	9	conj
26	who	who	WP	O	27	nsubj
27	came	come	VBD	O	25	acl:relcl
28	across	across	IN	O	32	case
29	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	32	nmod:poss
30	's	's	POS	O	29	case
31	Tumblr	Tumblr	NNP	MISC	32	compound
32	page	page	NN	O	27	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	3	amod
3	audience	audience	NN	O	15	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
6	reacted	react	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
7	to	to	TO	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	EW	ew	NN	O	10	compound
10	article	article	NN	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	3	punct
12	is	be	VBZ	O	15	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	main	main	JJ	O	15	amod
15	source	source	NN	O	0	ROOT
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	exigence	exigence	NN	O	15	nmod
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	this	this	DT	O	20	det
20	situation	situation	NN	O	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Members	member	NNS	O	5	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	this	this	DT	O	4	det
4	audience	audience	NN	O	1	nmod
5	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	statements	statement	NNS	O	5	dobj
7	such	such	JJ	O	13	case
8	as	as	IN	O	7	mwe
9	,	,	,	O	13	punct
10	``	``	``	O	13	punct
11	I	I	PRP	O	13	nsubjpass
12	was	be	VBD	O	13	auxpass
13	pumped	pump	VBN	O	5	advcl
14	about	about	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	MISC	17	compound
17	Games	Games	NNPS	MISC	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Until	until	IN	O	3	mark
2	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	learned	learn	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	black	black	JJ	O	7	amod
7	girl	girl	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	was	be	VBD	O	3	ccomp
9	playing	play	VBG	O	8	ccomp
10	Rue	Rue	NNP	O	9	dobj
11	''	''	''	O	9	punct
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
13	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	9	dep
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	appos
16	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	18	case
17	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	nmod
19	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	audience	audience	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	essentially	essentially	RB	O	4	advmod
4	overlooked	overlook	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	entire	entire	JJ	O	7	amod
7	plot	plot	NN	O	4	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	story	story	NN	O	7	nmod
11	because	because	IN	O	14	case
12	of	of	IN	O	11	mwe
13	their	they	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	disgust	disgust	NN	O	4	nmod
15	with	with	IN	O	18	case
16	Rue	Rue	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod:poss
17	's	's	POS	O	16	case
18	ethnicity	ethnicity	NN	O	14	nmod
19	on	on	IN	O	20	case
20	screen	screen	NN	O	4	nmod
21	when	when	WRB	O	30	advmod
22	,	,	,	O	30	punct
23	according	accord	VBG	O	26	case
24	to	to	TO	O	23	mwe
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	article	article	NN	O	30	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	30	punct
28	Collins	Collins	NNP	PERSON	30	nsubj
29	was	be	VBD	O	30	cop
30	clear	clear	JJ	O	4	advcl
31	about	about	IN	O	33	case
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	ethnicity	ethnicity	NN	O	30	nmod
34	of	of	IN	O	36	case
35	both	both	CC	O	36	cc:preconj
36	Rue	rue	NN	PERSON	33	nmod
37	and	and	CC	O	36	cc
38	another	another	DT	O	39	det
39	character	character	NN	O	36	conj
40	,	,	,	O	33	punct
41	Thresh	Thresh	NNP	PERSON	33	appos
42	,	,	,	O	41	punct
43	who	who	WP	O	46	nsubj
44	both	both	DT	O	46	dep
45	are	be	VBP	O	46	cop
46	black	black	JJ	O	41	acl:relcl
47	on	on	IN	O	48	case
48	screen	screen	NN	O	46	nmod
49	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	audience	audience	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	7	case
4	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	Tumblr	Tumblr	NNP	MISC	7	compound
7	page	page	NN	O	2	nmod
8	takes	take	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	opposite	opposite	JJ	O	11	amod
11	stance	stance	NN	O	8	dobj
12	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	support	support	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	blog	blog	NN	O	2	dobj
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	which	which	WDT	O	8	nmod
7	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	describes	describe	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
9	as	as	IN	O	11	mark
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	page	page	NN	O	8	advcl
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	created	create	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
14	in	in	IN	O	18	mark
15	order	order	NN	O	14	mwe
16	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
17	``	``	``	O	18	punct
18	acknowledge	acknowledge	VB	O	13	advcl
19	all	all	DT	O	18	dobj
20	of	of	IN	O	23	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	idiotic	idiotic	JJ	O	23	amod
23	tweets	tweet	NNS	O	19	nmod
24	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
25	I	I	PRP	O	27	nsubj
26	've	have	VBP	O	27	aux
27	come	come	VBN	O	18	ccomp
28	across	across	RP	O	27	compound:prt
29	as	as	IN	O	31	mark
30	they	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
31	concern	concern	VBP	O	27	advcl
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	MISC	34	compound
34	Games	Games	NNPS	MISC	31	dobj
35	''	''	''	O	18	punct
36	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	37	punct
37	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	11	dep
38	,	,	,	O	37	punct
39	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	37	appos
40	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	42	case
41	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	42	compound
42	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	37	nmod
43	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	37	punct
44	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	According	accord	VBG	O	4	case
2	to	to	TO	O	1	mwe
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	article	article	NN	O	8	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
7	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
8	share	share	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	screenshots	screenshot	NNS	O	8	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	O	12	compound
12	users	user	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	making	make	VBG	O	8	ccomp
14	these	these	DT	O	16	det
15	rude	rude	JJ	O	16	amod
16	comments	comment	NNS	O	13	dobj
17	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
18	that	that	IN	O	24	mark
19	all	all	DT	O	24	nsubj
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	these	these	DT	O	22	det
22	shots	shot	NNS	O	19	nmod
23	would	would	MD	O	24	aux
24	receive	receive	VB	O	13	conj
25	up	up	IN	O	24	advmod
26	to	to	TO	O	27	case
27	twenty	twenty	CD	NUMBER	24	nmod
28	``	``	``	O	29	punct
29	likes	likes	NN	O	24	nmod:tmod
30	''	''	''	O	29	punct
31	each	each	DT	O	29	dep
32	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	6	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	two	two	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
4	audiences	audience	NNS	O	6	nsubj
5	clearly	clearly	RB	O	6	advmod
6	differ	differ	VBP	O	12	advcl
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	their	they	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	opinions	opinion	NNS	O	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	12	punct
11	there	there	EX	O	12	expl
12	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
13	a	a	DT	O	15	det
14	few	few	JJ	O	15	amod
15	commonalities	commonality	NNS	O	12	nsubj
16	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
17	we	we	PRP	O	19	nsubj
18	can	can	MD	O	19	aux
19	assume	assume	VB	O	15	dep
20	they	they	PRP	O	21	nsubj
21	have	have	VBP	O	19	ccomp
22	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	First	first	RB	ORDINAL	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	they	they	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	have	have	VBP	O	5	aux
5	read	read	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	The	the	DT	O	9	det
7	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	MISC	9	compound
8	Games	Games	NNPS	MISC	9	compound
9	text	text	NN	O	5	dobj
10	because	because	IN	O	28	mark
11	if	if	IN	O	15	mark
12	they	they	PRP	O	15	nsubj
13	did	do	VBD	O	15	aux
14	not	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	have	have	VB	O	28	advcl
16	any	any	DT	O	18	det
17	prior	prior	JJ	O	18	amod
18	knowledge	knowledge	NN	O	15	dobj
19	of	of	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	characters	character	NNS	O	18	nmod
22	then	then	RB	O	15	advmod
23	they	they	PRP	O	28	nsubjpass
24	would	would	MD	O	28	aux
25	not	not	RB	O	28	neg
26	have	have	VB	O	28	aux
27	been	be	VBN	O	28	auxpass
28	affected	affect	VBN	O	5	advcl
29	by	by	IN	O	33	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	character	character	NN	O	33	nmod:poss
32	's	's	POS	O	31	case
33	race	race	NN	O	28	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	we	we	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	can	can	MD	O	5	aux
5	assume	assume	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	two	two	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
9	audiences	audience	NNS	O	10	nsubj
10	follow	follow	VBP	O	5	ccomp
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	trilogy	trilogy	NN	O	10	dobj
13	closely	closely	RB	O	14	advmod
14	enough	enough	RB	O	10	advmod
15	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
16	they	they	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	were	be	VBD	O	18	cop
18	able	able	JJ	O	14	advcl
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	track	track	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	down	down	RP	O	20	compound:prt
22	news	news	NN	O	23	compound
23	articles	article	NNS	O	20	dobj
24	concerning	concern	VBG	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	making	making	NN	O	23	nmod
27	of	of	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	film	film	NN	O	26	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	3	aux
3	make	make	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	assumption	assumption	NN	O	3	dobj
6	because	because	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	article	article	NN	O	3	nmod
9	that	that	WDT	O	10	nsubj
10	sparked	spark	VBD	O	8	acl:relcl
11	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod:poss
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	action	action	NN	O	15	nsubjpass
14	was	be	VBD	O	15	auxpass
15	published	publish	VBN	O	10	ccomp
16	by	by	IN	O	18	case
17	Entertainment	Entertainment	NNP	O	18	compound
18	Weekly	Weekly	NNP	SET	15	nmod
19	in	in	IN	SET	20	case
20	October	October	NNP	DATE	18	nmod
21	2010	2010	CD	DATE	20	nummod
22	,	,	,	O	15	punct
23	long	long	RB	O	15	advmod
24	before	before	IN	O	29	case
25	the	the	DT	O	29	det
26	March	March	NNP	DATE	29	compound
27	2012	2012	CD	DATE	29	nummod
28	release	release	NN	O	29	compound
29	date	date	NN	O	23	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	exigence	exigence	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	action	action	NN	O	2	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
8	obviously	obviously	RB	O	10	advmod
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	comments	comment	NNS	O	0	ROOT
11	made	make	VBN	O	10	acl
12	by	by	IN	O	14	case
13	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
14	users	user	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	concerning	concern	VBG	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	ethnicity	ethnicity	NN	O	14	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	21	case
19	Rue	Rue	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod:poss
20	's	's	POS	O	19	case
21	character	character	NN	O	17	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	4	cc
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	what	what	WP	O	4	nsubj
4	caused	cause	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	these	these	DT	O	6	det
6	people	people	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	get	get	VB	O	4	advcl
9	so	so	RB	O	10	advmod
10	upset	upset	JJ	O	8	xcomp
11	?	?	.	O	4	punct

1	According	accord	VBG	O	4	case
2	to	to	TO	O	1	mwe
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	article	article	NN	O	9	nmod
5	Rue	Rue	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	ethnicity	ethnicity	NN	O	9	nsubjpass
8	was	be	VBD	O	9	auxpass
9	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	clear	clear	JJ	O	9	xcomp
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	text	text	NN	O	10	nmod
14	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	15	punct
15	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	dep
16	,	,	,	O	15	punct
17	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	appos
18	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	20	case
19	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
20	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	nmod
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	15	punct
22	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Twitter	Twitter	NNP	O	2	compound
2	users	user	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	continued	continue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	saying	say	VBG	O	23	csubj
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	``	``	``	O	4	punct
7	awkward	awkward	JJ	O	8	amod
8	moment	moment	NN	O	22	nsubj
9	when	when	WRB	O	14	advmod
10	Rue	Rue	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
11	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
12	some	some	DT	O	14	det
13	black	black	JJ	O	14	amod
14	girl	girl	NN	O	8	acl:relcl
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
17	the	the	DT	O	21	det
18	little	little	JJ	O	21	amod
19	blonde	blonde	JJ	O	21	amod
20	innocent	innocent	JJ	O	21	amod
21	girl	girl	NN	O	14	conj
22	you	you	PRP	O	4	xcomp
23	picture	picture	VBP	O	3	ccomp
24	''	''	''	O	3	punct
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
26	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	3	dep
27	,	,	,	O	26	punct
28	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	appos
29	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	31	case
30	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	compound
31	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	nmod
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
33	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	scrolled	scroll	VBD	O	8	advcl
4	through	through	IN	O	6	case
5	these	these	DT	O	6	det
6	comments	comment	NNS	O	3	nmod
7	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	continued	continue	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	find	find	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	offensive	offensive	JJ	O	12	amod
12	statements	statement	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
14	went	go	VBD	O	12	acl:relcl
15	as	as	RB	O	16	advmod
16	far	far	RB	O	14	advmod
17	as	as	IN	O	19	mark
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	call	call	VB	O	16	advcl
20	Rue	Rue	NNP	PERSON	22	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	character	character	NN	O	19	dobj
23	``	``	``	O	10	punct
24	some	some	DT	O	27	det
25	ugly	ugly	JJ	O	27	amod
26	little	little	JJ	O	27	amod
27	girl	girl	NN	O	10	dobj
28	with	with	IN	O	29	case
29	nappy	nappy	NN	O	8	nmod
30	...	...	:	O	29	punct
31	hair	hair	NN	O	29	dep
32	''	''	''	O	8	punct
33	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
34	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	8	dep
35	,	,	,	O	34	punct
36	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	appos
37	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	39	case
38	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	39	compound
39	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	nmod
40	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
41	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	more	more	JJR	O	3	amod
3	comments	comment	NNS	O	12	nsubj
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	you	you	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	read	read	VBP	O	3	dep
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	better	better	JJR	O	10	amod
10	understanding	understanding	NN	O	11	nsubj
11	you	you	PRP	O	6	xcomp
12	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	people	people	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	making	make	VBG	O	12	xcomp
17	them	they	PRP	O	16	dobj
18	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	are	be	VBP	O	3	cop
3	people	people	NNS	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	WDT	O	7	nsubj
5	have	have	VBP	O	7	aux
6	been	be	VBN	O	7	aux
7	following	follow	VBG	O	3	acl:relcl
8	this	this	DT	O	9	det
9	trilogy	trilogy	NN	O	7	dobj
10	closely	closely	RB	O	7	advmod
11	,	,	,	O	7	punct
12	so	so	RB	O	13	advmod
13	closely	closely	RB	O	37	advmod
14	that	that	IN	O	37	mark
15	when	when	WRB	O	21	advmod
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	motion	motion	NN	O	18	compound
18	picture	picture	NN	O	21	nsubj
19	is	be	VBZ	O	21	aux
20	potentially	potentially	RB	O	21	advmod
21	portraying	portray	VBG	O	37	advcl
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	character	character	NN	O	21	dobj
24	in	in	IN	O	26	case
25	a	a	DT	O	26	det
26	way	way	NN	O	21	nmod
27	that	that	WDT	O	29	nsubj
28	is	be	VBZ	O	29	cop
29	incorrect	incorrect	JJ	O	26	acl:relcl
30	in	in	IN	O	33	case
31	their	they	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
32	own	own	JJ	O	33	amod
33	opinion	opinion	NN	O	29	nmod
34	,	,	,	O	37	punct
35	they	they	PRP	O	37	nsubjpass
36	are	be	VBP	O	37	auxpass
37	offended	offend	VBN	O	7	dep
38	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	5	mark
2	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	shares	share	NNS	O	5	nsubj
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	posts	post	NNS	O	11	advcl
6	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	finds	find	VBZ	O	5	dep
9	,	,	,	O	11	punct
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	attaches	attach	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	comments	comment	NNS	O	11	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	own	own	JJ	O	12	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	response	response	NN	O	12	nmod
18	to	to	TO	O	21	case
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	offensive	offensive	JJ	O	21	amod
21	statements	statement	NNS	O	11	nmod
22	being	be	VBG	O	23	auxpass
23	made	make	VBN	O	21	acl
24	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	post	post	NN	O	37	nmod
4	where	where	WRB	O	6	advmod
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	shared	share	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	comment	comment	NN	O	11	nsubj
9	about	about	IN	O	10	case
10	Rue	Rue	NNP	O	8	nmod
11	not	not	RB	O	6	ccomp
12	being	be	VBG	O	16	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	16	det
14	``	``	``	O	16	punct
15	innocent	innocent	JJ	O	16	amod
16	girl	girl	NN	O	11	xcomp
17	you	you	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	picture	picture	VBP	O	16	acl:relcl
19	''	''	''	O	6	punct
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	6	dep
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	White	White	NNP	O	21	appos
24	Until	until	IN	O	26	case
25	Proven	Proven	NNP	O	26	compound
26	Black	Black	NNP	O	21	nmod
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
28	he	he	PRP	O	29	dep
29	references	reference	NNS	O	37	nsubj
30	the	the	DT	O	32	det
31	Trayvon	Trayvon	NNP	PERSON	32	compound
32	Martin	Martin	NNP	PERSON	29	dep
33	killing	kill	VBG	O	29	acl
34	that	that	DT	O	33	dobj
35	had	have	VBD	O	37	aux
36	recently	recently	RB	DATE	37	advmod
37	occurred	occur	VBN	O	0	ROOT
38	.	.	.	O	37	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	compares	compare	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	two	two	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	events	event	NNS	O	2	dobj
6	by	by	IN	O	16	mark
7	how	how	WRB	O	16	advmod
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	guilt	guilt	NN	O	16	nsubjpass
10	or	or	CC	O	9	cc
11	innocence	innocence	NN	O	9	conj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	subject	subject	NN	O	9	nmod
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	auxpass
16	determined	determine	VBN	O	2	advcl
17	by	by	IN	O	19	case
18	an	a	DT	O	19	det
19	outsider	outsider	NN	O	16	nmod
20	who	who	WP	O	27	nsubj
21	,	,	,	O	27	punct
22	in	in	IN	O	25	case
23	Trayvon	Trayvon	NNP	LOCATION	25	nmod:poss
24	's	's	POS	O	23	case
25	case	case	NN	O	27	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	27	punct
27	had	have	VBD	O	19	acl:relcl
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	motivation	motivation	NN	O	27	dobj
30	to	to	TO	O	32	mark
31	actually	actually	RB	O	32	advmod
32	kill	kill	VB	O	29	acl
33	their	they	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
34	subject	subject	NN	O	32	dobj
35	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	references	reference	NNS	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	Trayvon	Trayvon	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Martin	Martin	NNP	PERSON	2	dep
6	killing	kill	VBG	O	2	acl
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	an	a	DT	O	9	det
9	attempt	attempt	NN	O	6	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	show	show	VB	O	6	xcomp
12	how	how	WRB	O	19	advmod
13	Trayvon	Trayvon	NNP	PERSON	15	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	O	13	case
15	race	race	NN	O	19	nsubj
16	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	determining	determine	VBG	O	19	amod
19	factor	factor	NN	O	11	ccomp
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	innocence	innocence	NN	O	19	nmod
23	which	which	WDT	O	25	nsubj
24	ultimately	ultimately	RB	O	25	advmod
25	lead	lead	VBP	O	19	acl:relcl
26	to	to	TO	O	28	case
27	his	he	PRP$	O	28	nmod:poss
28	death	death	NN	O	25	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Anna	Anna	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	writer	writer	NN	O	2	appos
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	essay	essay	NN	O	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	built	build	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	off	off	IN	O	10	compound:prt
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	comments	comment	NNS	O	10	nmod
15	that	that	WDT	O	17	dobj
16	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
17	made	make	VBD	O	10	ccomp
18	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	continued	continue	VBD	O	35	ccomp
3	his	he	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	argument	argument	NN	O	2	dobj
5	saying	say	VBG	O	2	xcomp
6	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	way	way	NN	O	9	compound
9	Rue	rue	NN	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
10	's	's	POS	O	9	case
11	identity	identity	NN	O	12	nsubj
12	changed	change	VBD	O	5	ccomp
13	from	from	IN	O	14	case
14	that	that	DT	O	12	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	any	any	DT	O	18	det
17	other	other	JJ	O	18	amod
18	character	character	NN	O	14	nmod
19	to	to	TO	O	14	case
20	,	,	,	O	35	punct
21	``	``	``	O	24	punct
22	some	some	DT	O	24	det
23	black	black	JJ	O	24	amod
24	girl	girl	NN	O	35	nsubj
25	''	''	''	O	24	punct
26	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	27	punct
27	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	24	dep
28	,	,	,	O	27	punct
29	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	appos
30	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	32	case
31	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	32	compound
32	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	dep
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
34	is	be	VBZ	O	35	cop
35	comparable	comparable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
36	to	to	TO	O	40	case
37	the	the	DT	O	40	det
38	Trayvon	Trayvon	NNP	PERSON	40	compound
39	Martin	Martin	NNP	PERSON	40	compound
40	case	case	NN	O	35	nmod
41	.	.	.	O	35	punct

1	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	continues	continue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	with	with	IN	O	5	case
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	argument	argument	NN	O	2	nmod
6	quoting	quote	VBG	O	5	acl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	director	director	NN	O	6	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	14	case
10	the	the	DT	O	14	det
11	Ezra	Ezra	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
12	Jack	Jack	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
13	Keats	Keats	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
14	Foundation	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	5	punct
16	Deborah	Deborah	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Pope	Pope	NNP	PERSON	5	appos
18	,	,	,	O	5	punct
19	who	who	WP	O	20	nsubj
20	says	say	VBZ	O	5	acl:relcl
21	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
22	many	many	JJ	O	23	amod
23	readers	reader	NNS	O	25	nsubj
24	unfortunately	unfortunately	RB	O	25	advmod
25	assume	assume	VBP	O	20	ccomp
26	that	that	IN	O	37	mark
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	characters	character	NNS	O	37	nsubj
29	of	of	IN	O	31	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	stories	story	NNS	O	28	nmod
32	that	that	IN	O	35	mark
33	they	they	PRP	O	35	nsubj
34	are	be	VBP	O	35	aux
35	reading	read	VBG	O	31	dep
36	are	be	VBP	O	37	cop
37	white	white	JJ	O	25	ccomp
38	,	,	,	O	37	punct
39	unless	unless	IN	O	42	mark
40	otherwise	otherwise	RB	O	42	advmod
41	explicitly	explicitly	RB	O	42	advmod
42	indicated	indicate	VBN	O	37	advcl
43	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Pope	Pope	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	continues	continue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	saying	say	VBG	O	2	xcomp
5	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
6	these	these	DT	O	7	det
7	assumptions	assumption	NNS	O	10	nsubjpass
8	are	be	VBP	O	10	auxpass
9	``	``	``	O	10	punct
10	learned	learn	VBN	O	4	ccomp
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	internalized	internalize	VBN	O	10	conj
13	early	early	RB	O	10	advmod
14	,	,	,	O	10	punct
15	including	include	VBG	O	17	case
16	by	by	IN	O	17	case
17	children	child	NNS	O	10	advcl
18	of	of	IN	O	19	case
19	color	color	NN	O	17	nmod
20	''	''	''	O	17	punct
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	22	punct
22	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	17	dep
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	appos
25	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	27	case
26	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	compound
27	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	dep
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	22	punct
29	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
30	that	that	IN	O	32	mark
31	it	it	PRP	O	32	nsubj
32	takes	take	VBZ	O	10	conj
33	a	a	DT	O	35	det
34	large	large	JJ	O	35	amod
35	commitment	commitment	NN	O	32	dobj
36	and	and	CC	O	35	cc
37	considerable	considerable	JJ	O	35	conj
38	``	``	``	O	44	punct
39	self-awareness	self-awareness	NN	O	44	dep
40	to	to	TO	O	41	mark
41	overcome	overcome	VB	O	39	dep
42	''	''	''	O	44	punct
43	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	44	punct
44	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	37	dep
45	,	,	,	O	44	punct
46	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	44	appos
47	Until	until	IN	ORGANIZATION	49	case
48	Proven	Proven	NNP	ORGANIZATION	49	compound
49	Black	Black	NNP	ORGANIZATION	44	dep
50	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	44	punct
51	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	end	end	NN	O	9	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	her	she	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	essay	essay	NN	O	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	9	punct
8	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
9	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
10	an	a	DT	O	11	det
11	example	example	NN	O	9	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	this	this	DT	O	14	det
14	point	point	NN	O	11	nmod
15	by	by	IN	O	16	mark
16	indicating	indicate	VBG	O	9	advcl
17	that	that	IN	O	22	mark
18	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
19	is	be	VBZ	O	22	cop
20	of	of	IN	O	21	case
21	Caribbean	Caribbean	NNP	LOCATION	22	nmod
22	decent	decent	JJ	O	16	ccomp
23	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	3	case
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	statement	statement	NN	O	7	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	7	punct
5	my	my	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	jaw	jaw	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	dropped	drop	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	had	have	VBD	O	3	aux
3	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	same	same	JJ	O	6	amod
6	assumption	assumption	NN	O	3	dobj
7	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
8	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
9	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
10	white	white	JJ	O	3	ccomp
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	not	not	RB	O	20	neg
13	only	only	RB	O	20	advmod
14	because	because	IN	O	20	case
15	of	of	IN	O	20	case
16	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
17	obviously	obviously	RB	O	18	advmod
18	white	white	JJ	O	20	amod
19	sounding	sound	VBG	O	20	amod
20	name	name	NN	O	10	dep
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	but	but	CC	O	20	cc
23	because	because	IN	O	27	case
24	of	of	IN	O	27	case
25	his	he	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
26	Canadian	canadian	JJ	MISC	27	amod
27	citizenship	citizenship	NN	O	20	conj
28	;	;	:	O	3	punct
29	well	well	RB	O	30	advmod
30	played	play	VBN	O	3	parataxis
31	by	by	IN	O	32	case
32	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	30	nmod
33	in	in	IN	O	36	mark
34	order	order	NN	O	33	mwe
35	to	to	TO	O	36	mark
36	prove	prove	VB	O	30	advcl
37	her	she	PRP$	O	38	nmod:poss
38	point	point	NN	O	36	dobj
39	to	to	TO	O	40	case
40	readers	reader	NNS	O	36	nmod
41	on	on	IN	O	44	case
42	a	a	DT	O	44	det
43	personal	personal	JJ	O	44	amod
44	level	level	NN	O	40	nmod
45	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	three	three	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
3	main	main	JJ	O	4	amod
4	elements	element	NNS	O	16	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	rhetorical	rhetorical	JJ	O	7	amod
7	situations	situation	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	:	:	:	O	4	punct
9	context	context	NN	O	4	dep
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	audience	audience	NN	O	9	conj
12	,	,	,	O	9	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
14	exigence	exigence	NN	O	9	conj
15	,	,	,	O	4	punct
16	were	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
17	all	all	DT	O	18	det
18	important	important	JJ	O	16	advmod
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	this	this	DT	O	21	det
21	issue	issue	NN	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Without	without	IN	O	2	case
2	context	context	NN	O	9	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	9	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	arguments	argument	NNS	O	9	nsubj
6	would	would	MD	O	9	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
8	have	have	VB	O	9	aux
9	existed	exist	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	because	because	IN	O	14	mark
11	these	these	DT	O	12	det
12	arguments	argument	NNS	O	14	nsubjpass
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	sparked	spark	VBN	O	9	advcl
15	when	when	WRB	O	19	advmod
16	Hunger	Hunger	NNP	O	18	compound
17	Games	Games	NNPS	O	18	compound
18	fans	fan	NNS	O	19	nsubj
19	found	find	VBD	O	14	advcl
20	out	out	RP	O	19	compound:prt
21	that	that	IN	O	30	mark
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	context	context	NN	O	30	nsubj
24	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
25	they	they	PRP	O	27	nsubj
26	had	have	VBD	O	27	aux
27	assumed	assume	VBN	O	23	dep
28	,	,	,	O	30	punct
29	was	be	VBD	O	30	cop
30	incorrect	incorrect	JJ	O	19	ccomp
31	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	two	two	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	audiences	audience	NNS	O	11	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	clashing	clash	VBG	O	3	acl
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	their	they	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	disagreements	disagreement	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	online	online	NN	O	5	advcl
10	,	,	,	O	3	punct
11	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
12	what	what	WP	O	13	nsubj
13	brought	bring	VBD	O	11	ccomp
14	this	this	DT	O	16	det
15	entire	entire	JJ	O	16	amod
16	issue	issue	NN	O	13	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	20	case
18	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	20	nmod:poss
19	's	's	POS	O	18	case
20	attention	attention	NN	O	13	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Without	without	IN	O	3	case
2	these	these	DT	O	3	det
3	audiences	audience	NNS	O	9	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	9	punct
5	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
6	would	would	MD	O	9	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
8	have	have	VB	O	9	aux
9	started	start	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	blog	blog	NN	O	9	dobj
12	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
13	Holmes	Holmes	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
14	would	would	MD	O	17	aux
15	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
16	have	have	VB	O	17	aux
17	written	write	VBN	O	9	conj
18	this	this	DT	O	19	det
19	essay	essay	NN	O	17	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Most	most	RBS	O	2	advmod
2	importantly	importantly	RB	O	9	advmod
3	,	,	,	O	9	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	exigence	exigence	NN	O	9	nsubj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	situation	situation	NN	O	5	nmod
9	brought	bring	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	9	dobj
11	into	into	IN	O	15	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	public	public	NN	O	15	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	O	13	case
15	attention	attention	NN	O	9	nmod
16	by	by	IN	O	17	mark
17	causing	cause	VBG	O	9	advcl
18	him	he	PRP	O	17	dobj
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	react	react	VB	O	17	xcomp
21	to	to	TO	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	rude	rude	JJ	O	24	amod
24	comments	comment	NNS	O	20	nmod
25	that	that	IN	O	29	mark
26	other	other	JJ	O	27	amod
27	readers	reader	NNS	O	29	nsubj
28	were	be	VBD	O	29	aux
29	making	make	VBG	O	20	ccomp
30	.	.	.	O	9	punct

