1	H.P.	H.P.	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
4	well	well	RB	O	5	advmod
5	known	know	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	bring	bring	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	death	death	NN	O	7	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
11	insanity	insanity	NN	O	8	conj
12	among	among	IN	O	13	case
13	characters	character	NNS	O	11	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	his	he	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	writings	writings	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	story	story	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	``	``	``	O	2	punct
4	The	the	DT	O	5	det
5	Rats	rat	NNS	O	2	dep
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	Walls	wall	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	''	''	''	O	2	punct
10	matches	match	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
11	perfectly	perfectly	RB	O	10	advmod
12	with	with	IN	O	14	case
13	that	that	DT	O	14	det
14	style	style	NN	O	10	nmod
15	as	as	IN	O	17	mark
16	you	you	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	read	read	VBP	O	14	acl:relcl
18	about	about	IN	O	20	case
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	man	man	NN	O	17	nmod
21	named	name	VBN	O	20	acl
22	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	21	dobj
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	who	who	WP	O	26	nsubjpass
25	is	be	VBZ	O	26	auxpass
26	found	find	VBN	O	22	acl:relcl
27	discovering	discover	VBG	O	26	xcomp
28	family	family	NN	O	29	compound
29	heritage	heritage	NN	O	27	dobj
30	on	on	IN	O	33	case
31	an	a	DT	O	33	det
32	old	old	JJ	O	33	amod
33	estate	estate	NN	O	27	nmod
34	called	call	VBN	O	33	acl
35	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	36	compound
36	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	34	dobj
37	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	2	compound
2	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	4	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
4	notorious	notorious	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	for	for	IN	O	6	case
6	horror	horror	NN	O	4	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	evil	evil	NN	O	6	conj
9	being	be	VBG	O	10	cop
10	present	present	JJ	DATE	4	acl
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	its	its	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	vicinity	vicinity	NN	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	mark
2	you	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	read	read	VBP	O	17	advcl
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	story	story	NN	O	3	dobj
6	you	you	PRP	O	8	nsubj
7	can	can	MD	O	8	aux
8	see	see	VB	O	5	acl:relcl
9	how	how	WRB	O	12	advmod
10	H.P.	H.P.	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	O	12	nsubj
12	displays	display	VBZ	O	8	ccomp
13	human	human	JJ	O	14	amod
14	degeneration	degeneration	NN	O	12	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	17	punct
16	otherwise	otherwise	RB	O	17	advmod
17	known	know	VBN	O	0	ROOT
18	as	as	IN	O	19	case
19	mutilation	mutilation	NN	O	17	nmod
20	of	of	IN	O	21	case
21	humans	human	NNS	O	19	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	25	case
23	less	less	RBR	O	24	advmod
24	primitive	primitive	JJ	O	25	amod
25	states	state	NNS	O	17	nmod
26	from	from	IN	O	28	case
27	past	past	JJ	DATE	28	amod
28	generations	generation	NNS	O	17	nmod
29	of	of	IN	O	30	case
30	time	time	NN	O	28	nmod
31	against	against	IN	O	34	case
32	their	they	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
33	own	own	JJ	O	34	amod
34	will	will	NN	O	30	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	achieves	achieve	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	2	dobj
4	with	with	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	danger	danger	NN	O	3	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	human	human	JJ	O	9	amod
9	understanding	understanding	NN	O	6	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	13	case
11	``	``	``	O	13	punct
12	The	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Rats	rat	NNS	O	9	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	Walls	wall	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	''	''	''	O	13	punct
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	utilizes	utilize	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	constant	constant	JJ	O	4	amod
4	repetition	repetition	NN	O	2	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	8	compound
8	family	family	NN	O	4	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
10	their	they	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	tendency	tendency	NN	O	4	conj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	avoid	avoid	VB	O	11	acl
14	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
15	attempt	attempt	VB	O	13	conj
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	rid	rid	VB	O	15	xcomp
18	themselves	themselves	PRP	O	17	dobj
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	violence	violence	NN	O	17	nmod
21	or	or	CC	O	20	cc
22	evil	evil	NN	O	20	conj
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	their	they	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	lives	life	NNS	O	20	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	20	punct
27	as	as	RB	O	20	cc
28	well	well	RB	O	27	mwe
29	as	as	IN	O	27	mwe
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	mutilation	mutilation	NN	O	20	conj
32	of	of	IN	O	33	case
33	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	31	nmod
34	himself	himself	PRP	O	15	dobj
35	as	as	IN	O	37	mark
36	he	he	PRP	O	37	nsubj
37	tries	try	VBZ	O	13	advcl
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	unveil	unveil	VB	O	37	xcomp
40	what	what	WP	O	42	nsubj
41	is	be	VBZ	O	42	aux
42	occurring	occur	VBG	O	39	ccomp
43	in	in	IN	O	45	case
44	his	he	PRP$	O	45	nmod:poss
45	house	house	NN	O	42	nmod
46	at	at	IN	O	48	case
47	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	48	compound
48	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	42	nmod
49	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Despite	despite	IN	O	4	case
2	his	he	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
3	best	best	JJS	O	4	amod
4	efforts	effort	NNS	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	falls	fall	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	under	under	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	malevolent	malevolent	JJ	O	11	amod
11	influence	influence	NN	O	7	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	15	case
13	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
14	family	family	NN	O	15	compound
15	curse	curse	NN	O	11	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	curiosity	curiosity	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	works	work	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	against	against	IN	O	7	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
6	better	better	JJR	O	7	amod
7	judgement	judgement	NN	O	3	nmod
8	leading	lead	VBG	O	7	acl
9	to	to	TO	O	13	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
11	inevitable	inevitable	JJ	O	13	amod
12	horrific	horrific	JJ	O	13	amod
13	fate	fate	NN	O	8	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	cursed	curse	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	into	into	IN	O	6	case
5	human	human	JJ	O	6	amod
6	degeneration	degeneration	NN	O	3	nmod
7	beyond	beyond	IN	O	10	case
8	both	both	DT	O	10	cc:preconj
9	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	families	family	NNS	O	3	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	control	control	NN	O	10	conj
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	avoidant	avoidant	JJ	O	3	amod
3	nature	nature	NN	O	11	nsubj
4	that	that	WDT	O	6	nsubj
5	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
6	prominent	prominent	JJ	O	3	acl:relcl
7	in	in	IN	O	10	case
8	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	family	family	NN	O	6	nmod
11	led	lead	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	to	to	TO	O	15	case
13	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	15	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	O	13	case
15	initiative	initiative	NN	O	11	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	many	many	JJ	O	11	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	actions	action	NNS	O	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	sole	sole	JJ	O	3	amod
3	survivor	survivor	NN	O	10	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	O	7	compound
7	line	line	NN	O	3	nmod
8	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	0	ROOT
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	experience	experience	VB	O	10	dep
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	unexplained	unexplained	JJ	O	15	amod
15	occurrences	occurrence	NNS	O	12	dobj
16	at	at	IN	O	18	case
17	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Walter	Walter	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	affected	affect	VBN	O	5	amod
5	ancestor	ancestor	NN	O	1	appos
6	,	,	,	O	1	punct
7	witnessed	witness	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	murder	murder	NN	O	7	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	own	own	JJ	O	13	amod
13	family	family	NN	O	9	nmod
14	at	at	IN	O	16	case
15	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	16	compound
16	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	Walter	Walter	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	placed	place	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	blame	blame	NN	O	5	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	10	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	families	family	NNS	O	10	compound
10	death	death	NN	O	6	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	surrounding	surround	VBG	O	3	amod
3	population	population	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	turned	turn	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	on	on	RP	O	4	compound:prt
6	Walter	Walter	NNP	PERSON	4	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
9	``	``	``	O	10	punct
10	denounced	denounce	VBD	O	6	conj
11	as	as	IN	O	13	case
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	murderer	murderer	NN	O	10	nmod
14	''	''	''	O	10	punct
15	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	16	punct
16	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	dep
17	30	30	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
18	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	16	punct
19	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
20	eventually	eventually	RB	O	22	advmod
21	was	be	VBD	O	22	auxpass
22	described	describe	VBN	O	10	conj
23	as	as	IN	O	25	case
24	``	``	``	O	25	punct
25	Shaken	shake	VBN	O	22	nmod
26	by	by	IN	O	29	case
27	some	some	DT	O	29	det
28	horror	horror	NN	O	29	dep
29	greater	greater	JJR	O	25	nmod
30	than	than	IN	O	31	case
31	that	that	DT	O	29	nmod
32	of	of	IN	O	33	case
33	conscience	conscience	NN	O	31	nmod
34	or	or	CC	O	33	cc
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	law	law	NN	O	33	conj
37	''	''	''	O	25	punct
38	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	39	punct
39	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	appos
40	30	30	CD	NUMBER	39	nummod
41	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	39	punct
42	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
3	so	so	RB	O	4	advmod
4	impacted	impact	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	in	in	IN	O	6	case
6	fact	fact	NN	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	4	punct
8	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
9	he	he	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	fled	flee	VBD	O	4	ccomp
11	away	away	RB	O	10	advmod
12	from	from	IN	O	14	case
13	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	14	compound
14	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	start	start	VB	O	10	xcomp
17	a	a	DT	O	19	det
18	new	new	JJ	O	19	amod
19	family	family	NN	O	16	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	both	both	CC	O	4	advmod
4	knowledgeable	knowledgeable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	proactive	proactive	JJ	O	4	conj
7	to	to	TO	O	10	case
8	these	these	DT	O	10	det
9	unknown	unknown	JJ	O	10	amod
10	happenings	happening	NNS	O	4	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
13	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	turn	turn	NN	O	5	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	ordered	order	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	workmen	workman	NNS	O	5	dobj
7	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
8	``	``	``	O	9	punct
9	blow	blow	VB	O	6	acl
10	up	up	RP	O	9	compound:prt
11	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
12	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	9	dobj
13	''	''	''	O	9	punct
14	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	15	punct
15	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	appos
16	31	31	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
17	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	15	punct
18	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	demolition	demolition	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
5	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	2	nmod
6	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
7	hopefully	hopefully	RB	O	8	advmod
8	rid	rid	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	evil	evil	JJ	O	8	nmod
12	``	``	``	O	11	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	traces	trace	NNS	O	18	nsubj
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	it	it	PRP	O	14	nmod
17	's	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
18	foundations	foundation	NNS	O	11	dep
19	''	''	''	O	11	punct
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	appos
22	31	31	CD	NUMBER	21	nummod
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
24	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Ridding	rid	VBG	O	8	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	5	case
3	these	these	DT	O	5	det
4	evil	evil	JJ	O	5	amod
5	traces	trace	NNS	O	1	nmod
6	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
7	hopefully	hopefully	RB	O	8	advmod
8	destroy	destroy	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	any	any	DT	O	10	det
10	chance	chance	NN	O	8	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	curse	curse	NN	O	10	nmod
14	that	that	WDT	O	16	nsubj
15	would	would	MD	O	16	aux
16	control	control	VB	O	13	acl:relcl
17	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	O	16	dobj
18	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	actions	action	NNS	O	10	nsubj
3	taken	take	VBN	O	2	acl
4	by	by	IN	O	6	case
5	both	both	CC	O	6	cc:preconj
6	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	3	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	ancestor	ancestor	NN	O	6	conj
10	show	show	VBP	O	0	ROOT
11	their	they	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	unwillingness	unwillingness	NN	O	10	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	cooperate	cooperate	VB	O	12	acl
15	in	in	IN	O	21	mark
16	what	what	WP	O	21	nsubj
17	very	very	RB	O	18	advmod
18	well	well	RB	O	21	advmod
19	was	be	VBD	O	21	cop
20	a	a	DT	O	21	det
21	mutilation	mutilation	NN	O	14	advcl
22	of	of	IN	O	24	case
23	a	a	DT	O	24	det
24	human	human	JJ	O	21	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	3	mark
2	Lovecraft	lovecraft	NN	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	made	make	VBD	O	22	advcl
4	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	obvious	obvious	JJ	O	3	xcomp
6	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
7	nobody	nobody	NN	O	13	nsubj
8	in	in	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	line	line	NN	O	7	nmod
12	necessarily	necessarily	RB	O	13	advmod
13	wanted	want	VBD	O	5	ccomp
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	participate	participate	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	this	this	DT	O	18	det
18	degeneration	degeneration	NN	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	22	punct
20	nothing	nothing	NN	O	22	nsubj
21	was	be	VBD	O	22	aux
22	going	go	VBG	O	0	ROOT
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	stop	stop	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	it	it	PRP	O	24	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	only	only	RB	O	3	advmod
3	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	matter	matter	NN	O	3	xcomp
6	of	of	IN	O	7	case
7	time	time	NN	O	5	nmod
8	before	before	IN	O	10	mark
9	somebody	somebody	NN	O	10	nsubj
10	fell	fall	VBD	O	3	advcl
11	victim	victim	NN	O	10	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	curse	curse	NN	O	10	nmod
15	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubjpass
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	auxpass
17	laid	lay	VBN	O	14	acl:relcl
18	upon	upon	IN	O	20	case
19	their	they	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	family	family	NN	O	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Later	later	RB	O	18	advmod
2	in	in	IN	O	4	case
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	story	story	NN	O	18	nmod
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	efforts	effort	NNS	O	18	nsubj
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	rid	rid	VB	O	6	acl
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	evil	evil	JJ	O	12	amod
12	traces	trace	NNS	O	8	nmod
13	at	at	IN	O	15	case
14	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	15	compound
15	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
16	did	do	VBD	O	18	aux
17	not	not	RB	O	18	neg
18	succeed	succeed	VB	O	0	ROOT
19	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	found	find	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	end	end	NN	O	3	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	passage	passage	NN	O	6	nmod
10	saying	say	VBG	O	3	ccomp
11	ancient	ancient	JJ	O	12	amod
12	language	language	NN	O	10	dobj
13	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
14	``	``	``	O	15	punct
15	crouching	crouch	VBG	O	10	conj
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	blackness	blackness	NN	O	15	nmod
19	over	over	IN	O	24	case
20	the	the	DT	O	24	det
21	plump	plump	JJ	O	24	amod
22	,	,	,	O	24	punct
23	half-eaten	half-eaten	JJ	O	24	amod
24	body	body	NN	O	18	nmod
25	''	''	''	O	15	punct
26	of	of	IN	O	29	case
27	his	he	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
28	own	own	JJ	O	29	amod
29	friend	friend	NN	O	15	nmod
30	,	,	,	O	29	punct
31	Captain	Captain	NNP	O	32	compound
32	Norrys	Norrys	NNP	PERSON	29	appos
33	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	34	punct
34	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	32	appos
35	44	44	CD	NUMBER	34	nummod
36	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	34	punct
37	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	idea	idea	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	human	human	JJ	O	5	amod
5	degeneration	degeneration	NN	O	2	nmod
6	took	take	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	full	full	JJ	O	8	amod
8	effect	effect	NN	O	6	dobj
9	on	on	IN	O	10	case
10	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	O	6	nmod
11	even	even	RB	O	14	advmod
12	though	though	IN	O	14	mark
13	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	resisted	resist	VBD	O	6	advcl
15	its	its	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	efforts	effort	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	along	along	IN	O	20	case
18	with	with	IN	O	20	case
19	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	family	family	NN	O	14	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	led	lead	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	back	back	RB	O	3	advmod
5	to	to	TO	O	7	case
6	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	7	compound
7	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
9	could	could	MD	O	11	aux
10	not	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	avoid	avoid	VB	O	3	conj
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	curse	curse	NN	O	11	dobj
14	that	that	WDT	O	16	nsubjpass
15	was	be	VBD	O	16	auxpass
16	bound	bind	VBN	O	13	acl:relcl
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	control	control	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	manipulate	manipulate	VB	O	18	conj
21	him	he	PRP	O	18	dobj
22	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	curiosity	curiosity	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	actively	actively	RB	O	5	advmod
5	worked	work	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	against	against	IN	O	8	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	drive	drive	NN	O	5	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	break	break	VB	O	8	acl
11	free	free	JJ	O	10	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	curse	curse	NN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	quality	quality	NN	O	13	nsubj
3	that	that	WDT	O	4	nsubj
4	turned	turn	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
5	into	into	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	downfall	downfall	NN	O	4	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	13	punct
11	was	be	VBD	O	13	cop
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	curiosity	curiosity	NN	O	0	ROOT
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	drive	drive	NN	O	13	conj
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	learn	learn	VB	O	13	acl
18	about	about	IN	O	20	case
19	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	families	family	NNS	O	17	nmod
21	past	past	IN	DATE	20	case
22	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Especially	especially	RB	O	0	ROOT
2	with	with	IN	O	3	case
3	concern	concern	NN	O	1	nmod
4	towards	towards	IN	O	6	case
5	darker	darker	JJR	O	6	amod
6	pieces	piece	NNS	O	3	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	family	family	NN	O	10	compound
10	line	line	NN	O	6	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Lovecraft	lovecraft	NN	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	developed	develop	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
4	's	's	POS	O	3	case
5	cursed	cursed	JJ	O	6	amod
6	manipulation	manipulation	NN	O	2	dobj
7	through	through	IN	O	10	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	desperate	desperate	JJ	O	10	amod
10	need	need	NN	O	2	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	discover	discover	VB	O	2	dep
13	what	what	WP	O	12	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	15	punct
15	when	when	WRB	O	12	discourse
16	,	,	,	O	15	punct
17	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
18	how	how	WRB	O	21	advmod
19	things	thing	NNS	O	21	nsubj
20	were	be	VBD	O	21	aux
21	happening	happen	VBG	O	12	conj
22	at	at	IN	O	24	case
23	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	24	compound
24	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	21	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
2	initial	initial	JJ	O	3	amod
3	interest	interest	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	6	auxpass
5	ironically	ironically	RB	O	6	advmod
6	gained	gain	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	from	from	IN	O	10	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	younger	younger	JJR	O	10	amod
10	brother	brother	NN	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	Alfred	Alfred	NNP	PERSON	10	appos
13	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	4	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	war	war	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	caused	cause	VBD	O	11	advcl
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	brother	brother	NN	O	4	dobj
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	die	die	VB	O	6	acl
9	,	,	,	O	11	punct
10	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
11	received	receive	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	letters	letter	NNS	O	11	dobj
13	from	from	IN	O	14	case
14	him	he	PRP	O	12	nmod
15	that	that	DT	O	16	nsubj
16	revealed	reveal	VBD	O	12	acl:relcl
17	``	``	``	O	23	punct
18	a	a	DT	O	23	det
19	colourful	colourful	JJ	O	23	amod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	19	advmod
22	sinister	sinister	JJ	O	23	amod
23	history	history	NN	O	16	dobj
24	''	''	''	O	23	punct
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	his	he	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
27	family	family	NN	O	23	nmod
28	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	29	punct
29	Lovecraft	lovecraft	NN	ORGANIZATION	27	appos
30	32	32	CD	NUMBER	29	nummod
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	29	punct
32	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	det
2	intrigued	intrigued	JJ	O	3	amod
3	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	14	nsubj
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	search	search	VB	O	3	acl
6	for	for	IN	O	8	case
7	more	more	JJR	O	8	amod
8	clues	clue	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	on	on	IN	O	10	case
10	what	what	WP	O	8	nmod
11	really	really	RB	O	14	advmod
12	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	charge	charge	NN	O	0	ROOT
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	dark	dark	JJ	O	18	amod
18	parts	part	NNS	O	14	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	24	case
20	his	he	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	family	family	NN	O	24	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	ancestral	ancestral	JJ	O	24	amod
24	line	line	NN	O	18	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	curiosity	curiosity	NN	O	9	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	fact	fact	NN	O	2	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	9	punct
6	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	main	main	JJ	O	9	amod
9	contributor	contributor	NN	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	14	case
11	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	14	nmod:poss
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	eventual	eventual	JJ	O	14	amod
14	outburst	outburst	NN	O	9	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
16	actions	action	NNS	O	9	conj
17	by	by	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	end	end	NN	O	16	nmod
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	story	story	NN	O	19	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Lovecraft	lovecraft	NN	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	showed	show	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
4	's	's	POS	O	3	case
5	curious	curious	JJ	O	6	amod
6	characteristic	characteristic	NN	O	2	dobj
7	through	through	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	many	many	JJ	O	10	amod
10	questions	question	NNS	O	2	nmod
11	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
12	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	asked	ask	VBD	O	2	ccomp
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Often	often	RB	O	2	advmod
2	times	time	NNS	O	6	ccomp
3	,	,	,	O	6	punct
4	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
5	would	would	MD	O	6	aux
6	find	find	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	himself	himself	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	thinking	think	VBG	O	6	ccomp
9	about	about	IN	O	12	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
11	family	family	NN	O	12	compound
12	line	line	NN	O	8	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	8	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
15	questioning	question	VBG	O	8	conj
16	if	if	IN	O	19	mark
17	Walter	Walter	NNP	PERSON	19	nsubj
18	had	have	VBD	O	19	aux
19	come	come	VBN	O	15	advcl
20	across	across	IN	O	25	case
21	``	``	``	O	25	punct
22	Some	some	DT	O	25	det
23	appalling	appalling	JJ	O	25	amod
24	ancient	ancient	JJ	O	25	amod
25	rite	rite	NN	O	19	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	19	punct
27	or	or	CC	O	19	cc
28	stumbled	stumble	VBN	O	19	conj
29	upon	upon	IN	O	34	case
30	some	some	DT	O	34	det
31	frightful	frightful	JJ	O	34	amod
32	and	and	CC	O	31	cc
33	revealing	revealing	JJ	O	31	conj
34	symbol	symbol	NN	O	28	nmod
35	in	in	IN	O	37	case
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	priory	priory	NN	O	34	nmod
38	''	''	''	O	37	punct
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	37	appos
41	35	35	CD	NUMBER	40	nummod
42	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct
43	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	understanding	understanding	NN	O	13	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	cursed	curse	VBN	O	7	amod
7	gods	god	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	that	that	WDT	O	9	nsubj
9	affected	affect	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	family	family	NN	O	9	dobj
12	``	``	``	O	13	punct
13	repelled	repel	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	me	I	PRP	O	13	dobj
15	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	16	punct
16	Delapore	delapore	NN	O	13	nmod
17	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	16	punct
18	greatly	greatly	RB	O	13	advmod
19	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Their	they	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	persistence	persistence	NN	O	18	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
5	their	they	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	application	application	NN	O	2	conj
7	to	to	TO	O	11	case
8	so	so	RB	O	9	advmod
9	long	long	RB	O	11	advmod
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	line	line	NN	O	6	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	my	my	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	ancestors	ancestor	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	2	punct
16	were	be	VBD	O	18	cop
17	especially	especially	RB	O	18	advmod
18	annoying	annoying	JJ	O	0	ROOT
19	''	''	''	O	18	punct
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	dep
22	34	34	CD	NUMBER	21	nummod
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
24	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	anger	anger	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	LOCATION	2	nmod
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
6	one	one	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
7	that	that	WDT	O	8	nsubj
8	contributes	contribute	VBZ	O	6	acl:relcl
9	to	to	TO	O	12	case
10	both	both	DT	O	12	cc:preconj
11	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	fear	fear	NN	O	8	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	drive	drive	NN	O	12	conj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	understand	understand	VB	O	8	xcomp
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	disturbances	disturbance	NNS	O	16	dobj
19	that	that	WDT	O	20	nsubj
20	laid	lay	VBD	O	18	acl:relcl
21	below	below	IN	O	23	case
22	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	23	compound
23	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	4	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	story	story	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	progressed	progress	VBD	O	12	advcl
5	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	cat	cat	NN	O	5	conj
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	Nigger-man	nigger-man	NN	MISC	8	appos
11	,	,	,	O	8	punct
12	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	hear	hear	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	what	what	WP	O	17	nsubjpass
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	auxpass
17	considered	consider	VBN	O	14	ccomp
18	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
19	be	be	VB	O	20	cop
20	rats	rat	NNS	O	17	xcomp
21	crawling	crawl	VBG	O	20	acl
22	in	in	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	walls	wall	NNS	O	21	nmod
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	his	he	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
27	home	home	NN	O	24	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	8	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	8	cop
3	at	at	IN	O	8	case
4	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	8	amod
5	oblivious	oblivious	JJ	O	8	amod
6	to	to	TO	O	7	case
7	these	these	DT	O	5	nmod
8	sounds	sound	NNS	O	0	ROOT
9	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	16	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	16	punct
3	as	as	IN	O	5	mark
4	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	began	begin	VBD	O	16	advcl
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	pick	pick	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	up	up	RP	O	7	compound:prt
9	on	on	IN	O	14	mark
10	what	what	WP	O	14	dobj
11	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	cat	cat	NN	O	14	nsubj
13	was	be	VBD	O	14	aux
14	hearing	hear	VBG	O	7	advcl
15	he	he	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
17	his	he	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	mind	mind	NN	O	16	dobj
19	set	set	VBN	O	18	acl
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	see	see	VB	O	19	xcomp
22	what	what	WP	O	24	nsubj
23	was	be	VBD	O	24	aux
24	happening	happen	VBG	O	21	ccomp
25	at	at	IN	O	27	case
26	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	27	compound
27	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	24	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Nigger-Man	Nigger-Man	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	would	would	MD	O	4	aux
3	often	often	RB	O	4	advmod
4	lead	lead	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	Delapore	delapore	RB	PERSON	4	advmod
6	as	as	IN	O	8	mark
7	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	used	use	VBD	O	4	advcl
9	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	cat	cat	NN	O	8	dobj
11	as	as	IN	O	13	case
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	reference	reference	NN	O	8	nmod
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	try	try	VB	O	8	advcl
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	decipher	decipher	VB	O	15	conj
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	reasons	reason	NNS	O	15	dobj
20	behind	behind	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	presence	presence	NN	O	15	nmod
23	of	of	IN	O	24	case
24	rats	rat	NNS	O	22	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	commented	comment	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	on	on	IN	O	9	case
4	his	he	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	cat	cat	NN	O	9	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	``	``	``	O	9	punct
8	persuasive	persuasive	JJ	O	9	amod
9	manner	manner	NN	O	2	nmod
10	''	''	''	O	9	punct
11	as	as	IN	O	13	mark
12	it	it	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	scampered	scamper	VBD	O	2	advcl
14	around	around	IN	O	15	mark
15	looking	look	VBG	O	13	advcl
16	for	for	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	rats	rat	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	itself	itself	PRP	O	18	advmod
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	appos
22	40	40	CD	NUMBER	21	nummod
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
24	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	5	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	found	find	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	himself	himself	PRP	O	5	dobj
7	discovering	discover	VBG	O	5	xcomp
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	downward	downward	JJ	O	10	amod
10	direction	direction	NN	O	7	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	rats	rat	NNS	O	10	nmod
14	to	to	TO	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	place	place	NN	O	7	nmod
17	far	far	RB	O	16	advmod
18	below	below	IN	O	20	case
19	Exham	Exham	NNP	LOCATION	20	compound
20	Priory	Priory	NNP	LOCATION	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	4	mark
2	he	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
4	uncertain	uncertain	JJ	O	9	advcl
5	,	,	,	O	9	punct
6	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	9	nsubj
7	did	do	VBD	O	9	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	deny	deny	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
11	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nsubj
12	``	``	``	O	14	punct
13	fascination	fascination	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	became	become	VBD	O	9	ccomp
15	twofold	twofold	JJ	O	14	xcomp
16	''	''	''	O	14	punct
17	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
18	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	decided	decide	VBD	O	14	conj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	pursue	pursue	VB	O	19	xcomp
22	what	what	WP	O	24	nsubj
23	was	be	VBD	O	24	aux
24	causing	cause	VBG	O	21	ccomp
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	disturbances	disturbance	NNS	O	24	dobj
27	in	in	IN	O	29	case
28	his	he	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
29	house	house	NN	O	26	nmod
30	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	31	punct
31	Lovecraft	lovecraft	NN	ORGANIZATION	29	appos
32	40	40	CD	NUMBER	31	nummod
33	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	31	punct
34	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	2	case
2	anytime	anytime	RB	O	9	nmod
3	throughout	throughout	IN	O	5	case
4	his	he	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	search	search	NN	O	2	nmod
6	Delapore	delapore	NN	PERSON	9	nsubj
7	could	could	MD	O	9	aux
8	have	have	VB	O	9	aux
9	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	level	level	NN	O	12	nsubj
12	headed	head	VBD	O	9	ccomp
13	decision	decision	NN	O	12	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
15	stopped	stop	VBD	O	12	conj
16	what	what	WP	O	19	dobj
17	he	he	PRP	O	19	nsubj
18	was	be	VBD	O	19	aux
19	doing	do	VBG	O	15	ccomp
20	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	11	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	11	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	knowledge	knowledge	NN	O	11	nsubj
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	gained	gain	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	family	family	NN	O	4	nmod
10	only	only	RB	O	11	advmod
11	pushed	push	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	him	he	PRP	O	11	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	develop	develop	VB	O	11	xcomp
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	further	further	JJ	O	17	amod
17	understanding	understanding	NN	O	14	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	21	mark
19	what	what	WP	O	21	nsubj
20	was	be	VBD	O	21	aux
21	bothering	bother	VBG	O	17	acl
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	household	household	NN	O	21	dobj
24	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	desire	desire	NN	O	13	nsubj
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	know	know	VB	O	2	acl
5	more	more	JJR	O	4	dobj
6	about	about	IN	O	8	case
7	his	he	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	family	family	NN	O	4	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	home	home	NN	O	8	conj
12	slowly	slowly	RB	O	13	advmod
13	pulled	pull	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	13	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	case
16	depths	depths	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	curse	curse	NN	O	16	nmod
20	laid	lay	VBN	O	19	acl
21	upon	upon	IN	O	22	case
22	him	he	PRP	O	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Lovecraft	Lovecraft	NNP	O	2	nsubj
2	used	use	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	help	help	VB	O	2	dep
6	convert	convert	VB	O	5	xcomp
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	idea	idea	NN	O	6	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	human	human	JJ	O	11	amod
11	understanding	understanding	NN	O	8	nmod
12	plus	plus	CC	O	8	cc
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	curse	curse	NN	O	8	conj
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	human	human	JJ	O	17	amod
17	degeneration	degeneration	NN	O	14	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
19	how	how	WRB	O	22	advmod
20	it	it	PRP	O	22	nsubjpass
21	is	be	VBZ	O	22	auxpass
22	correlated	correlate	VBN	O	5	conj
23	with	with	IN	O	24	case
24	danger	danger	NN	O	22	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Because	because	IN	O	5	case
2	of	of	IN	O	1	mwe
3	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
4	's	's	POS	O	3	case
5	curse	curse	NN	O	14	nmod
6	that	that	WDT	O	8	nsubjpass
7	was	be	VBD	O	8	auxpass
8	laid	lay	VBN	O	5	acl:relcl
9	upon	upon	IN	O	10	case
10	him	he	PRP	O	8	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	14	punct
12	it	it	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
14	inevitable	inevitable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
15	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
16	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	18	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	18	aux
18	going	go	VBG	O	14	ccomp
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	die	die	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Delaware	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	curiosity	curiosity	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	6	auxpass
5	clearly	clearly	RB	O	6	advmod
6	shown	show	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	throughout	throughout	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	text	text	NN	O	6	nmod
10	as	as	IN	O	12	mark
11	it	it	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	worked	work	VBD	O	6	advcl
13	against	against	IN	O	16	case
14	his	he	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	resistant	resistant	JJ	O	16	amod
16	actions	action	NNS	O	12	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	combination	combination	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	both	both	DT	O	2	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	these	these	DT	O	7	det
7	factors	factor	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	led	lead	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	13	case
10	Delapore	Delapore	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod:poss
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	unavoidable	unavoidable	JJ	O	13	amod
13	death	death	NN	O	8	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	8	punct

