1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	short	short	JJ	O	4	amod
3	story	story	NN	O	4	compound
4	Everything	everything	NN	O	17	nsubj
5	That	that	WDT	O	6	nsubj
6	Rises	rise	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
7	Must	must	MD	O	8	aux
8	Converge	converge	VB	O	6	ccomp
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	written	write	VBN	O	4	acl
11	by	by	IN	O	13	case
12	Flannery	Flannery	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	4	punct
15	is	be	VBZ	O	17	cop
16	about	about	IN	O	17	case
17	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	mother	mother	NN	O	17	conj
21	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	both	both	DT	O	3	dep
3	get	get	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	bus	bus	NN	O	3	dep
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
9	they	they	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	get	get	VBP	O	6	conj
11	on	on	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	bus	bus	NN	O	14	compound
14	reality	reality	NN	O	10	nmod
15	breaking	break	VBG	O	14	acl
16	events	event	NNS	O	17	nsubj
17	happen	happen	VB	O	15	ccomp
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Then	then	RB	O	11	advmod
2	in	in	IN	O	4	case
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	end	end	NN	O	11	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	story	story	NN	O	4	nmod
8	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	mother	mother	NN	O	11	nsubj
11	dies	die	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	story	story	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	written	write	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	around	around	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	time	time	NN	O	4	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	12	case
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
11	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	movement	movement	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	caused	cause	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	great	great	JJ	O	6	amod
6	shift	shift	NN	O	3	dobj
7	in	in	IN	O	10	case
8	people	people	NNS	O	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	culture	culture	NN	O	6	nmod
11	there	there	EX	O	12	expl
12	were	be	VBD	O	6	acl:relcl
13	many	many	JJ	O	14	amod
14	things	thing	NNS	O	12	nsubj
15	that	that	WDT	O	16	nsubj
16	changed	change	VBD	O	14	acl:relcl
17	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Legislation	legislation	NN	O	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	passed	pass	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	helps	help	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
6	African	african	JJ	MISC	7	amod
7	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	5	dobj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	get	get	VB	O	5	xcomp
10	their	they	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	freedom	freedom	NN	O	9	dobj
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	legislations	legislation	NNS	O	0	ROOT
3	where	where	WRB	O	16	dep
4	laws	law	NNS	O	3	dep
5	about	about	IN	O	6	case
6	voting	voting	NN	O	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	equality	equality	NN	O	6	appos
9	between	between	IN	O	11	case
10	different	different	JJ	O	11	amod
11	races	race	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	6	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
14	also	also	RB	O	3	conj
15	about	about	IN	O	14	case
16	schools	school	NNS	O	2	dep
17	as	as	RB	O	16	advmod
18	well	well	RB	O	17	mwe
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	story	story	NN	O	3	compound
3	Everything	everything	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	That	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	Rises	rise	VBZ	O	3	acl:relcl
6	Must	must	MD	O	7	aux
7	Converge	converge	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	shows	show	NNS	O	7	dobj
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	reader	reader	NN	O	7	nmod:tmod
11	what	what	WDT	O	12	det
12	life	life	NN	O	19	nsubj
13	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
14	like	like	IN	O	19	case
15	after	after	IN	O	19	case
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
18	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
19	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	acl:relcl
20	with	with	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	legislation	legislation	NN	O	19	nmod
23	in	in	IN	O	24	case
24	place	place	NN	O	22	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	story	story	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	literary	literary	JJ	O	5	amod
5	devices	device	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	setting	set	VBG	O	5	acl
7	,	,	,	O	5	punct
8	characterization	characterization	NN	O	5	appos
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	hubris	hubris	NN	O	8	appos
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	show	show	VB	O	10	acl
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	reader	reader	NN	O	12	dobj
15	what	what	WDT	O	16	det
16	life	life	NN	O	23	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	23	cop
18	like	like	IN	O	23	case
19	after	after	IN	O	23	case
20	the	the	DT	O	23	det
21	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
22	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
23	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	acl:relcl
24	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	setting	setting	NN	O	10	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	Everything	everything	NN	O	4	nmod
7	That	that	WDT	O	8	nsubj
8	Rises	rise	VBZ	O	6	acl:relcl
9	Must	must	MD	O	10	aux
10	Converge	converge	VB	O	2	ccomp
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	show	show	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	people	people	NNS	O	12	dobj
14	how	how	WRB	O	16	advmod
15	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	16	nsubj
16	has	have	VBZ	O	12	dep
17	change	change	NN	O	16	dobj
18	after	after	IN	O	22	case
19	the	the	DT	O	22	det
20	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
21	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
22	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	story	story	NN	O	5	nmod
4	O'Conner	O'Conner	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	sets	set	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	5	dobj
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	mother	mother	NN	O	6	conj
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	bus	bus	NN	O	9	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	bus	bus	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	good	good	JJ	O	6	amod
6	place	place	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	show	show	VB	O	6	acl
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	change	change	NN	O	8	dobj
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
13	after	after	IN	O	17	case
14	the	the	DT	O	17	det
15	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
16	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
18	because	because	IN	O	23	mark
19	at	at	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	bus	bus	NN	O	23	nmod
22	it	it	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	shows	show	VBZ	O	8	advcl
24	how	how	WRB	O	29	advmod
25	thing	thing	NN	O	29	nsubjpass
26	have	have	VBP	O	29	aux
27	now	now	RB	DATE	29	advmod
28	been	be	VBN	O	29	auxpass
29	desegregated	desegregate	VBN	O	23	ccomp
30	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Having	have	VBG	O	8	csubj
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	bus	bus	NN	O	1	dobj
4	as	as	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	setting	setting	NN	O	3	nmod
7	also	also	RB	O	1	advmod
8	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	racism	racism	NN	O	8	dobj
11	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
13	still	still	RB	O	14	advmod
14	prevalent	prevalent	JJ	O	10	acl:relcl
15	after	after	IN	O	19	case
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
18	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
19	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	mother	mother	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	both	both	DT	O	4	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	these	these	DT	O	8	det
8	concepts	concept	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	story	story	NN	O	8	nmod
12	with	with	IN	O	14	case
13	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	conversation	conversation	NN	O	11	nmod
15	with	with	IN	O	18	case
16	another	another	DT	O	18	det
17	white	white	JJ	O	18	amod
18	person	person	NN	O	4	nmod
19	that	that	WDT	O	21	nsubj
20	was	be	VBD	O	21	cop
21	one	one	CD	NUMBER	18	acl:relcl
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	bus	bus	NN	O	21	dep
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	3	amod
3	comment	comment	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	WDT	O	8	dobj
5	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	mother	mother	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	made	make	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
9	was	be	VBD	O	8	ccomp
10	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
11	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	was	be	VBD	O	13	cop
13	happy	happy	JJ	O	9	ccomp
14	that	that	IN	O	16	case
15	white	white	JJ	O	16	amod
16	people	people	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	''	''	''	O	16	punct
18	...	...	:	O	16	punct
19	have	have	VB	O	16	dep
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	bus	bus	NN	O	19	dobj
22	to	to	TO	O	19	acl
23	...	...	:	O	16	punct
24	''	''	''	O	16	punct
25	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
26	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	3	appos
27	185	185	CD	NUMBER	26	nummod
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
29	themselves	themselves	PRP	O	3	dep
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Then	then	RB	O	0	ROOT
2	after	after	IN	O	5	mark
3	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
4	she	she	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	strikes	strike	VBZ	O	1	dep
6	up	up	RP	O	5	compound:prt
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	conversation	conversation	NN	O	5	dobj
9	with	with	IN	O	12	case
10	another	another	DT	O	12	det
11	white	white	JJ	O	12	amod
12	person	person	NN	O	8	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	white	white	JJ	O	4	amod
3	person	person	NN	O	4	compound
4	talks	talk	NNS	O	0	ROOT
5	about	about	IN	O	30	mark
6	how	how	WRB	O	30	advmod
7	she	she	PRP	O	30	nsubj
8	was	be	VBD	O	30	cop
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	bus	bus	NN	O	30	nmod
12	one	one	CD	NUMBER	11	nmod
13	where	where	WRB	O	12	dep
14	she	she	PRP	O	12	dep
15	saw	see	VBD	O	14	acl
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	lot	lot	NN	O	15	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	black	black	JJ	O	20	amod
20	people	people	NNS	O	17	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	how	how	WRB	O	23	advmod
23	the	the	DT	O	25	amod
24	black	black	JJ	O	25	amod
25	people	people	NNS	O	26	dep
26	where	where	WRB	O	20	conj
27	''	''	''	O	11	punct
28	...	...	:	O	30	punct
29	up	up	RP	O	30	dep
30	front	front	NN	O	4	acl
31	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
32	all	all	DT	O	30	conj
33	through	through	IN	O	32	acl
34	...	...	:	O	30	punct
35	''	''	''	O	30	punct
36	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	37	punct
37	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	30	dep
38	185	185	CD	NUMBER	37	nummod
39	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	37	punct
40	the	the	DT	O	41	det
41	bus	bus	NN	O	4	dep
42	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	conversation	conversation	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	12	advmod
5	life	life	NN	O	12	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
7	like	like	IN	O	12	case
8	after	after	IN	O	12	case
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
11	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	ccomp
13	as	as	IN	O	17	mark
14	black	black	JJ	O	15	amod
15	people	people	NNS	O	17	nsubj
16	are	be	VBP	O	17	cop
17	free	free	JJ	O	12	dep
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	sit	sit	VB	O	17	xcomp
20	where	where	WRB	O	23	advmod
21	ever	ever	RB	O	23	advmod
22	they	they	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	wanted	want	VBD	O	19	advcl
24	,	,	,	O	12	punct
25	but	but	CC	O	12	cc
26	also	also	RB	O	28	advmod
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	racism	racism	NN	O	12	conj
29	that	that	WDT	O	33	nsubj
30	was	be	VBD	O	33	cop
31	still	still	RB	O	33	advmod
32	in	in	IN	O	33	case
33	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	28	acl:relcl
34	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	reason	reason	NN	O	27	nsubj
3	why	why	WRB	O	4	advmod
4	having	have	VBG	O	2	acl:relcl
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	story	story	NN	O	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	setting	setting	NN	O	13	nsubj
9	in	in	IN	O	12	case
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	bus	bus	NN	O	12	compound
12	help	help	NN	O	8	nmod
13	show	show	VB	O	4	ccomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	reader	reader	NN	O	13	dobj
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	life	life	NN	O	4	dep
18	after	after	IN	O	22	case
19	the	the	DT	O	22	det
20	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
21	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	22	compound
22	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	nmod
23	because	because	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	setting	setting	NN	O	22	nmod
26	also	also	RB	O	27	advmod
27	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
28	how	how	WRB	O	31	advmod
29	black	black	JJ	O	30	amod
30	people	people	NNS	O	31	nsubj
31	feel	feel	VBP	O	27	ccomp
32	as	as	RB	O	31	advmod
33	well	well	RB	O	32	mwe
34	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	Everything	everything	NN	O	4	nmod
3	That	that	WDT	O	4	nsubj
4	Rises	rise	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	Must	must	MD	O	6	aux
6	Converge	converge	VB	O	4	ccomp
7	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
8	also	also	RB	O	9	advmod
9	brings	bring	VBZ	O	6	ccomp
10	in	in	IN	O	13	case
11	African	african	JJ	MISC	13	amod
12	American	american	JJ	MISC	13	amod
13	people	people	NNS	O	9	nmod
14	into	into	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	bus	bus	NN	O	9	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	setting	setting	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	perfect	perfect	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	as	as	IN	O	9	mark
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	reader	reader	NN	O	9	nsubj
8	can	can	MD	O	9	aux
9	see	see	VB	O	4	advcl
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	reaction	reaction	NN	O	9	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	black	black	JJ	O	14	amod
14	people	people	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	toward	toward	IN	O	19	case
16	white	white	JJ	O	17	amod
17	people	people	NNS	O	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	racism	racism	NN	O	9	nmod
20	because	because	IN	O	25	mark
21	they	they	PRP	O	25	nsubj
22	are	be	VBP	O	25	cop
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	a	a	DT	O	25	det
25	bus	bus	NN	O	9	advcl
26	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	bus	bus	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	an	a	DT	O	6	det
5	enclosed	enclosed	JJ	O	6	amod
6	space	space	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	where	where	WRB	O	9	advmod
8	people	people	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	have	have	VBP	O	6	acl:relcl
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	be	be	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	with	with	IN	O	16	mark
13	other	other	JJ	O	14	amod
14	people	people	NNS	O	16	nsubj
15	thus	thus	RB	O	16	advmod
16	conflict	conflict	VBP	O	11	advcl
17	can	can	MD	O	18	aux
18	arise	arise	VB	O	16	ccomp
19	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
20	be	be	VB	O	21	auxpass
21	seen	see	VBN	O	18	conj
22	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	6	advmod
2	the	the	DT	O	5	det
3	African	african	JJ	MISC	5	amod
4	American	american	JJ	MISC	5	amod
5	women	woman	NNS	O	6	nsubj
6	comes	come	VBZ	O	16	advcl
7	into	into	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	bus	bus	NN	O	6	nmod
10	with	with	IN	O	12	case
11	her	she	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	child	child	NN	O	9	nmod
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	reader	reader	NN	O	16	nsubj
15	soon	soon	RB	O	16	advmod
16	sees	see	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
17	that	that	IN	O	22	mark
18	the	the	DT	O	21	det
19	African	african	JJ	MISC	21	amod
20	American	american	JJ	MISC	21	amod
21	mother	mother	NN	O	22	nsubj
22	is	be	VBZ	O	16	ccomp
23	not	not	RB	O	24	dep
24	will	will	MD	O	22	ccomp
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	allow	allow	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	her	she	PRP$	O	28	nmod:poss
28	child	child	NN	O	26	dobj
29	to	to	TO	O	31	mark
30	be	be	VB	O	31	auxpass
31	treated	treat	VBN	O	28	acl
32	like	like	IN	O	34	case
33	a	a	DT	O	34	det
34	dog	dog	NN	O	31	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	tells	tell	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	of	of	IN	O	8	mark
4	how	how	WRB	O	8	advmod
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	mother	mother	NN	O	8	nsubj
7	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
8	smile	smile	VB	O	2	advcl
9	at	at	IN	O	13	case
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	African	African	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
12	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
13	child	child	NN	O	8	nmod
14	that	that	WDT	O	19	nsubj
15	was	be	VBD	O	19	cop
16	his	he	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	mother	mother	NN	O	19	nmod:poss
18	's	's	POS	O	17	case
19	smile	smile	NN	O	13	acl:relcl
20	when	when	WRB	O	22	advmod
21	she	she	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	is	be	VBZ	O	8	advcl
23	''	''	''	O	8	punct
24	...	...	:	O	8	punct
25	being	be	VBG	O	27	cop
26	particularly	particularly	RB	O	27	advmod
27	gracious	gracious	JJ	O	8	parataxis
28	to	to	TO	O	30	case
29	an	a	DT	O	30	det
30	inferior	inferior	JJ	O	27	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	2	punct
32	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	190	190	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	mother	mother	NN	O	4	compound
4	attitude	attitude	NN	O	8	nsubj
5	was	be	VBD	O	8	cop
6	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
7	uncommon	uncommon	JJ	O	8	advcl
8	as	as	IN	O	0	ROOT
9	''	''	''	O	8	punct
10	...	...	:	O	8	punct
11	racism	racism	NN	O	8	parataxis
12	remained	remain	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
13	alive	alive	JJ	O	12	xcomp
14	and	and	CC	O	12	advmod
15	well	well	RB	O	16	advmod
16	long	long	RB	O	12	advcl
17	after	after	IN	O	16	case
18	...	...	:	O	16	punct
19	''	''	''	O	12	punct
20	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
21	Ross	Ross	NNP	PERSON	12	dep
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	Austin	Austin	NNP	LOCATION	21	conj
24	:	:	:	O	21	punct
25	On	on	IN	O	27	amod
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	Impact	impact	NN	O	21	dep
28	of	of	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	nmod
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
32	the	the	DT	O	35	det
33	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	compound
34	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	35	compound
35	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	dep
36	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	why	why	WRB	O	8	advmod
4	buses	bus	NNS	O	8	nsubj
5	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	good	good	JJ	O	8	amod
8	setting	setting	NN	O	2	advcl
9	for	for	IN	O	11	case
10	this	this	DT	O	11	det
11	story	story	NN	O	8	nmod
12	as	as	IN	O	16	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	reader	reader	NN	O	16	nsubj
15	can	can	MD	O	16	aux
16	see	see	VB	O	11	nmod
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	racism	racism	NN	O	16	dobj
19	still	still	RB	O	16	advmod
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	16	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	16	punct
23	but	but	CC	O	16	cc
24	also	also	RB	O	26	advmod
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	desegregation	desegregation	NN	O	16	conj
27	of	of	IN	O	28	case
28	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	26	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	next	next	JJ	O	4	amod
3	literary	literary	JJ	O	4	amod
4	device	device	NN	O	16	nsubj
5	that	that	WDT	O	7	dobj
6	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	uses	use	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	show	show	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	changes	change	NNS	O	9	dobj
12	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	13	nsubj
13	went	go	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
14	through	through	IN	O	13	nmod
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
16	characterization	characterization	NN	O	0	ROOT
17	of	of	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	characters	character	NNS	O	20	compound
20	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	16	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	his	he	PRP$	O	23	nmod:poss
23	Mother	mother	NN	O	20	conj
24	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	characterization	characterization	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	starts	start	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	off	off	RP	O	4	compound:prt
6	with	with	IN	O	7	case
7	readers	reader	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	seeing	see	VBG	O	7	acl
9	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	has	have	VBZ	O	8	ccomp
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	take	take	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	mother	mother	NN	O	13	dobj
16	to	to	TO	O	19	case
17	an	a	DT	O	19	det
18	exercising	exercise	VBG	O	19	amod
19	class	class	NN	O	13	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Then	then	RB	O	5	advmod
2	as	as	IN	O	5	mark
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	story	story	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	goes	go	VBZ	O	10	csubj
6	on	on	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	reader	reader	NN	O	5	nmod
9	can	can	MD	O	10	aux
10	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
11	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
12	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
13	does	do	VBZ	O	15	aux
14	not	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	respect	respect	VB	O	10	ccomp
16	his	he	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	mother	mother	NN	O	15	dobj
18	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	reason	reason	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	for	for	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	disrespect	disrespect	NN	O	2	nmod
6	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
8	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	mother	mother	NN	O	15	nsubj
11	is	be	VBZ	O	15	cop
12	still	still	RB	O	15	advmod
13	with	with	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	thinking	thinking	NN	O	6	ccomp
16	before	before	IN	O	20	case
17	the	the	DT	O	20	det
18	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
19	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
20	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	way	way	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	thinking	thinking	NN	O	2	nmod
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	way	way	NN	O	0	ROOT
8	of	of	IN	O	9	mark
9	thinking	think	VBG	O	7	acl
10	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
11	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
12	hates	hate	VBZ	O	9	ccomp
13	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Throughout	throughout	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	story	story	NN	O	7	nmod
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	reader	reader	NN	O	7	nsubj
6	can	can	MD	O	7	aux
7	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
9	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
10	wants	want	VBZ	O	7	ccomp
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	teach	teach	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	mother	mother	NN	O	12	dep
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	less	less	JJR	O	12	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	24	mark
18	how	how	WRB	O	24	advmod
19	she	she	PRP	O	24	nsubj
20	should	should	MD	O	24	aux
21	not	not	RB	O	24	neg
22	be	be	VB	O	24	cop
23	so	so	RB	O	24	advmod
24	racist	racist	JJ	O	16	acl
25	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	way	way	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	mark
4	thinking	think	VBG	O	2	acl
5	by	by	IN	O	6	case
6	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod
7	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
9	people	people	NNS	O	11	nsubj
10	are	be	VBP	O	11	aux
11	changing	change	VBG	O	7	ccomp
12	as	as	IN	O	14	nmod
13	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	says	say	VBZ	O	11	ccomp
15	he	he	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	had	have	VBD	O	14	ccomp
17	''	''	''	O	14	punct
18	...	...	:	O	7	punct
19	mixed	mixed	JJ	O	20	amod
20	feelings	feeling	NNS	O	21	nmod:npmod
21	now	now	RB	DATE	7	advmod
22	...	...	:	O	7	punct
23	''	''	''	O	7	punct
24	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
25	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	35	dep
26	183	183	CD	NUMBER	25	nummod
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
28	when	when	WRB	O	31	advmod
29	his	he	PRP$	O	30	nmod:poss
30	mother	mother	NN	O	31	nsubj
31	said	say	VBD	O	35	advcl
32	that	that	IN	O	33	case
33	life	life	NN	O	31	nmod
34	was	be	VBD	O	35	cop
35	better	better	RB	O	46	advcl
36	when	when	WRB	O	39	advmod
37	slaver	slaver	NN	O	39	nsubj
38	still	still	RB	O	39	advmod
39	existed	exist	VBD	O	35	advcl
40	and	and	CC	O	39	cc
41	that	that	IN	O	39	conj
42	biracial	biracial	JJ	O	43	amod
43	people	people	NNS	O	46	nsubj
44	are	be	VBP	O	46	cop
45	a	a	DT	O	46	det
46	tragedy	tragedy	NN	O	7	parataxis
47	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Now	now	RB	DATE	9	advmod
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	characterization	characterization	NN	O	9	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	mother	mother	NN	O	3	nmod
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
9	different	different	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	as	as	IN	O	13	mark
11	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubjpass
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	auxpass
13	used	use	VBN	O	9	advcl
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	show	show	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	difference	difference	NN	O	15	dobj
18	as	as	IN	O	20	mark
19	time	time	NN	O	20	nsubj
20	goes	go	VBZ	O	15	advcl
21	on	on	IN	O	20	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	characterization	characterization	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	mother	mother	NN	O	2	nmod
7	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
9	she	she	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
11	one	one	CD	NUMBER	7	ccomp
12	of	of	IN	O	15	case
13	many	many	JJ	O	15	amod
14	older	older	JJR	O	13	dep
15	generation	generation	NN	O	11	nmod
16	white	white	JJ	O	17	amod
17	people	people	NNS	O	15	dep
18	that	that	WDT	O	21	nsubj
19	do	do	VBP	O	21	aux
20	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
21	like	like	VB	O	17	acl:relcl
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	changes	change	NNS	O	21	dobj
24	made	make	VBN	O	23	acl
25	by	by	IN	O	26	case
26	presidents	president	NNS	O	24	nmod
27	like	like	IN	O	29	case
28	President	President	NNP	O	29	compound
29	Johnson	Johnson	NNP	PERSON	26	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	mother	mother	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	believes	believe	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
6	when	when	WRB	O	8	advmod
7	there	there	EX	O	8	expl
8	were	be	VBD	O	4	ccomp
9	slaves	slave	NNS	O	8	nsubj
10	as	as	IN	O	12	nmod
11	she	she	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	tells	tell	VBZ	O	9	acl:relcl
13	her	she	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	son	son	NN	O	12	dobj
15	when	when	WRB	O	17	advmod
16	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	points	point	VBZ	O	12	ccomp
18	out	out	RP	O	17	compound:prt
19	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
20	there	there	EX	O	21	expl
21	are	be	VBP	O	17	ccomp
22	no	no	RB	O	23	neg
23	more	more	RBR	O	21	advmod
24	slaves	slave	NNS	O	21	nsubj
25	that	that	WDT	O	24	acl:relcl
26	''	''	''	O	12	punct
27	...	...	:	O	9	punct
28	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
29	they	they	PRP	O	40	dep
30	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	32	nsubj
31	were	be	VBD	O	32	cop
32	better	better	JJR	O	29	dep
33	off	off	RP	O	32	dep
34	when	when	WRB	O	36	advmod
35	they	they	PRP	O	36	nsubj
36	were	be	VBD	O	32	advcl
37	...	...	:	O	32	punct
38	''	''	''	O	40	punct
39	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	40	punct
40	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	9	dep
41	183	183	CD	NUMBER	40	nummod
42	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	40	punct
43	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	4	det
2	two	two	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
3	different	different	JJ	O	4	amod
4	ways	way	NNS	O	7	nsubj
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	think	think	NN	O	4	nmod
7	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	reader	reader	NN	O	7	dobj
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	difference	difference	NN	O	15	nsubj
12	as	as	IN	O	13	case
13	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod
14	is	be	VBZ	O	15	aux
15	try	try	VB	O	9	acl:relcl
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	live	live	VB	O	15	xcomp
18	a	a	DT	O	19	det
19	life	life	NN	O	17	dobj
20	where	where	WRB	O	22	advmod
21	there	there	EX	O	22	expl
22	is	be	VBZ	O	17	advcl
23	equality	equality	NN	O	22	nsubj
24	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
25	change	change	VB	O	17	conj
26	his	he	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
27	mother	mother	NN	O	29	nmod:poss
28	's	's	POS	O	27	case
29	way	way	NN	O	25	dobj
30	of	of	IN	O	31	mark
31	thinking	think	VBG	O	29	acl
32	while	while	IN	O	37	mark
33	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	35	nmod:poss
34	's	's	POS	O	33	case
35	mother	mother	NN	O	37	nsubj
36	is	be	VBZ	O	37	aux
37	trying	try	VBG	O	31	advcl
38	to	to	TO	O	39	mark
39	make	make	VB	O	37	xcomp
40	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	41	nsubj
41	show	show	VB	O	39	ccomp
42	racism	racism	NN	O	41	dobj
43	to	to	TO	O	45	case
44	African	african	JJ	MISC	45	amod
45	American	American	NNP	MISC	41	nmod
46	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	conflict	conflict	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	between	between	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	two	two	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	characters	character	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	show	show	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	reader	reader	NN	O	7	dobj
10	how	how	WRB	O	15	advmod
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	newer	newer	JJR	O	13	amod
13	generations	generation	NNS	O	15	nsubj
14	was	be	VBD	O	15	aux
15	changing	change	VBG	O	9	dep
16	while	while	IN	O	20	mark
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	older	older	JJR	O	20	nsubj
19	one	one	CD	NUMBER	18	nummod
20	remained	remain	VBD	O	15	advcl
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	same	same	JJ	O	20	xcomp
23	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	last	last	JJ	O	4	amod
3	literary	literary	JJ	O	4	amod
4	device	device	NN	O	18	nsubj
5	that	that	WDT	O	7	dobj
6	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	uses	use	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	show	show	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	changes	change	NNS	O	15	nsubj
12	the	the	DT	O	15	det
13	Civil	Civil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
14	Rights	Rights	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
15	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	xcomp
16	is	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	hubris	hubris	NN	O	0	ROOT
19	or	or	CC	O	18	cc
20	pride	pride	NN	O	18	conj
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	both	both	CC	O	23	cc:preconj
23	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod
24	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
25	his	he	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
26	Mother	mother	NN	O	23	conj
27	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	pride	pride	NN	O	6	advmod
3	that	that	IN	O	2	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	mother	mother	NN	O	6	nsubj
6	feels	feel	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	12	mark
8	her	she	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	heritage	heritage	NN	O	12	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
11	very	very	RB	O	12	advmod
12	strong	strong	JJ	O	6	advcl
13	as	as	IN	O	15	mark
14	she	she	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	tells	tell	VBZ	O	12	advcl
16	her	she	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	son	son	NN	O	15	dobj
18	that	that	WDT	O	17	acl:relcl
19	''	''	''	O	6	punct
20	...	...	:	O	6	punct
21	if	if	IN	O	23	mark
22	you	you	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	know	know	VBP	O	30	advcl
24	who	who	WP	O	26	dobj
25	you	you	PRP	O	26	nsubj
26	are	be	VBP	O	23	ccomp
27	,	,	,	O	30	punct
28	you	you	PRP	O	30	nsubj
29	can	can	MD	O	30	aux
30	go	go	VB	O	6	parataxis
31	anywhere	anywhere	RB	O	30	advmod
32	.	.	.	O	6	punct
33	''	''	''	O	6	punct

1	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
3	183	183	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
4	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	2	punct
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	statement	statement	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	told	tell	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	case
6	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod
7	before	before	IN	O	11	mark
8	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	mother	mother	NN	O	11	nsubj
11	started	start	VBD	O	4	advcl
12	listing	list	VBG	O	11	xcomp
13	grandfather	grandfather	NN	O	12	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	great-grandfathers	great-grandfather	NNS	O	13	conj
16	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
17	where	where	WRB	O	13	dep
18	very	very	RB	O	12	advmod
19	important	important	JJ	O	20	amod
20	people	people	NNS	O	18	nmod:npmod
21	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	information	information	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	important	important	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	because	because	IN	O	10	mark
6	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	mother	mother	NN	O	10	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	aux
10	saying	say	VBG	O	4	advcl
11	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
12	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	knows	know	VBZ	O	10	ccomp
14	who	who	WP	O	19	dobj
15	she	she	PRP	O	19	nsubj
16	is	be	VBZ	O	19	cop
17	through	through	IN	O	19	case
18	her	she	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	family	family	NN	O	13	ccomp
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	pride	pride	NN	O	17	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	4	mark
4	knowing	know	VBG	O	2	acl
5	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
6	she	she	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	had	have	VBD	O	4	ccomp
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	family	family	NN	O	7	dobj
10	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
11	owned	own	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	lot	lot	NN	O	11	dobj
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	slaves	slave	NNS	O	13	nmod
16	just	just	RB	O	17	advmod
17	tells	tell	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	a	a	DT	O	19	det
19	person	person	NN	O	17	dobj
20	that	that	IN	O	26	mark
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	older	older	JJR	O	23	amod
23	generation	generation	NN	O	26	nsubj
24	will	will	MD	O	26	aux
25	not	not	RB	O	26	neg
26	change	change	VB	O	17	ccomp
27	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	not	not	RB	O	0	ROOT
3	being	be	VBG	O	4	cop
4	able	able	JJ	O	2	xcomp
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	change	change	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	her	she	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	viewpoint	viewpoint	NN	O	6	dep
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	way	way	NN	O	6	dobj
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	13	nsubj
13	shows	show	VBZ	O	10	acl:relcl
14	that	that	IN	O	24	mark
15	even	even	RB	O	20	advmod
16	though	though	IN	O	20	mark
17	African	african	JJ	MISC	18	amod
18	Americans	american	NNS	MISC	20	nsubjpass
19	are	be	VBP	O	20	auxpass
20	freed	free	VBN	O	24	advcl
21	racism	racism	NN	O	24	nsubj
22	will	will	MD	O	24	aux
23	still	still	RB	O	24	advmod
24	exist	exist	VB	O	13	ccomp
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	racism	racism	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
4	exist	exist	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	even	even	RB	O	10	advmod
6	legislation	legislation	NN	O	9	compound
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	court	court	NN	O	6	conj
9	cases	case	NNS	O	10	nsubj
10	went	go	VBD	O	4	ccomp
11	through	through	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	American	american	JJ	MISC	14	amod
14	government	government	NN	O	10	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
16	changed	change	VBD	O	10	conj
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	rules	rule	NNS	O	16	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Now	now	RB	DATE	6	advmod
2	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	hubris	hubris	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	show	show	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	through	through	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	way	way	NN	O	6	nmod
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	acts	act	VBZ	O	9	acl:relcl
12	towards	towards	IN	O	13	case
13	people	people	NNS	O	11	nmod
14	on	on	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	bus	bus	NN	O	13	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
18	towards	towards	IN	O	21	case
19	his	he	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
20	own	own	JJ	O	21	amod
21	mother	mother	NN	O	13	conj
22	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	9	nsubj
2	When	when	WRB	O	5	advmod
3	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	introduced	introduce	VBN	O	1	acl:relcl
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	reader	reader	NN	O	5	dobj
8	could	could	MD	O	9	aux
9	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
11	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	does	do	VBZ	O	9	ccomp
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	respect	respect	NN	O	16	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
16	mother	mother	NN	O	12	ccomp
17	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	mother	mother	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
5	say	say	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	things	thing	NNS	O	5	dobj
7	about	about	IN	O	12	mark
8	how	how	WRB	O	12	advmod
9	slavery	slavery	NN	O	12	nsubj
10	was	be	VBD	O	12	cop
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	best	best	JJS	O	5	advcl
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	how	how	WRB	O	18	advmod
15	desegregation	desegregation	NN	O	18	nsubj
16	is	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
17	very	very	RB	O	18	advmod
18	wrong	wrong	JJ	O	12	conj
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	words	word	NNS	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	racism	racism	NN	O	2	nmod
5	would	would	MD	O	6	aux
6	make	make	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	feel	feel	VB	O	6	ccomp
9	very	very	RB	O	10	advmod
10	angry	angry	JJ	O	8	xcomp
11	towards	towards	IN	O	13	case
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	mother	mother	NN	O	10	nmod
14	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
15	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
16	would	would	MD	O	17	aux
17	want	want	VB	O	6	conj
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	teach	teach	VB	O	17	xcomp
20	his	he	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	mother	mother	NN	O	19	dep
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	lesson	lesson	NN	O	19	dobj
24	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	need	need	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	for	for	IN	O	4	case
4	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	prove	prove	VB	O	2	acl
7	to	to	TO	O	11	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
9	mother	mother	NN	O	11	compound
10	wrong	wrong	JJ	O	11	amod
11	shows	show	NNS	O	6	nmod
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	change	change	NN	O	11	dep
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	lives	life	NNS	O	6	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	people	people	NNS	O	16	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
3	an	a	DT	O	4	det
4	example	example	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	11	mark
6	how	how	WRB	O	11	advmod
7	people	people	NNS	O	11	nsubj
8	are	be	VBP	O	11	cop
9	no	no	RB	O	10	neg
10	longer	longer	RB	O	11	advmod
11	afraid	afraid	JJ	O	4	acl
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	show	show	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	that	that	IN	O	21	mark
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	ideals	ideal	NNS	O	21	nsubj
17	of	of	IN	O	19	case
18	past	past	JJ	DATE	19	amod
19	generation	generation	NN	O	16	nmod
20	is	be	VBZ	O	21	cop
21	wrong	wrong	JJ	O	13	ccomp
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	that	that	IN	O	26	mark
24	things	thing	NNS	O	26	nsubj
25	are	be	VBP	O	26	aux
26	changing	change	VBG	O	21	conj
27	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Then	then	RB	O	15	advmod
2	another	another	DT	O	3	det
3	thing	thing	NN	O	15	nsubj
4	that	that	WDT	O	6	dobj
5	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	uses	use	VBZ	O	3	acl:relcl
7	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	hubris	hubris	NN	O	6	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	show	show	VB	O	8	acl
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	reader	reader	NN	O	10	dobj
13	is	be	VBZ	O	15	cop
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	actions	action	NNS	O	0	ROOT
16	of	of	IN	O	19	mark
17	just	just	RB	O	19	advmod
18	being	be	VBG	O	19	cop
19	able	able	JJ	O	15	acl
20	for	for	IN	O	23	case
21	a	a	DT	O	23	det
22	white	white	JJ	O	23	amod
23	man	man	NN	O	19	nmod
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	sit	sit	VB	O	23	acl
26	next	next	JJ	O	25	advmod
27	to	to	TO	O	30	case
28	an	a	DT	O	30	det
29	African	African	NNP	O	30	compound
30	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	25	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	action	action	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	comes	come	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	from	from	IN	O	7	case
5	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	pride	pride	NN	O	3	nmod
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	what	what	WP	O	11	nmod
10	he	he	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	thinks	think	VBZ	O	7	acl:relcl
12	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
13	the	the	DT	DATE	14	det
14	future	future	NN	DATE	11	ccomp
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	action	action	NN	O	14	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	sitting	sit	VBG	O	4	acl
6	next	next	JJ	O	5	advmod
7	to	to	TO	O	10	case
8	an	a	DT	O	10	det
9	African	African	NNP	O	10	compound
10	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
11	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
12	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	14	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	way	way	NN	O	0	ROOT
15	of	of	IN	O	16	mark
16	showing	show	VBG	O	14	acl
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	reader	reader	NN	O	16	dobj
19	that	that	WDT	O	22	dobj
20	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	22	nsubj
21	is	be	VBZ	O	22	aux
22	getting	get	VBG	O	18	acl:relcl
23	better	better	RBR	O	24	advmod
24	slowly	slowly	RB	O	26	advmod
25	,	,	,	O	26	punct
26	but	but	CC	O	22	advmod
27	surely	surely	RB	O	26	advmod
28	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	conclusion	conclusion	NN	O	11	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	11	punct
4	Everything	everything	NN	O	11	nsubj
5	That	that	WDT	O	6	nsubj
6	Rises	rise	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
7	Must	must	MD	O	8	aux
8	Converge	converge	VB	O	6	ccomp
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	story	story	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubjpass
13	was	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	written	write	VBN	O	11	acl:relcl
15	by	by	IN	O	16	case
16	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	14	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	tell	tell	VB	O	14	xcomp
19	people	people	NNS	O	18	iobj
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	changes	change	NNS	O	18	dobj
22	that	that	WDT	O	23	nsubj
23	happened	happen	VBD	O	21	acl:relcl
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	23	nmod
26	after	after	IN	O	30	case
27	the	the	DT	O	30	det
28	Civil	civil	JJ	ORGANIZATION	30	amod
29	Right	Right	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
30	Movement	Movement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	changes	change	NNS	O	4	dep
3	where	where	WRB	O	4	advmod
4	shown	show	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	through	through	IN	O	8	case
6	three	three	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
7	literary	literary	JJ	O	8	amod
8	devices	device	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	that	that	WDT	O	11	dobj
10	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
11	put	put	VBD	O	8	acl:relcl
12	into	into	IN	O	14	case
13	his	he	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	story	story	NN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	3	amod
3	one	one	CD	NUMBER	4	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	was	be	VBD	O	4	dep
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	use	use	NN	O	5	nsubj
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	setting	setting	NN	O	7	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	2	dobj
4	setting	set	VBG	O	3	acl
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	show	show	VB	O	4	ccomp
7	people	people	NNS	O	6	iobj
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	changes	change	NNS	O	6	dobj
10	that	that	WDT	O	12	nsubj
11	were	be	VBD	O	12	aux
12	happening	happen	VBG	O	9	acl:relcl
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	USA	USA	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	6	punct
17	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
18	also	also	RB	O	20	advmod
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	show	show	VB	O	6	conj
21	that	that	IN	O	26	mark
22	racism	racism	NN	O	26	nsubj
23	is	be	VBZ	O	26	cop
24	still	still	RB	O	26	advmod
25	an	a	DT	O	26	det
26	issue	issue	NN	O	20	ccomp
27	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	setting	setting	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	story	story	NN	O	2	nmod
6	also	also	RB	O	7	advmod
7	allows	allow	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	reader	reader	NN	O	7	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	see	see	VB	O	9	acl
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	conflicts	conflict	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	between	between	IN	O	16	case
15	African	african	JJ	MISC	16	amod
16	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	13	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	white	white	JJ	O	19	amod
19	people	people	NNS	O	16	conj
20	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	4	amod
3	literary	literary	JJ	O	4	amod
4	device	device	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	use	use	NN	O	0	ROOT
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	characterization	characterization	NN	O	7	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	characterization	characterization	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	Julian	Julian	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	his	he	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	mother	mother	NN	O	4	conj
8	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	difference	difference	NN	O	8	dobj
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	generations	generation	NNS	O	10	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	final	final	JJ	O	3	amod
3	device	device	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	use	use	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	hubris	hubris	NN	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
10	O'Connor	O'Connor	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
11	uses	use	VBZ	O	6	conj
12	hubris	hubris	NN	O	11	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	show	show	VB	O	11	advcl
15	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
16	people	people	NNS	O	18	nsubj
17	are	be	VBP	O	18	aux
18	staying	stay	VBG	O	14	ccomp
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	same	same	JJ	O	18	dobj
21	,	,	,	O	6	punct
22	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
23	some	some	DT	O	24	det
24	people	people	NNS	O	26	nsubj
25	are	be	VBP	O	26	aux
26	changing	change	VBG	O	6	conj
27	to	to	TO	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	betterment	betterment	NN	O	26	nmod
30	of	of	IN	O	31	case
31	tomorrow	tomorrow	NN	DATE	29	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	6	punct

