1	Is	be	VBZ	O	3	auxpass
2	clearly	clearly	RB	O	3	advmod
3	showed	show	VBN	O	9	dep
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	this	this	DT	O	6	det
6	passage	passage	NN	O	3	nmod
7	I	I	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	have	have	VBP	O	9	aux
9	closed	close	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	read	read	VBN	O	9	dep
11	on	on	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	prisoner	prisoner	NN	O	10	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	Azkaban	Azkaban	NNP	MISC	13	nmod
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	little	little	JJ	O	19	amod
18	``	``	``	O	19	punct
19	respect	respect	NN	O	10	dobj
20	''	''	''	O	19	punct
21	,	,	,	O	19	punct
22	consideration	consideration	NN	O	19	appos
23	that	that	WDT	O	24	det
24	students	student	NNS	O	27	nsubj
25	at	at	IN	O	26	case
26	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	nmod
27	have	have	VBP	O	22	acl:relcl
28	upon	upon	IN	O	30	case
29	their	they	PRP$	O	30	nmod:poss
30	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	27	nmod
31	which	which	WDT	O	36	dobj
32	most	most	RBS	O	33	advmod
33	readers	reader	NNS	O	36	nsubj
34	do	do	VBP	O	36	aux
35	n't	not	RB	O	36	neg
36	notice	notice	VB	O	30	acl:relcl
37	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	students	student	NNS	O	6	nsubj
3	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	4	punct
4	Children	child	NNS	O	2	appos
5	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
6	seem	seem	VBP	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
8	be	be	VB	O	12	cop
9	on	on	IN	O	12	case
10	a	a	DT	O	12	det
11	higher	higher	JJR	O	12	amod
12	position	position	NN	O	6	xcomp
13	than	than	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	17	punct
17	Adults	adult	NNS	O	15	appos
18	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	17	punct
19	with	with	IN	O	21	case
20	more	more	JJR	O	21	amod
21	liberty	liberty	NN	O	15	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	commit	commit	VB	O	12	ccomp
24	errors	error	NNS	O	23	dobj
25	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
26	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
27	be	be	VB	O	28	auxpass
28	forgiven	forgive	VBN	O	23	conj
29	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	9	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	9	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	9	nsubj
5	are	be	VBP	O	9	cop
6	in	in	IN	O	9	case
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	continuing	continue	VBG	O	9	amod
9	observation	observation	NN	O	0	ROOT
10	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	one	one	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
4	thing	thing	NN	O	2	advmod
5	out	out	IN	O	4	case
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	normal	normal	JJ	O	2	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
10	they	they	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
12	out	out	RB	O	2	conj
13	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Potter	Potter	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	2	conj
5	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
6	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	2	conj
7	do	do	VBP	O	9	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	have	have	VB	O	18	dep
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	``	``	``	O	12	punct
12	fear	fear	NN	O	9	dobj
13	''	''	''	O	12	punct
14	most	most	RBS	O	9	advmod
15	student	student	NN	O	18	nsubj
16	have	have	VBP	O	18	aux
17	upon	upon	IN	O	18	case
18	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	0	ROOT
19	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	capitalization	capitalization	NN	O	11	dep
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	words	word	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	-	-	:	O	2	punct
8	''	''	''	O	2	punct
9	YOU	you	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	'RE	be	VBP	O	11	cop
11	PATHETIC	pathetic	JJ	O	0	ROOT
12	!	!	.	O	11	punct
13	''	''	''	O	11	punct

1	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	yelled	yell	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	-	-	:	O	21	punct
2	when	when	WRB	O	3	advmod
3	talking	talk	VBG	O	21	parataxis
4	to	to	TO	O	5	case
5	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	one	one	CD	NUMBER	5	appos
8	of	of	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	most	most	RBS	O	11	advmod
11	feared	fear	VBN	O	7	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	``	``	``	O	16	punct
14	respected	respect	VBN	O	16	amod
15	''	''	''	O	16	punct
16	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	11	conj
17	at	at	IN	O	18	case
18	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	21	punct
20	clearly	clearly	RB	O	21	advmod
21	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
22	how	how	WRB	O	30	advmod
23	confidents	confident	NNS	O	24	compound
24	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	30	nsubj
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	others	other	NNS	O	24	conj
28	have	have	VBP	O	30	aux
29	on	on	IN	O	30	case
30	themselves	themselves	PRP	O	21	ccomp
31	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	How	how	WRB	O	7	advmod
2	because	because	RB	O	1	dep
3	Dumblendore	Dumblendore	NNP	O	7	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
5	on	on	IN	O	7	case
6	their	they	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	side	side	NN	O	15	advcl
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	auxpass
10	fooled	fool	VBN	O	7	conj
11	by	by	IN	O	12	case
12	them	they	PRP	O	10	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	it	it	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	means	mean	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
16	that	that	IN	O	22	mark
17	their	they	PRP$	O	22	nsubjpass
18	wo	will	MD	O	22	aux
19	n't	not	RB	O	22	neg
20	ever	ever	RB	O	22	advmod
21	be	be	VB	O	22	auxpass
22	punished	punish	VBN	O	15	ccomp
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	they	they	PRP	O	26	nsubj
25	can	can	MD	O	26	aux
26	do	do	VB	O	22	conj
27	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	29	dobj
28	they	they	PRP	O	29	nsubj
29	want	want	VBP	O	26	ccomp
30	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Others	other	NNS	O	2	compound
2	students	student	NNS	O	6	nsubj
3	could	could	MD	O	6	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	even	even	RB	O	6	advmod
6	think	think	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	on	on	IN	O	8	mark
8	confronting	confront	VBG	O	6	advcl
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	teacher	teacher	NN	O	8	dobj
11	like	like	IN	O	21	mark
12	those	those	DT	O	21	nsubj
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	12	appos
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	14	conj
17	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
18	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	14	conj
19	,	,	,	O	12	punct
20	are	be	VBP	O	21	aux
21	doing	do	VBG	O	6	advcl
22	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	5	cc
2	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
3	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	5	nsubj
4	could	could	MD	O	5	aux
5	let	let	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	them	they	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	confront	confront	VB	O	5	ccomp
8	them	they	PRP	O	7	dobj
9	either	either	CC	O	12	dep
10	as	as	IN	O	12	mark
11	they	they	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	letting	let	VBG	O	7	dep
13	those	those	DT	O	14	det
14	three	three	CD	NUMBER	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	all	all	DT	O	0	ROOT
4	because	because	IN	O	7	mark
5	they	they	PRP	O	7	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	7	cop
7	privileged	privileged	JJ	O	3	dep
8	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
2	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
3	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
4	anymore	anymore	RB	O	7	advmod
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	only	only	JJ	O	7	amod
7	one	one	NN	NUMBER	0	ROOT
8	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
9	can	can	MD	O	10	aux
10	do	do	VB	O	7	acl:relcl
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	do	do	VB	O	10	conj
13	n't	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	do	do	VB	O	10	ccomp
15	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	17	dobj
16	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	wants	want	VBZ	O	14	ccomp
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	its	its	PRP$	O	17	dep
20	now	now	RB	DATE	19	advmod
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	other	other	JJ	O	23	amod
23	two	two	CD	NUMBER	14	dep
24	,	,	,	O	23	punct
25	his	he	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
26	friends	friend	NNS	O	23	conj
27	,	,	,	O	23	punct
28	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	23	conj
29	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
30	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	23	conj
31	that	that	WDT	O	32	nsubj
32	have	have	VBP	O	10	ccomp
33	also	also	RB	O	32	advmod
34	start	start	VB	O	32	ccomp
35	doing	do	VBG	O	34	xcomp
36	as	as	IN	O	38	mark
37	they	they	PRP	O	38	nsubj
38	want	want	VBP	O	35	advcl
39	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	On	on	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
4	hand	hand	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	9	conj
12	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
13	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	O	9	conj
14	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Firstly	firstly	RB	O	51	advmod
2	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	51	nsubj
3	as	as	IN	O	5	mark
4	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	said	say	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
6	before	before	RB	O	5	advmod
7	,	,	,	O	5	punct
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
9	one	one	CD	NUMBER	5	conj
10	of	of	IN	O	11	case
11	the	the	DT	O	9	nmod
12	most	most	RBS	O	11	advmod
13	``	``	``	O	11	punct
14	respected	respect	VBN	O	11	acl
15	''	''	''	O	14	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
17	feared	fear	VBD	O	5	conj
18	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	17	dobj
19	at	at	IN	O	20	case
20	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	17	nmod
21	but	but	CC	O	5	cc
22	for	for	IN	O	23	case
23	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	32	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	23	punct
25	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	23	conj
26	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
27	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	23	conj
28	,	,	,	O	32	punct
29	he	he	PRP	O	32	nsubj
30	is	be	VBZ	O	32	cop
31	just	just	RB	O	32	advmod
32	one	one	CD	NUMBER	5	conj
33	of	of	IN	O	35	case
34	a	a	DT	O	35	advmod
35	million	million	CD	NUMBER	32	nmod
36	,	,	,	NUMBER	35	punct
37	one	one	CD	NUMBER	35	appos
38	among	among	IN	O	40	case
39	the	the	DT	O	40	det
40	others	other	NNS	O	37	nmod
41	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
42	what	what	WP	O	44	dobj
43	he	he	PRP	O	44	nsubj
44	says	say	VBZ	O	5	conj
45	or	or	CC	O	44	cc
46	order	order	VB	O	44	conj
47	them	they	PRP	O	46	dobj
48	to	to	TO	O	49	mark
49	do	do	VB	O	46	xcomp
50	is	be	VBZ	O	51	cop
51	something	something	NN	O	0	ROOT
52	they	they	PRP	O	55	nsubj
53	do	do	VBP	O	55	aux
54	n't	not	RB	O	55	neg
55	take	take	VB	O	51	acl:relcl
56	on	on	RP	O	55	compound:prt
57	consideration	consideration	NN	O	55	dobj
58	.	.	.	O	51	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	4	neg
2	even	even	RB	O	3	advmod
3	Dumblendore	dumblendore	JJ	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	listens	listen	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	8	case
6	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	words	word	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
3	since	since	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	beginning	beginning	NN	O	6	nmod
6	did	do	VBD	O	1	acl:relcl
7	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
8	trust	trust	NN	O	9	compound
9	Lupin	lupin	NN	O	6	dobj
10	-	-	:	O	1	punct
11	``	``	``	O	14	punct
12	I	I	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	've	have	VBP	O	14	aux
14	told	tell	VBN	O	1	parataxis
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	14	dobj
17	again	again	RB	O	14	advmod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	again	again	RB	O	17	conj
20	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
21	you	you	PRP	O	23	nsubj
22	're	be	VBP	O	23	aux
23	helping	help	VBG	O	14	ccomp
24	your	you	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
25	old	old	JJ	O	26	amod
26	friend	friend	NN	O	23	dobj
27	Black	black	JJ	PERSON	26	amod
28	into	into	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	castle	castle	NN	O	23	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	30	punct
32	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	O	30	appos
33	,	,	,	O	30	punct
34	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
35	here	here	RB	O	38	advmod
36	's	be	VBZ	O	38	cop
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	proof	proof	NN	O	14	conj
39	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	-	-	:	O	38	punct
2	''	''	''	O	38	punct
3	thinking	think	VBG	O	38	dep
4	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
5	he	he	PRP	O	8	nsubj
6	will	will	MD	O	8	aux
7	probably	probably	RB	O	8	advmod
8	listen	listen	VB	O	3	ccomp
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	his	he	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	words	word	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	8	punct
13	but	but	CC	O	8	cc
14	once	once	RB	DATE	17	advmod
15	again	again	RB	O	17	advmod
16	this	this	DT	O	17	det
17	show	show	NN	O	8	conj
18	that	that	IN	O	22	mark
19	Dumblendore	dumblendore	NN	PERSON	22	nsubj
20	does	do	VBZ	O	22	aux
21	n't	not	RB	O	22	neg
22	trust	trust	VB	O	17	ccomp
23	his	he	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	own	own	JJ	O	25	amod
25	staff	staff	NN	O	22	dobj
26	or	or	CC	O	22	cc
27	does	do	VBZ	O	29	aux
28	n't	not	RB	O	29	neg
29	believe	believe	VB	O	22	conj
30	at	at	IN	O	32	case
31	all	all	DT	O	32	det
32	everything	everything	NN	O	29	nmod
33	they	they	PRP	O	34	nsubj
34	have	have	VBP	O	32	acl:relcl
35	to	to	TO	O	36	mark
36	say	say	VB	O	34	xcomp
37	,	,	,	O	38	punct
38	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
39	like	like	IN	O	48	mark
40	if	if	IN	O	48	mark
41	what	what	WP	O	43	dobj
42	they	they	PRP	O	43	nsubj
43	think	think	VBP	O	48	csubj
44	or	or	CC	O	43	cc
45	say	say	VBP	O	43	conj
46	do	do	VBP	O	48	aux
47	not	not	RB	O	48	neg
48	count	count	VB	O	38	advcl
49	at	at	IN	O	50	case
50	all	all	DT	O	48	nmod
51	,	,	,	O	48	punct
52	but	but	CC	O	48	cc
53	if	if	IN	O	59	mark
54	instead	instead	RB	O	56	case
55	of	of	IN	O	54	mwe
56	Snape	Snape	NNP	LOCATION	59	nmod
57	,	,	,	O	59	punct
58	were	be	VBD	O	59	cop
59	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	71	advcl
60	,	,	,	O	59	punct
61	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	59	conj
62	,	,	,	O	59	punct
63	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	59	conj
64	or	or	CC	O	59	cc
65	other	other	JJ	O	66	amod
66	student	student	NN	O	59	conj
67	,	,	,	O	71	punct
68	Dumblendore	Dumblendore	NNP	PERSON	71	nsubj
69	will	will	MD	O	71	aux
70	have	have	VB	O	71	aux
71	listened	listen	VBN	O	48	conj
72	to	to	TO	O	73	case
73	them	they	PRP	O	71	nmod
74	because	because	IN	O	85	mark
75	once	once	RB	DATE	76	advmod
76	again	again	RB	O	79	advmod
77	as	as	IN	O	79	mark
78	I	I	PRP	O	79	nsubj
79	said	say	VBD	O	85	advcl
80	before	before	RB	O	79	advmod
81	,	,	,	O	85	punct
82	students	student	NNS	O	85	nsubj
83	are	be	VBP	O	85	cop
84	the	the	DT	O	85	det
85	privileged	privileged	JJ	O	71	advcl
86	.	.	.	O	38	punct

1	Most	most	JJS	O	2	amod
2	readers	reader	NNS	O	5	nsubj
3	do	do	VBP	O	5	aux
4	n't	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	notice	notice	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	how	how	WRB	O	7	advmod
7	students	student	NNS	O	17	dobj
8	at	at	IN	O	9	case
9	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
10	most	most	JJS	O	17	nsubjpass
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	time	time	NN	O	10	nmod
14	do	do	VBP	O	17	aux
15	n't	not	RB	O	17	neg
16	get	get	VB	O	17	auxpass
17	punished	punish	VBN	O	5	dep
18	when	when	WRB	O	20	advmod
19	they	they	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	do	do	VBP	O	17	advcl
21	something	something	NN	O	20	dobj
22	they	they	PRP	O	26	nsubjpass
23	should	should	MD	O	26	aux
24	clearly	clearly	RB	O	26	advmod
25	be	be	VB	O	26	auxpass
26	punished	punish	VBN	O	21	acl:relcl
27	from	from	IN	O	26	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
29	how	how	WRB	O	31	advmod
30	they	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
31	influence	influence	VBP	O	17	conj
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	headmaster	headmaster	NN	O	31	dobj
34	,	,	,	O	33	punct
35	Dumblendore	dumblendore	NN	LOCATION	33	appos
36	,	,	,	O	33	punct
37	most	most	JJS	O	33	appos
38	of	of	IN	O	40	case
39	the	the	DT	O	40	det
40	time	time	NN	O	37	nmod
41	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	On	on	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
4	hand	hand	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	who	who	WP	O	15	dobj
12	It	it	PRP	O	15	nsubj
13	does	do	VBZ	O	15	aux
14	n't	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	matter	matter	VB	O	9	acl:relcl
16	how	how	WRB	O	19	advmod
17	right	right	JJ	O	16	dep
18	they	they	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	are	be	VBP	O	15	ccomp
20	,	,	,	O	9	punct
21	or	or	CC	O	9	cc
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	proofs	proof	NNS	O	9	conj
24	that	that	IN	O	28	mark
25	they	they	PRP	O	28	nsubj
26	have	have	VBP	O	28	aux
27	about	about	IN	O	28	case
28	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	23	dep
29	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	6	nsubjpass
2	definitely	definitely	RB	O	6	advmod
3	wo	will	MD	O	6	aux
4	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	be	be	VB	O	6	auxpass
6	taken	take	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	as	as	RB	O	8	advmod
8	serious	serious	JJ	O	6	xcomp
9	as	as	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	students	student	NNS	O	6	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
13	that	that	DT	O	15	nsubj
14	is	be	VBZ	O	15	cop
15	something	something	NN	O	6	conj
16	very	very	RB	O	17	advmod
17	unusual	unusual	JJ	O	15	amod
18	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	no	no	DT	O	4	neg
4	school	school	NN	O	2	nsubj
5	like	like	IN	O	6	case
6	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	world	world	NN	O	6	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	school	school	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	which	which	WDT	O	5	det
5	students	student	NNS	O	2	nmod
6	would	would	MD	O	7	aux
7	raise	raise	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	their	they	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	voices	voice	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	7	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	7	punct
14	without	without	IN	O	16	mark
15	being	be	VBG	O	16	auxpass
16	punished	punish	VBN	O	7	advcl
17	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	school	school	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	which	which	WDT	O	5	det
5	students	student	NNS	O	2	nmod
6	would	would	MD	O	7	aux
7	hit	hit	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	this	this	DT	O	11	det
11	case	case	NN	O	16	nmod
12	with	with	IN	O	14	case
13	their	they	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	wands	wand	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	11	punct
16	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	7	dobj
17	without	without	IN	O	19	mark
18	being	be	VBG	O	19	auxpass
19	punished	punish	VBN	O	7	advcl
20	either	either	RB	O	19	advmod
21	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	school	school	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	in	in	IN	O	4	case
4	which	which	WDT	O	8	nmod
5	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	8	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	ones	one	NNS	O	2	ccomp
9	who	who	WP	O	11	nsubj
10	should	should	MD	O	11	aux
11	control	control	VB	O	8	acl:relcl
12	what	what	WP	O	14	dobj
13	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	say	say	VBP	O	11	ccomp
15	or	or	CC	O	14	cc
16	do	do	VBP	O	14	conj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	students	student	NNS	O	14	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	3	aux
3	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	by	by	IN	O	5	mark
5	looking	look	VBG	O	3	advcl
6	at	at	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	passage	passage	NN	O	5	nmod
9	that	that	WDT	O	20	dobj
10	at	at	IN	O	11	case
11	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	nmod
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	students	student	NNS	O	20	nsubj
14	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	15	punct
15	young	young	JJ	O	13	dep
16	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	15	punct
17	are	be	VBP	O	20	cop
18	above	above	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	8	acl:relcl
21	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	22	punct
22	adults	adult	NNS	O	20	appos
23	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	22	punct
24	,	,	,	O	3	punct
25	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
26	that	that	DT	O	28	nsubj
27	is	be	VBZ	O	28	cop
28	something	something	NN	O	3	conj
29	that	that	IN	O	34	mark
30	most	most	JJS	O	31	amod
31	readers	reader	NNS	O	34	nsubj
32	do	do	VBP	O	34	aux
33	n't	not	RB	O	34	neg
34	see	see	VB	O	28	ccomp
35	,	,	,	O	3	punct
36	this	this	DT	O	38	nsubj
37	is	be	VBZ	O	38	cop
38	important	important	JJ	O	3	conj
39	because	because	IN	O	41	mark
40	it	it	PRP	O	41	nsubj
41	explain	explain	VB	O	38	advcl
42	the	the	DT	O	43	det
43	actions	action	NNS	O	41	dobj
44	of	of	IN	O	45	case
45	most	most	JJS	O	43	nmod
46	of	of	IN	O	48	case
47	the	the	DT	O	48	det
48	students	student	NNS	O	45	nmod
49	at	at	IN	O	50	case
50	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	48	nmod
51	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
52	most	most	RBS	O	53	advmod
53	importantly	importantly	RB	O	55	advmod
54	it	it	PRP	O	55	nsubj
55	explains	explain	VBZ	O	3	conj
56	why	why	WRB	O	63	advmod
57	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	63	nsubj
58	,	,	,	O	57	punct
59	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	57	conj
60	and	and	CC	O	57	cc
61	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	57	conj
62	``	``	``	O	63	punct
63	keep	keep	VB	O	55	advcl
64	searching	search	VBG	O	63	xcomp
65	for	for	IN	O	66	case
66	troubles	trouble	NNS	O	64	nmod
67	''	''	''	O	55	punct
68	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	All	all	DT	O	9	nsubj
2	because	because	IN	O	4	mark
3	they	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	know	know	VBP	O	1	dep
5	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
6	they	they	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	wont	wont	VBP	O	4	ccomp
8	get	get	VB	O	7	xcomp
9	punished	punish	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	because	because	IN	O	14	mark
11	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	are	be	VBP	O	14	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	heros	hero	NNS	O	9	advcl
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	ones	one	NNS	O	14	appos
18	who	who	WP	O	19	nsubj
19	run	run	VBP	O	17	acl:relcl
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	school	school	NN	O	19	dobj
22	like	like	IN	O	23	case
23	most	most	JJS	O	21	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	students	student	NNS	O	23	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	something	something	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	WDT	O	8	nsubjpass
6	is	be	VBZ	O	8	auxpass
7	just	just	RB	O	8	advmod
8	started	start	VBN	O	4	acl:relcl
9	at	at	IN	O	10	case
10	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	10	advmod
2	when	when	WRB	O	10	advmod
3	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
6	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
7	Sirious	Sirious	NNP	O	3	conj
8	were	be	VBD	O	10	cop
9	at	at	IN	O	10	case
10	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	advcl
11	,	,	,	O	15	punct
12	it	it	PRP	O	15	nsubj
13	was	be	VBD	O	15	cop
14	like	like	IN	O	15	case
15	this	this	DT	O	0	ROOT
16	too	too	RB	O	15	advmod
17	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	3	case
2	example	example	NN	O	3	compound
3	Lupin	lupin	NN	O	28	nmod
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	Sirious	Sirious	NNP	O	3	conj
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	almost	almost	RB	O	8	advmod
8	killed	kill	VBD	O	28	dep
9	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	8	dobj
10	when	when	WRB	O	14	advmod
11	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	all	all	DT	O	14	advmod
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	cop
14	students	student	NNS	O	8	dep
15	at	at	IN	O	16	case
16	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	8	punct
18	those	those	DT	O	19	det
19	two	two	CD	NUMBER	28	nsubjpass
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	including	include	VBG	O	24	case
22	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	24	nmod:poss
23	's	's	POS	O	22	case
24	dad	dad	NN	O	19	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	19	punct
26	were	be	VBD	O	28	auxpass
27	not	not	RB	O	28	neg
28	punished	punish	VBN	O	0	ROOT
29	for	for	IN	O	32	mark
30	what	what	WP	O	32	dobj
31	they	they	PRP	O	32	nsubj
32	did	do	VBD	O	28	advcl
33	but	but	CC	O	28	cc
34	they	they	PRP	O	36	nsubjpass
35	were	be	VBD	O	36	auxpass
36	forgiven	forgive	VBN	O	28	conj
37	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	28	cc
2	what	what	WP	O	7	dep
3	if	if	IN	O	7	mark
4	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
5	himself	himself	PRP	O	4	nmod:npmod
6	had	have	VBD	O	7	aux
7	killed	kill	VBN	O	28	csubj
8	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	7	dobj
9	because	because	IN	O	13	mark
10	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
11	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
12	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
13	get	get	VB	O	7	advcl
14	out	out	IN	O	17	case
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	way	way	NN	O	13	nmod
18	trying	try	VBG	O	17	acl
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	protect	protect	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	,	,	,	O	13	punct
22	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	PERSON	13	dobj
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	Sirious	Sirious	NNP	O	22	conj
25	,	,	,	O	22	punct
26	or	or	CC	O	22	cc
27	simply	simply	RB	O	22	advmod
28	used	use	VBD	O	0	ROOT
29	his	he	PRP$	O	30	nmod:poss
30	wand	wand	NN	O	28	dobj
31	against	against	IN	O	32	case
32	one	one	CD	NUMBER	28	nmod
33	of	of	IN	O	34	case
34	them	they	PRP	O	32	nmod
35	,	,	,	O	34	punct
36	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	34	appos
37	,	,	,	O	36	punct
38	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	36	conj
39	or	or	CC	O	36	cc
40	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	36	conj
41	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	definitely	definitely	RB	O	4	advmod
3	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	kick	kick	NN	O	4	ccomp
6	out	out	IN	O	5	advmod
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	school	school	NN	O	6	nmod
10	even	even	RB	O	14	advmod
11	though	though	IN	O	14	mark
12	he	he	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	had	have	VBD	O	14	aux
14	told	tell	VBN	O	5	advcl
15	them	they	PRP	O	14	dobj
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	get	get	VB	O	14	xcomp
18	out	out	IN	O	17	compound:prt
19	of	of	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	way	way	NN	O	17	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	6	cc
2	it	it	PRP	O	6	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
4	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	case	case	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
6	,	,	,	O	1	punct
7	were	be	VBD	O	9	cop
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	ones	one	NNS	O	0	ROOT
10	who	who	WP	O	11	nsubj
11	used	use	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	wands	wand	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	against	against	IN	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	teacher	teacher	NN	O	11	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	who	who	WP	O	20	nsubjpass
19	is	be	VBZ	O	20	auxpass
20	supposed	suppose	VBN	O	16	acl:relcl
21	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
22	be	be	VB	O	23	cop
23	superior	superior	JJ	O	20	xcomp
24	than	than	IN	O	25	case
25	them	they	PRP	O	23	nmod
26	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
27	from	from	IN	O	31	mark
28	whom	whom	WP	O	31	dobj
29	they	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
30	should	should	MD	O	31	aux
31	have	have	VB	O	16	conj
32	respect	respect	NN	O	31	dobj
33	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
34	had	have	VBD	O	35	aux
35	listened	listen	VBN	O	11	conj
36	when	when	WRB	O	38	advmod
37	he	he	PRP	O	38	nsubj
38	told	tell	VBD	O	35	advcl
39	them	they	PRP	O	38	dobj
40	to	to	TO	O	41	mark
41	let	let	VB	O	38	xcomp
42	Sirious	Sirious	NNP	PERSON	41	dobj
43	and	and	CC	O	42	cc
44	Lupin	Lupin	NNP	O	42	conj
45	to	to	TO	O	46	case
46	him	he	PRP	O	41	nmod
47	,	,	,	O	38	punct
48	but	but	CC	O	38	cc
49	those	those	DT	O	50	det
50	three	three	CD	NUMBER	51	nsubj
51	knowing	know	VBG	O	38	conj
52	that	that	IN	O	55	mark
53	they	they	PRP	O	55	nsubj
54	could	could	MD	O	55	aux
55	do	do	VB	O	51	ccomp
56	whatever	whatever	WDT	O	58	dobj
57	they	they	PRP	O	58	nsubj
58	want	want	VBP	O	55	ccomp
59	and	and	CC	O	38	cc
60	it	it	PRP	O	61	dep
61	wont	wont	NN	O	38	conj
62	be	be	VB	O	63	cop
63	consequences	consequence	NNS	O	11	dep
64	,	,	,	O	11	punct
65	did	do	VBD	O	67	aux
66	n't	not	RB	O	67	neg
67	care	care	VB	O	11	dep
68	about	about	IN	O	71	mark
69	what	what	WP	O	71	dobj
70	Snape	Snape	NNP	PERSON	71	nsubj
71	had	have	VBD	O	67	advcl
72	to	to	TO	O	73	mark
73	say	say	VB	O	71	xcomp
74	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	n't	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	listened	listen	VBN	O	2	ccomp
5	to	to	TO	O	6	case
6	anybody	anybody	NN	O	4	nmod
7	but	but	CC	O	2	cc
8	themselves	themselves	PRP	O	13	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	that	that	DT	O	8	conj
11	's	be	VBZ	O	13	cop
12	something	something	NN	O	13	nmod:npmod
13	unusual	unusual	JJ	O	2	conj
14	when	when	WRB	O	15	advmod
15	talking	talk	VBG	O	13	advcl
16	about	about	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	relation	relation	NN	O	15	nmod
19	between	between	IN	O	20	case
20	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	students	student	NNS	O	20	conj
23	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	seem	seem	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	2	xcomp
4	as	as	IN	O	7	case
5	our	we	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
6	``	``	``	O	7	punct
7	parents	parent	NNS	O	2	nmod
8	''	''	''	O	7	punct
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	adults	adult	NNS	O	2	xcomp
11	from	from	IN	O	15	mark
12	who	who	WP	O	15	dobj
13	we	we	PRP	O	15	nsubj
14	should	should	MD	O	15	aux
15	take	take	VB	O	10	acl
16	advices	advice	NNS	O	15	dobj
17	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
18	listen	listen	VB	O	15	conj
19	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
20	what	what	WP	O	22	dobj
21	they	they	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	have	have	VBP	O	18	advcl
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	say	say	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	People	people	NNS	O	18	nsubj
2	from	from	IN	O	5	mark
3	whom	whom	WP	O	5	dobj
4	we	we	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	learn	learn	VBP	O	1	acl
6	about	about	IN	O	7	case
7	life	life	NN	O	5	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	case	case	NN	O	7	conj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	wizards	wizard	NNS	O	14	compound
14	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	11	nmod
15	are	be	VBP	O	18	cop
16	their	they	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
17	``	``	``	O	18	punct
18	masters	master	NNS	O	0	ROOT
19	''	''	''	O	18	punct
20	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	21	cc
2	especially	especially	RB	O	5	advmod
3	for	for	IN	O	5	case
4	those	those	DT	O	5	det
5	three	three	CD	NUMBER	21	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	21	punct
7	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	21	nsubj
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	7	conj
10	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
11	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	7	conj
12	,	,	,	O	7	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	only	only	JJ	O	15	amod
15	teacher	teacher	NN	O	7	appos
16	they	they	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	respect	respect	VBP	O	15	acl:relcl
18	so	so	RB	O	19	advmod
19	far	far	RB	O	17	advmod
20	is	be	VBZ	O	21	cop
21	Dumblendore	Dumblendore	NNP	O	0	ROOT
22	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	3	mark
2	we	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	read	read	VBP	O	14	advcl
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	this	this	DT	O	6	det
6	passage	passage	NN	O	3	nmod
7	more	more	RBR	O	9	advmod
8	than	than	IN	O	9	case
9	once	once	RB	DATE	3	advmod
10	,	,	,	O	14	punct
11	we	we	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	can	can	MD	O	14	aux
13	also	also	RB	O	14	advmod
14	notice	notice	VB	O	0	ROOT
15	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	relation	relation	NN	O	25	nsubj
18	between	between	IN	O	19	case
19	young	young	JJ	O	17	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	adult	adult	JJ	O	19	conj
22	is	be	VBZ	O	25	cop
23	practically	practically	RB	O	25	advmod
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	same	same	JJ	O	14	ccomp
26	as	as	IN	O	27	case
27	students	student	NNS	O	25	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
29	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	27	conj
30	in	in	IN	O	31	case
31	which	which	WDT	O	38	nmod
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	34	amod
34	ones	one	NNS	O	38	nsubj
35	are	be	VBP	O	38	cop
36	above	above	IN	O	38	case
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	other	other	JJ	O	25	acl:relcl
39	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	passage	passage	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	clearly	clearly	RB	O	3	advmod
5	how	how	WRB	O	6	advmod
6	privileged	privileged	JJ	O	9	dep
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	students	student	NNS	O	9	nsubj
9	are	be	VBP	O	3	ccomp
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	on	on	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	other	other	JJ	O	14	amod
14	hand	hand	NN	O	9	conj
15	how	how	WRB	O	20	advmod
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	20	nsubj
18	are	be	VBP	O	20	cop
19	below	below	IN	O	20	case
20	them	they	PRP	O	14	ccomp
21	.	.	.	O	3	punct

