1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	Scottish	scottish	JJ	MISC	3	amod
3	teacher	teacher	NN	O	30	nsubj
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	historian	historian	NN	O	3	conj
6	,	,	,	O	3	punct
7	Thomas	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Carlyle	Carlyle	NNP	PERSON	3	appos
9	,	,	,	O	3	punct
10	once	once	RB	DATE	11	advmod
11	said	say	VBD	O	3	dep
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	``	``	``	O	11	punct
14	A	a	DT	O	15	det
15	man	man	NN	O	16	nsubj
16	willing	willing	JJ	O	11	xcomp
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	work	work	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	,	,	,	O	16	punct
20	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
21	unable	unable	JJ	O	16	conj
22	to	to	TO	O	23	mark
23	find	find	VB	O	21	xcomp
24	work	work	NN	O	23	dobj
25	,	,	,	O	3	punct
26	is	be	VBZ	O	30	cop
27	perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	30	advmod
28	the	the	DT	O	30	det
29	saddest	saddest	JJS	O	30	amod
30	sight	sight	NN	O	0	ROOT
31	that	that	WDT	O	35	dobj
32	fortune	fortune	NN	O	34	nmod:poss
33	's	's	POS	O	32	case
34	inequality	inequality	NN	O	35	nsubj
35	exhibits	exhibit	VBZ	O	30	acl:relcl
36	under	under	IN	O	38	case
37	this	this	DT	DATE	38	det
38	sun	sun	NN	DATE	35	nmod
39	''	''	''	O	35	punct
40	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	41	punct
41	Carlyle	Carlyle	NNP	PERSON	35	dep
42	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	41	punct
43	.	.	.	O	30	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	5	mark
2	Thomas	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Carlyle	Carlyle	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	aux
5	referring	refer	VBG	O	31	advcl
6	to	to	TO	O	8	case
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	need	need	NN	O	5	nmod
9	for	for	IN	O	11	case
10	social	social	JJ	O	11	amod
11	reform	reform	NN	O	8	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	15	compound
15	Kingdom	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	11	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	31	punct
17	in	in	IN	O	19	case
18	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	Potter	Potter	NNP	PERSON	31	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	Goblet	Goblet	NNP	MISC	19	conj
23	of	of	IN	MISC	24	case
24	Fire	Fire	NNP	MISC	22	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	31	punct
26	house	house	NN	O	27	compound
27	elves	elf	NNS	O	31	nsubj
28	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	27	dep
29	and	and	CC	O	28	cc
30	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	28	conj
31	demonstrate	demonstrate	VBP	O	0	ROOT
32	this	this	DT	O	33	det
33	quote	quote	NN	O	31	dobj
34	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
35	be	be	VB	O	37	cop
36	very	very	RB	O	37	advmod
37	true	true	JJ	O	31	xcomp
38	.	.	.	O	31	punct

1	Reactions	reaction	NNS	O	11	nsubj
2	to	to	TO	O	3	case
3	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	1	nmod
4	are	be	VBP	O	11	cop
5	as	as	IN	O	11	case
6	varied	vary	VBN	O	11	amod
7	as	as	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	people	people	NNS	O	10	compound
10	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	6	nmod
11	effects	effect	NNS	O	0	ROOT
12	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	2	mark
2	looking	look	VBG	O	12	advcl
3	at	at	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	history	history	NN	O	2	nmod
6	of	of	IN	O	7	case
7	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	5	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	12	punct
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	reader	reader	NN	O	12	nsubj
11	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
12	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
13	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
14	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	18	nsubj
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	house	house	NN	O	17	compound
17	elf	elf	NN	O	14	dep
18	shows	show	VBZ	O	12	ccomp
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	psychological	psychological	JJ	O	21	amod
21	effects	effect	NNS	O	18	dobj
22	that	that	WDT	O	24	nsubj
23	can	can	MD	O	24	aux
24	happen	happen	VB	O	21	acl:relcl
25	after	after	IN	O	29	mark
26	someone	someone	NN	O	29	nsubjpass
27	has	have	VBZ	O	29	aux
28	been	be	VBN	O	29	auxpass
29	fired	fire	VBN	O	24	advcl
30	;	;	:	O	12	punct
31	this	this	DT	O	33	nsubj
32	is	be	VBZ	O	33	cop
33	important	important	JJ	O	12	parataxis
34	because	because	IN	O	38	mark
35	J.K.	J.K.	NNP	PERSON	36	compound
36	Rowling	Rowling	NNP	PERSON	38	nsubj
37	is	be	VBZ	O	38	cop
38	able	able	JJ	O	33	advcl
39	to	to	TO	O	40	mark
40	show	show	VB	O	38	xcomp
41	how	how	WRB	O	43	advmod
42	humans	human	NNS	O	43	nsubj
43	react	react	VBP	O	40	ccomp
44	to	to	TO	O	47	case
45	high	high	JJ	O	47	amod
46	stress	stress	NN	O	47	compound
47	situations	situation	NNS	O	43	nmod
48	through	through	IN	O	50	case
49	a	a	DT	O	50	det
50	character	character	NN	O	43	nmod
51	that	that	WDT	O	53	nsubjpass
52	was	be	VBD	O	53	auxpass
53	created	create	VBN	O	50	acl:relcl
54	not	not	RB	O	56	neg
55	to	to	TO	O	56	mark
56	endure	endure	VB	O	53	xcomp
57	stressful	stressful	JJ	O	58	amod
58	situations	situation	NNS	O	56	dobj
59	well	well	RB	O	56	advmod
60	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Great	Great	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Depression	Depression	NNP	O	4	nsubj
4	happened	happen	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	over	over	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	period	period	NN	O	4	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	ten	ten	CD	DURATION	10	nummod
10	years	year	NNS	DURATION	7	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	14	compound
14	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	10	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
16	some	some	DT	O	17	det
17	places	place	NNS	O	10	conj
18	in	in	IN	O	19	case
19	Europe	Europe	NNP	LOCATION	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Many	many	JJ	O	2	amod
2	things	thing	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	led	lead	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	6	case
5	this	this	DT	O	6	det
6	period	period	NN	O	3	nmod
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	time	time	NN	O	6	nmod
9	the	the	DT	O	12	det
10	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
11	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	12	compound
12	History	history	NN	O	3	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	19	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	conclusion	conclusion	NN	O	19	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	7	case
5	World	World	NNP	MISC	7	compound
6	War	War	NNP	MISC	7	compound
7	I	I	NNP	O	3	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	hands-off	hands-off	JJ	O	11	amod
11	government	government	NN	O	7	appos
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	people	people	NNS	O	11	appos
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
18	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	14	nmod
19	discovering	discover	VBG	O	30	advcl
20	credit	credit	NN	O	19	dobj
21	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
22	doubting	doubt	VBG	O	19	conj
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	stock	stock	NN	O	25	compound
25	market	market	NN	O	22	dobj
26	,	,	,	O	30	punct
27	no	no	DT	O	28	neg
28	one	one	CD	NUMBER	30	nsubj
29	really	really	RB	O	30	advmod
30	understood	understand	VBN	O	0	ROOT
31	how	how	WRB	O	32	advmod
32	bad	bad	JJ	O	35	dep
33	things	thing	NNS	O	35	nsubj
34	could	could	MD	O	35	aux
35	get	get	VB	O	30	ccomp
36	.	.	.	O	30	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	collapse	collapse	NN	O	11	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Stock	Stock	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Market	Market	NNP	O	2	nmod
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	October	October	NNP	DATE	6	nmod
9	of	of	IN	DATE	10	case
10	1929	1929	CD	DATE	8	nmod
11	set	set	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	14	compound
14	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	15	nsubj
15	marked	mark	VBD	O	11	ccomp
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	beginning	beginning	NN	O	15	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	21	case
19	The	the	DT	O	21	det
20	Great	Great	NNP	O	21	compound
21	Depression	Depression	NNP	O	17	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Banks	bank	NNS	O	10	nsubj
2	failing	fail	VBG	O	1	acl
3	,	,	,	O	10	punct
4	along	along	IN	O	10	advmod
5	with	with	IN	O	8	case
6	many	many	JJ	O	8	amod
7	small	small	JJ	O	8	amod
8	businesses	business	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	10	punct
10	left	leave	VBD	O	0	ROOT
11	many	many	JJ	O	12	amod
12	people	people	NNS	O	13	nsubj
13	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	10	xcomp
14	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Most	most	JJS	O	2	nsubj
2	struggled	struggle	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	with	with	IN	O	4	mark
4	finding	find	VBG	O	2	advcl
5	new	new	JJ	O	6	amod
6	work	work	NN	O	4	dobj
7	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
8	began	begin	VBD	O	2	conj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	rely	rely	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	on	on	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	government	government	NN	O	10	nmod
14	once	once	RB	DATE	18	advmod
15	Franklin	Franklin	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
16	D.	D.	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Roosevelt	Roosevelt	NNP	PERSON	18	nsubj
18	came	come	VBD	O	10	ccomp
19	into	into	IN	O	20	case
20	office	office	NN	O	18	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Roosevelt	Roosevelt	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	5	cop
4	completely	completely	RB	O	5	advmod
5	opposite	opposite	JJ	O	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	10	case
7	President	President	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Hoover	Hoover	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	method	method	NN	O	5	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	public	public	JJ	O	13	amod
13	welfare	welfare	NN	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Hoover	Hoover	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	hands-off	hands-off	JJ	O	4	amod
4	approach	approach	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	left	leave	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	most	most	RBS	O	5	advmod
7	distrusting	distrust	VBG	O	5	xcomp
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	government	government	NN	O	7	dobj
10	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
11	Roosevelt	Roosevelt	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod:poss
12	's	's	POS	O	11	case
13	involvement	involvement	NN	O	25	nsubj
14	in	in	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	personal	personal	JJ	O	17	amod
17	welfare	welfare	NN	O	13	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	people	people	NNS	O	17	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	United	United	NNP	LOCATION	24	compound
24	States	States	NNPS	LOCATION	20	nmod
25	made	make	VBD	O	5	conj
26	him	he	PRP	O	25	iobj
27	an	a	DT	O	29	det
28	immediate	immediate	JJ	O	29	amod
29	favorite	favorite	JJ	O	25	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	set	set	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	up	up	RP	O	2	compound:prt
4	The	the	DT	O	6	det
5	New	New	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Deal	Deal	NNP	O	2	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	which	which	WDT	O	9	nsubj
9	helped	help	VBD	O	6	acl:relcl
10	those	those	DT	O	9	dobj
11	struggling	struggle	VBG	O	10	acl
12	by	by	IN	O	13	mark
13	providing	provide	VBG	O	11	advcl
14	them	they	PRP	O	13	dobj
15	with	with	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	help	help	NN	O	13	nmod
18	they	they	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	needed	need	VBD	O	17	acl:relcl
20	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Like	like	IN	O	3	mark
2	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	accepting	accept	VBG	O	14	advcl
4	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	3	dobj
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	4	conj
7	into	into	IN	O	10	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	work	work	NN	O	10	compound
10	force	force	NN	O	3	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	14	punct
12	President	President	NNP	O	13	compound
13	Roosevelt	Roosevelt	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
14	created	create	VBD	O	0	ROOT
15	jobs	job	NNS	O	14	dobj
16	by	by	IN	O	17	mark
17	employing	employ	VBG	O	14	advcl
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	17	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	5	case
2	the	the	DT	O	5	det
3	more	more	RBR	O	5	advmod
4	recent	recent	JJ	O	5	amod
5	recession	recession	NN	O	13	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	13	punct
7	reactions	reaction	NNS	O	13	nsubjpass
8	to	to	TO	O	9	case
9	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	7	nmod
10	have	have	VBP	O	13	aux
11	been	be	VBN	O	13	auxpass
12	extremely	extremely	RB	O	13	advmod
13	varied	vary	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	real	real	JJ	O	4	amod
3	estate	estate	NN	O	4	compound
4	industry	industry	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	crashed	crash	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	almost	almost	RB	O	8	advmod
7	five	five	CD	DATE	8	nummod
8	years	year	NNS	DATE	9	nmod:npmod
9	ago	ago	RB	DATE	5	advmod
10	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
11	has	have	VBZ	O	5	conj
12	yet	yet	RB	O	11	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
14	be	be	VB	O	16	auxpass
15	fully	fully	RB	O	16	advmod
16	fixed	fix	VBN	O	12	dep
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Agents	agent	NNS	O	11	nsubj
2	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
3	were	be	VBD	O	5	aux
4	once	once	RB	DATE	5	advmod
5	making	make	VBG	O	1	acl:relcl
6	five	five	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
7	figure	figure	NN	O	8	compound
8	deals	deal	NNS	O	5	dobj
9	are	be	VBP	O	11	aux
10	now	now	RB	DATE	11	advmod
11	sitting	sit	VBG	O	0	ROOT
12	at	at	IN	O	13	case
13	home	home	NN	O	11	nmod
14	wondering	wonder	VBG	O	11	advcl
15	when	when	WRB	O	21	advmod
16	the	the	DT	O	19	det
17	real	real	JJ	O	19	amod
18	estate	estate	NN	O	19	compound
19	business	business	NN	O	21	nsubj
20	will	will	MD	O	21	aux
21	pick	pick	VB	O	14	ccomp
22	back	back	RB	O	23	advmod
23	up	up	RB	O	21	advmod
24	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	College	College	NNP	O	2	compound
2	students	student	NNS	O	8	nsubj
3	all	all	DT	O	8	advmod
4	over	over	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	country	country	NN	O	3	nmod
7	were	be	VBD	O	8	aux
8	changing	change	VBG	O	0	ROOT
9	majors	major	NNS	O	8	dobj
10	from	from	IN	O	11	case
11	things	thing	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	that	that	WDT	O	13	nsubj
13	used	use	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
14	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
15	be	be	VB	O	16	cop
16	lucrative	lucrative	JJ	O	13	xcomp
17	to	to	TO	O	18	case
18	things	thing	NNS	O	16	nmod
19	that	that	WDT	O	23	nsubj
20	were	be	VBD	O	23	cop
21	now	now	RB	DATE	23	advmod
22	safe	safe	JJ	O	23	amod
23	bets	bet	NNS	O	18	acl:relcl
24	,	,	,	O	13	punct
25	like	like	IN	O	29	case
26	business	business	NN	O	29	compound
27	or	or	CC	O	26	cc
28	medical	medical	JJ	O	26	conj
29	school	school	NN	O	13	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	questions	question	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	from	from	IN	O	8	case
5	what	what	WP	O	8	dep
6	can	can	MD	O	8	aux
7	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	make	make	VB	O	3	advcl
9	money	money	NN	O	8	dobj
10	in	in	IN	O	14	case
11	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
12	what	what	WP	O	14	nsubj
13	will	will	MD	O	14	aux
14	give	give	VB	O	9	acl
15	me	I	PRP	O	14	iobj
16	a	a	DT	O	18	det
17	steady	steady	JJ	O	18	amod
18	job	job	NN	O	14	dobj
19	?	?	.	O	8	punct

1	Budget	Budget	NNP	O	2	compound
2	cuts	cut	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	had	have	VBD	O	4	aux
4	forced	force	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	many	many	JJ	O	6	amod
6	people	people	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	out	out	IN	O	4	advmod
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	job	job	NN	O	7	nmod
11	as	as	RB	O	7	advmod
12	well	well	RB	O	11	mwe
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	How	how	WRB	O	2	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	5	amod
5	deal	deal	NN	O	2	dobj
6	with	with	IN	O	9	case
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	sudden	sudden	JJ	O	9	amod
9	change	change	NN	O	2	nmod
10	?	?	.	O	2	punct

1	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
2	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
3	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	1	conj
4	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
5	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
6	typical	typical	JJ	O	8	amod
7	house	house	NN	O	8	compound
8	elves	elf	NNS	O	0	ROOT
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	but	but	CC	O	8	cc
11	for	for	IN	O	13	case
12	different	different	JJ	O	13	amod
13	reasons	reason	NNS	O	8	conj
14	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
3	almost	almost	RB	O	6	advmod
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	anti-house	anti-house	JJ	O	6	amod
6	elf	elf	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	3	mark
2	being	be	VBG	O	3	auxpass
3	freed	free	VBN	O	6	advcl
4	,	,	,	O	6	punct
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	set	set	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	out	out	RP	O	6	compound:prt
8	for	for	IN	O	9	case
9	work	work	NN	O	6	nmod
10	with	with	IN	O	11	case
11	intention	intention	NN	O	6	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	14	mark
13	being	be	VBG	O	14	auxpass
14	paid	pay	VBN	O	11	acl
15	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
16	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	11	conj
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	5	cop
3	after	after	IN	O	5	case
4	two	two	CD	DURATION	5	nummod
5	years	year	NNS	DURATION	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	7	mark
7	searching	search	VBG	O	5	acl
8	he	he	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	found	find	VBD	O	7	ccomp
10	work	work	NN	O	9	dobj
11	at	at	IN	O	12	case
12	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNPS	LOCATION	9	nmod
13	with	with	IN	O	15	case
14	Professor	Professor	NNP	O	15	compound
15	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	9	nmod
16	as	as	IN	O	19	case
17	his	he	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
18	new	new	JJ	O	19	amod
19	master	master	NN	O	15	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubjpass
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	on	on	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	other	other	JJ	O	6	amod
6	hand	hand	NN	O	1	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	1	punct
8	was	be	VBD	O	9	auxpass
9	set	set	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	free	free	JJ	O	9	advmod
11	after	after	IN	O	13	case
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	misunderstanding	misunderstanding	NN	O	9	nmod
14	between	between	IN	O	16	case
15	government	government	NN	O	16	compound
16	officials	official	NNS	O	13	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	her	she	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	master	master	NN	O	16	conj
20	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	did	do	VBD	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	react	react	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	as	as	RB	O	8	cc
6	well	well	RB	O	5	mwe
7	as	as	IN	O	5	mwe
8	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	4	dobj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	her	she	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	new	new	JJ	O	8	conj
12	found	find	VBN	O	11	acl
13	freedom	freedom	NN	O	12	dobj
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	became	become	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	depressed	depressed	JJ	O	2	xcomp
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	even	even	RB	O	7	advmod
6	an	a	DT	O	7	det
7	alcoholic	alcoholic	JJ	O	3	conj
8	,	,	,	O	2	punct
9	going	go	VBG	O	2	advcl
10	through	through	IN	O	12	case
11	six	six	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	bottles	bottle	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	butter	butter	NN	O	15	compound
15	beer	beer	NN	O	12	nmod
16	a	a	DT	DURATION	17	det
17	day	day	NN	DURATION	15	dep
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
3	house	house	NN	O	4	compound
4	elves	elf	NNS	O	7	nsubj
5	at	at	IN	O	6	case
6	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
7	treat	treat	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	her	she	PRP$	O	7	dobj
9	as	as	IN	O	10	case
10	something	something	NN	O	7	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
12	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
13	shameful	shameful	JJ	O	10	acl
14	of	of	IN	O	17	mark
15	because	because	IN	O	17	mark
16	she	she	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	is	be	VBZ	O	13	advcl
18	always	always	RB	O	27	advmod
19	drunk	drunk	JJ	O	27	dep
20	,	,	,	O	27	punct
21	crying	cry	VBG	O	27	conj
22	,	,	,	O	27	punct
23	a	a	DT	O	25	det
24	sloppy	sloppy	JJ	O	25	amod
25	mess	mess	NN	O	27	dep
26	,	,	,	O	27	punct
27	or	or	CC	O	17	advmod
28	passed	pass	VBN	O	27	conj
29	out	out	RP	O	28	compound:prt
30	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	4	det
2	two	two	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
3	house	house	NN	O	4	compound
4	elves	elf	NNS	O	5	nsubj
5	show	show	VBP	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	9	det
7	two	two	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
8	opposite	opposite	JJ	O	9	amod
9	sides	side	NNS	O	5	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	spectrum	spectrum	NN	O	9	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	12	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	1	appos
4	thriving	thrive	VBG	O	3	acl
5	go	go	VB	O	4	ccomp
6	getter	getter	RB	O	5	advmod
7	,	,	,	O	3	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
9	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	3	conj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	depressed	depressed	JJ	O	13	amod
13	mess	mess	NN	O	9	appos
14	who	who	WP	O	17	nsubj
15	can	can	MD	O	17	aux
16	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
17	figure	figure	VB	O	13	acl:relcl
18	out	out	RP	O	17	compound:prt
19	what	what	WP	O	21	nsubj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	do	do	VB	O	17	ccomp
22	without	without	IN	O	24	case
23	a	a	DT	O	24	det
24	job	job	NN	O	21	nmod
25	or	or	CC	O	24	cc
26	family	family	NN	O	24	conj
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	take	take	VB	O	21	xcomp
29	care	care	NN	O	28	dobj
30	of	of	IN	O	28	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	relationship	relationship	NN	O	8	nsubj
3	between	between	IN	O	4	case
4	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	4	conj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
8	one	one	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	learn	learn	VB	O	8	advcl
11	from	from	IN	O	10	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	while	while	IN	O	4	mark
4	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	6	dep
5	,	,	,	O	6	punct
6	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	sure	sure	JJ	O	16	amod
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	look	look	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	out	out	RP	O	9	compound:prt
11	for	for	IN	O	15	case
12	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
13	newly	newly	RB	O	14	advmod
14	liberated	liberate	VBN	O	15	amod
15	friend	friend	NN	O	9	nmod
16	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	6	xcomp
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	2	mark
2	finding	find	VBG	O	8	advcl
3	them	they	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	both	both	DT	O	5	det
5	jobs	job	NNS	O	2	xcomp
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	becomes	become	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	protector	protector	NN	O	8	xcomp
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	8	punct
14	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
15	remains	remain	VBZ	O	8	conj
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	protector	protector	NN	O	15	xcomp
18	during	during	IN	O	20	case
19	their	they	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	stay	stay	NN	O	15	nmod
21	at	at	IN	O	22	case
22	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	LOCATION	20	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	6	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
4	house-elves	house-elf	NNS	O	6	nsubj
5	are	be	VBP	O	6	cop
6	ashamed	ashamed	JJ	O	13	advcl
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	behavior	behavior	NN	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	13	punct
12	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	13	nsubj
13	takes	take	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	looking	look	VBG	O	13	advcl
16	out	out	RP	O	15	compound:prt
17	for	for	IN	O	18	case
18	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	15	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	22	case
20	her	she	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
21	drunken	drunken	JJ	O	22	amod
22	stupors	stupor	NNS	O	18	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
24	periods	period	NNS	O	18	conj
25	of	of	IN	O	26	case
26	depression	depression	NN	O	24	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Depression	depression	NN	O	11	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	confusion	confusion	NN	O	1	conj
4	,	,	,	O	1	punct
5	anxiety	anxiety	NN	O	1	conj
6	,	,	,	O	1	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
8	alcoholism	alcoholism	NN	O	1	conj
9	are	be	VBP	O	11	cop
10	all	all	DT	O	11	det
11	things	thing	NNS	O	0	ROOT
12	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
13	can	can	MD	O	14	aux
14	happen	happen	VB	O	11	acl:relcl
15	to	to	TO	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	recently	recently	RB	DATE	18	advmod
18	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	14	nmod
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
20	Linn	Linn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	appos
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
22	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	demonstrates	demonstrate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	all	all	DT	O	2	dobj
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	these	these	DT	O	3	nmod
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	her	she	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	conversations	conversation	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	with	with	IN	O	10	case
10	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	friends	friend	NNS	O	10	conj
14	while	while	IN	O	18	mark
15	in	in	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	kitchens	kitchen	NNS	O	8	dep
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	n't	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	moved	move	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	for	for	IN	O	6	case
6	days	day	NNS	DURATION	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	which	which	WDT	O	10	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
10	prevalent	prevalent	JJ	O	6	acl:relcl
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	her	she	PRP$	O	10	nmod
13	stained	stain	VBN	O	12	acl
14	dress	dress	NN	O	13	dobj
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	somber	somber	JJ	O	17	amod
17	attitude	attitude	NN	O	14	conj
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	3	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	auxpass
3	confused	confuse	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	as	as	IN	O	9	case
5	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
6	who	who	WP	O	9	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
8	her	she	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	master	master	NN	O	3	dep
10	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	2	mark
2	refusing	refuse	VBG	O	22	advcl
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	reveal	reveal	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	any	any	DT	O	4	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	10	case
7	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Crouch	Crouch	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	secrets	secret	NNS	O	5	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
12	denying	deny	VBG	O	2	conj
13	pay	pay	NN	O	12	dobj
14	from	from	IN	O	17	case
15	her	she	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
16	new	new	JJ	O	17	amod
17	master	master	NN	O	12	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	22	punct
19	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
20	,	,	,	O	21	punct
21	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
22	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
23	her	she	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
24	confusion	confusion	NN	O	22	dobj
25	in	in	IN	O	29	mark
26	who	who	WP	O	29	dobj
27	she	she	PRP	O	29	nsubj
28	can	can	MD	O	29	aux
29	trust	trust	VB	O	22	advcl
30	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
31	who	who	WP	O	34	dobj
32	she	she	PRP	O	34	nsubj
33	should	should	MD	O	34	aux
34	obey	obey	VB	O	29	conj
35	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	almost	almost	RB	O	3	advmod
3	has	have	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	an	a	DT	O	6	det
5	anxiety	anxiety	NN	O	6	compound
6	attack	attack	NN	O	3	dobj
7	when	when	WRB	O	9	advmod
8	she	she	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	finds	find	VBZ	O	6	acl:relcl
10	out	out	RP	O	9	compound:prt
11	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
12	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	13	compound
13	Crouch	Crouch	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
14	has	have	VBZ	O	17	aux
15	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
16	been	be	VBN	O	17	aux
17	going	go	VBG	O	9	ccomp
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	work	work	VB	O	17	xcomp
20	because	because	IN	O	23	mark
21	he	he	PRP	O	23	nsubj
22	is	be	VBZ	O	23	cop
23	sick	sick	JJ	O	19	advcl
24	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	jumps	jump	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	conclusion	conclusion	NN	O	2	nmod
6	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
7	her	she	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
8	old	old	JJ	O	9	amod
9	master	master	NN	O	12	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
11	at	at	IN	O	12	case
12	home	home	NN	O	2	ccomp
13	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
14	has	have	VBZ	O	2	conj
15	no	no	DT	O	16	neg
16	one	one	NN	NUMBER	14	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	take	take	VB	O	16	acl
19	care	care	NN	O	18	dobj
20	of	of	IN	O	21	case
21	him	he	PRP	O	19	nmod
22	;	;	:	O	2	punct
23	automatically	automatically	RB	O	41	advmod
24	assuming	assume	VBG	O	41	csubj
25	no	no	DT	O	26	neg
26	one	one	NN	NUMBER	24	dobj
27	else	else	RB	O	26	advmod
28	is	be	VBZ	O	29	cop
29	capable	capable	JJ	O	26	acl:relcl
30	of	of	IN	O	31	mark
31	taking	take	VBG	O	29	advcl
32	care	care	NN	O	31	dobj
33	of	of	IN	O	36	case
34	her	she	PRP$	O	36	nmod:poss
35	old	old	JJ	O	36	amod
36	master	master	NN	O	32	nmod
37	as	as	RB	O	26	cc
38	well	well	RB	O	37	mwe
39	as	as	IN	O	37	mwe
40	she	she	PRP	O	26	conj
41	can	can	MD	O	2	parataxis
42	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Alcoholism	alcoholism	NN	O	3	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	auxpass
3	reveled	revel	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	through	through	IN	O	6	case
5	her	she	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	drunken	drunken	JJ	O	3	nmod
7	weeping	weep	VBG	O	3	xcomp
8	when	when	WRB	O	14	advmod
9	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	9	conj
12	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
13	Hermione	Hermione	NNP	PERSON	9	conj
14	come	come	VBP	O	7	advcl
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	visit	visit	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	a	a	DT	DURATION	19	det
18	second	second	JJ	DURATION	19	amod
19	time	time	NN	O	16	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Her	she	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
2	newly	newly	RB	O	3	advmod
3	found	find	VBN	O	4	amod
4	attachment	attachment	NN	O	9	nsubj
5	to	to	TO	O	7	case
6	alcoholic	alcoholic	JJ	O	7	amod
7	beverages	beverage	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
9	common	common	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	among	among	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	recently	recently	RB	DATE	13	advmod
13	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	9	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	a	a	DT	O	3	det
3	study	study	NN	O	16	nmod
4	published	publish	VBN	O	3	acl
5	in	in	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	American	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	Journal	Journal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
9	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	11	case
10	Public	Public	NNP	ORGANIZATION	11	compound
11	Health	Health	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	16	punct
13	recently	recently	RB	DATE	14	advmod
14	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	16	nsubjpass
15	were	be	VBD	O	16	auxpass
16	recorded	record	VBN	O	0	ROOT
17	spending	spend	VBG	O	16	xcomp
18	more	more	RBR	O	19	nummod
19	days	day	NNS	DURATION	22	nsubj
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	bed	bed	NN	O	19	nmod
22	sick	sick	JJ	O	17	xcomp
23	than	than	IN	O	24	case
24	those	those	DT	O	22	nmod
25	who	who	WP	O	26	nsubj
26	had	have	VBD	O	24	acl:relcl
27	steady	steady	JJ	O	28	amod
28	jobs	job	NNS	O	26	dobj
29	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	30	punct
30	Linn	Linn	NNP	ORGANIZATION	28	appos
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	30	punct
32	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	knows	know	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	there	there	EX	O	5	expl
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
5	work	work	NN	O	2	ccomp
6	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
7	be	be	VB	O	8	auxpass
8	done	do	VBN	O	5	advcl
9	in	in	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	Hogwarts	Hogwarts	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	kitchens	kitchen	NNS	O	8	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	but	but	CC	O	5	cc
15	stays	stay	VBZ	O	5	conj
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	her	she	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	spot	spot	NN	O	15	nmod
19	near	near	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	fire	fire	NN	O	18	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Her	she	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	responses	response	NNS	O	8	nsubj
3	to	to	TO	O	5	case
4	recent	recent	JJ	O	5	amod
5	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	2	nmod
6	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
7	only	only	RB	O	8	advmod
8	examples	example	NNS	O	0	ROOT
9	of	of	IN	O	13	case
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	negative	negative	JJ	O	13	amod
12	effects	effect	NNS	O	13	compound
13	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	8	nmod
14	has	have	VBZ	O	16	aux
15	on	on	IN	O	16	case
16	people	people	NNS	O	13	acl:relcl
17	who	who	WP	O	21	nsubj
18	are	be	VBP	O	21	cop
19	not	not	RB	O	21	neg
20	mentally	mentally	RB	O	21	advmod
21	prepared	prepared	JJ	O	8	acl:relcl
22	for	for	IN	O	25	case
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	sudden	sudden	JJ	O	25	amod
25	change	change	NN	O	21	nmod
26	in	in	IN	O	27	case
27	life	life	NN	O	25	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Another	another	DT	O	2	det
2	explanation	explanation	NN	O	13	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	depression	depression	NN	O	2	nmod
7	could	could	MD	O	13	aux
8	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
9	the	the	DT	O	13	det
10	``	``	``	O	13	punct
11	person-environment	person-environment	JJ	O	13	amod
12	fit	fit	NN	O	13	compound
13	theory	theory	NN	O	0	ROOT
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct
15	''	''	''	O	13	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	theory	theory	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	suggests	suggest	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	problems	problem	NNS	O	14	nsubjpass
7	,	,	,	O	14	punct
8	like	like	IN	O	9	case
9	anxiety	anxiety	NN	O	14	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	depression	depression	NN	O	9	conj
12	,	,	,	O	14	punct
13	are	be	VBP	O	14	auxpass
14	caused	cause	VBN	O	3	ccomp
15	from	from	IN	O	18	case
16	a	a	DT	O	18	det
17	sudden	sudden	JJ	O	18	amod
18	change	change	NN	O	14	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	20	case
20	environment	environment	NN	O	18	nmod
21	for	for	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	theory	theory	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	also	also	RB	O	4	advmod
4	claims	claim	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
6	persons	person	NNS	O	7	nsubj
7	seek	seek	VBP	O	4	ccomp
8	work	work	NN	O	9	compound
9	places	place	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
11	they	they	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	feel	feel	VBP	O	7	ccomp
13	comfortable	comfortable	JJ	O	12	xcomp
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	16	punct
16	Reynolds	Reynolds	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	advcl
17	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	16	punct
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	clearly	clearly	RB	O	5	advmod
3	did	do	VBD	O	5	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	feel	feel	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	comfortable	comfortable	JJ	O	10	amod
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	any	any	DT	O	9	det
9	environment	environment	NN	O	6	nmod
10	other	other	JJ	O	5	dobj
11	than	than	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	Crouch	Crouch	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	household	household	NN	O	10	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	problems	problem	NNS	O	2	dobj
4	opening	open	VBG	O	3	acl
5	up	up	RP	O	4	compound:prt
6	to	to	TO	O	9	case
7	her	she	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
8	new	new	JJ	O	9	amod
9	master	master	NN	O	4	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	Dumbledore	Dumbledore	NNP	PERSON	9	appos
12	,	,	,	O	9	punct
13	because	because	IN	O	17	mark
14	she	she	PRP	O	17	nsubjpass
15	was	be	VBD	O	17	auxpass
16	so	so	RB	O	17	advmod
17	caught	catch	VBN	O	4	advcl
18	up	up	RP	O	17	compound:prt
19	in	in	IN	O	21	mark
20	being	be	VBG	O	21	auxpass
21	sacked	sack	VBN	O	17	advcl
22	by	by	IN	O	24	case
23	Barty	Barty	NNP	PERSON	24	compound
24	Crouch	Crouch	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	2	mark
2	clinging	cling	VBG	O	14	advcl
3	to	to	TO	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	secrets	secret	NNS	O	2	nmod
6	she	she	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	kept	keep	VBD	O	5	acl:relcl
8	for	for	IN	O	11	case
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	Crouch	Crouch	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	family	family	NN	O	7	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	14	punct
13	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
14	feels	feel	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
15	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
16	she	she	PRP	O	20	nsubj
17	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
18	still	still	RB	O	20	advmod
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	part	part	NN	O	14	ccomp
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	environment	environment	NN	O	20	nmod
24	she	she	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	feels	feel	VBZ	O	23	acl:relcl
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	most	most	RBS	O	28	advmod
28	comfortable	comfortable	JJ	O	25	dobj
29	in	in	IN	O	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	something	something	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	WDT	O	5	nsubj
5	affects	affect	VBZ	O	3	acl:relcl
6	everyone	everyone	NN	O	5	dobj
7	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Especially	especially	RB	O	3	advmod
2	in	in	IN	O	3	case
3	times	time	NNS	O	9	nmod
4	like	like	IN	O	5	case
5	these	these	DT	O	3	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	9	punct
7	it	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
9	hard	hard	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	know	know	VB	O	9	xcomp
13	someone	someone	NN	O	12	dobj
14	who	who	WP	O	17	nsubjpass
15	has	have	VBZ	O	17	aux
16	been	be	VBN	O	17	auxpass
17	affected	affect	VBN	O	13	acl:relcl
18	by	by	IN	O	22	case
19	the	the	DT	O	22	det
20	sudden	sudden	JJ	O	22	amod
21	financial	financial	JJ	O	22	amod
22	changes	change	NNS	O	17	nmod
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	our	we	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	society	society	NN	O	17	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	an	a	DT	O	5	det
4	excellent	excellent	JJ	O	5	amod
5	example	example	NN	O	17	dep
6	of	of	IN	O	10	case
7	the	the	DT	O	10	det
8	negative	negative	JJ	O	10	amod
9	effects	effect	NNS	O	10	compound
10	unemployment	unemployment	NN	O	5	nmod
11	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
12	have	have	VB	O	10	acl:relcl
13	on	on	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	people	people	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	it	it	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	affects	affect	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
18	directly	directly	RB	O	17	advmod
19	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	2	case
2	events	event	NNS	O	15	nmod
3	like	like	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Great	Great	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Depression	Depression	NNP	O	2	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
8	today	today	NN	DATE	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	recession	recession	NN	O	2	conj
11	,	,	,	O	15	punct
12	researchers	researcher	NNS	O	15	nsubj
13	have	have	VBP	O	15	aux
14	been	be	VBN	O	15	cop
15	able	able	JJ	O	0	ROOT
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	record	record	VB	O	15	xcomp
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	mental	mental	JJ	O	20	amod
20	effects	effect	NNS	O	17	dobj
21	one	one	CD	NUMBER	23	nsubj
22	can	can	MD	O	23	aux
23	expect	expect	VB	O	20	acl:relcl
24	when	when	WRB	O	25	advmod
25	unemployed	unemployed	JJ	O	23	advcl
26	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	J.K.	J.K.	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Rowling	Rowling	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	does	do	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	good	good	JJ	O	6	amod
6	job	job	NN	O	3	dobj
7	revealing	reveal	VBG	O	6	acl
8	them	they	PRP	O	7	dobj
9	in	in	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	character	character	NN	O	12	compound
12	Winky	Winky	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	makes	make	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	reader	reader	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	see	see	VB	O	2	ccomp
6	how	how	WRB	O	13	advmod
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	good	good	JJ	O	9	amod
9	friend	friend	NN	O	13	nsubj
10	like	like	IN	O	11	case
11	Dobby	Dobby	NNP	PERSON	9	nmod
12	can	can	MD	O	13	aux
13	help	help	VB	O	5	ccomp
14	when	when	WRB	O	15	advmod
15	put	put	VBN	O	13	advcl
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	bad	bad	JJ	O	18	amod
18	situations	situation	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

